<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-08-29T12:29:23.405Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TMNT Cowabunga Collection review: A ‘90s dream, a few months too late]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876454</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876454"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[13-game compilation benefits from cool tweaks, rollback netcode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTC Vive headsets go on sale after Meta and PlayStation price hikes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/htc-vive-headsets-go-on-sale-after-meta-and-playstation-price-hikes</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/htc-vive-headsets-go-on-sale-after-meta-and-playstation-price-hikes"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTC Vive is running a sale across its VR hardware from 29th August to 11th September.


The timing of this couldn't have fallen (or been planned) better on HTC's part. Combined with the current cost of living crisis in the UK and the price hikes of both PlayStation 5 and Meta Quest 2, a discount is sorely welcomed.
For UK customers, the full list of discounts includes:
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liv Ngan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The final countdown begins for NASA’s hulking new rocket]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876538</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876538"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T06:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["We are prepared for just about anything."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.25: CSI Inline Volumes have graduated to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/29/csi-inline-volumes-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/29/csi-inline-volumes-ga/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jonathan Dobson (Red Hat)
CSI Inline Volumes were introduced as an alpha feature in Kubernetes 1.15 and have been beta since 1.16. We are happy to announce that this feature has graduated to General Availability (GA) status in Kubernetes 1.25.
CSI Inline Volumes are similar to other ephemeral volume types, such as configMap, downwardAPI and secret. The important difference is that the storage is provided by a CSI driver, which allows the use of ephemeral storage provided by third-party vendors. The volume is defined as part of the pod spec and follows the lifecycle of the pod, meaning the volume is created once the pod is scheduled and destroyed when the pod is destroyed.
What's new in 1.25?
There are a couple of new bug fixes related to this feature in 1.25, and the CSIInlineVolum…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valve's testing an all-new Steam Mobile app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/valves-testing-an-all-new-steam-mobile-app</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/valves-testing-an-all-new-steam-mobile-app"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T16:19:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valve has commenced rolling out a new version of its Steam Mobile app.

Not everyone will be able to give it a try just yet, though, as right now it's only available as part of "a limited beta". Valve said it's holding off from a public release in order to ensure the app works on "so many different phones and devices".

"We’ve rebuilt the app on a new framework and modernized the design," Valve said in a brief blog post on the website, before cheekily adding: "(2015 called and wanted their app back).
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diablo Immortal is redesigning its legendary crests to help players "differentiate" between them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/diablo-immortal-is-redesigning-its-legendary-crests-to-help-players-differentiate-between-them</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/diablo-immortal-is-redesigning-its-legendary-crests-to-help-players-differentiate-between-them"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T16:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blizzard is redesigning Diablo Immortal's legendary crests to "help differentiate" them from the eternal legendary chests that cost players real money.

Responding to a post in the game's subreddit, lead designer Wyatt Cheng said that the team not only wanted to ensure the colours were different, but also change their shape, too, so "players know exactly what they're getting when they make a purchase". 

"This is artwork that we're working on to help differentiate the Legendary Crest (which will become [the] Orange one) from the Eternal Legendary Crest (which will remain the purple one in the middle, that yields gems that can be sold on the Market)," Cheng explained.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There are no plans to bring couch co-op to MultiVersus just yet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/there-are-no-plans-to-bring-couch-co-op-to-multiversus-just-yet</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/there-are-no-plans-to-bring-couch-co-op-to-multiversus-just-yet"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T15:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are no plans to introduce co-op to Multiversus just yet. 

That's according to game director Tony Huynh, who - whilst responding to a question posed by a player on Twitter - said that as the team's current focus is "stabilising [MultiVersus'] experience", any plans to integrate couch co-op is "further out".

Huynh added that right now, "netcode improvements, hurt/hitboxes, projectiles, platform interactions" are most important to the team (thanks, NME).
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An "Xbox Game Pass: Friends and Family" logo has popped up online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/an-xbox-game-pass-friends-and-family-logo-has-popped-up-online</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/an-xbox-game-pass-friends-and-family-logo-has-popped-up-online"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T12:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A logo that says "Xbox Game Pass: Friends and Family" has popped up online.

Reportedly taken from Xbox's own backend system, it comes just weeks after Microsoft revealed that it was trialling an Xbox Game Pass tier that would permit players to share their Game Pass subscription with friends and family members.

Called Xbox Game Pass Insider Preview, the service allows users - currently restricted to Ireland and Colombia - to "add up to four people to [their] subscription, all with their own unique access to Xbox Game Pass Ultimate games, content, and benefits" (thanks, VGC). The newly discovered logo has yet to be formally shared with the public.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sonic Frontiers' file size is almost twice as big as Sonic Forces on Switch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/sonic-frontiers-file-size-is-almost-twice-as-big-as-sonic-forces-on-switch</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/sonic-frontiers-file-size-is-almost-twice-as-big-as-sonic-forces-on-switch"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T12:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sonic Frontiers will weigh in at 10.4GB on Nintendo Switch.

That makes it bulkier than prior Blue Blur games on Switch - as our friends at Nintendo Life point out, Sonic Forces was 6.6GB, and Sonic Colors: Ultimate was 6.8GB - and gives us a hint at how much bigger the latest instalment, set to be an open-world of course, will be.

As for what the game entails? The official store description says: "In search of the missing Chaos emeralds, Sonic becomes stranded on an ancient island teeming with unusual creatures. Battle hordes of powerful enemies as you explore a breathtaking world of action, adventure, and mystery. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twisted Metal TV show wraps filming and moves into post-production]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/twisted-metal-tv-show-wraps-filming-and-moves-into-post-production</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/twisted-metal-tv-show-wraps-filming-and-moves-into-post-production"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T11:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filming has now wrapped on the Twisted Metal TV show.

Set to star Will Arnett, Anthony Mackie, and Samoa Joe, the crew working on the live-action television series adapting destruction racer Twisted Metal had a wrap party over the weekend.

"That’s a wrap on season one!" tweeted showrunner Michael Jonathan, who also wrote the fan-favourite Netflix show, Cobra Kai (via VGC).
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Splatoon 3 cheaters are reportedly getting console and Nintendo Switch Online bans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/splatoon-3-cheaters-are-reportedly-getting-console-and-nintendo-switch-online-bans</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/splatoon-3-cheaters-are-reportedly-getting-console-and-nintendo-switch-online-bans"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T10:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Players are already trying to cheat in Splatoon 3, and Nintendo's already banning them.

As spotted by Nintendo dataminer OatmealDome, Nintendo is reportedly cracking down on players who are modifying the game, including a patch that let players prematurely enter the testing range. 

Affected players are getting console bans and "possibly" total bans from subscription service Nintendo Switch Online, too, without which players cannot access multiplayer features. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The weekend’s best deals: Apple iPad, MacBook Pro, OLED TVs, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876456</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876456"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T19:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealmaster also has HyperX gaming headsets, the Google Chromecast, and the Xbox Series S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Dunn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nightdive Studios says the fate of a third System Shock game lies in Tencent's hands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/nightdive-studios-says-the-fate-of-a-third-system-shock-game-lies-in-tencents-hands</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/nightdive-studios-says-the-fate-of-a-third-system-shock-game-lies-in-tencents-hands"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T16:39:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nightdive Studios has confirmed that the fate of the third instalment of the eagerly-anticipated System Shock series still lies with Tencent.

In an interview at Gamescom, CEO Stephen Kick confirmed that whilst his studio retains the right to remake the first - and potentially second - game from the series, rights to the third game were sold to Tencent.

"When we originally acquired the rights to the franchise, we licensed the rights for the third game to Warren and Paul [Neurath] at Otherside. They then subsequently sold their rights to Tencent," he told VGC.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GTFO developer 10 Chambers has a co-op heist FPS in "pre-production"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/gtfo-developer-10-chambers-has-a-co-op-heist-fps-in-pre-production</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/gtfo-developer-10-chambers-has-a-co-op-heist-fps-in-pre-production"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T16:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GTFO developer 10 Chambers has confirmed its next game will be a "techno-thriller" co-op heist shooter that "just has to be made".
In an interview with NME at Gamescom, 10 Chambers' creative director and CEO Ulf Andersson said that after working on Payday and Payday 2 before leaving for make GTFO with 10 Chambers, he still yearns to work on another heist game, saying "it feels like an unclosed chapter".

"So for me, this game is a game that just has to be made," Andersson said. "I’m back on the heist shit, basically – so it’s a heist cooperative FPS, and it has a sort of a techno-thriller theme. I read a lot of sci-fi books, and so imagine everything that cyberpunk is inspired by, and a ton of other shit.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: HP’s 13.5-inch Spectre x360 is a top ultralight—with flair]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1871379</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1871379"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T13:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not the top performer, but the Spectre has other wins, like its 3:2 screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scharon Harding</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terror Zones are coming to Diablo 2: Resurrected]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/terror-zones-are-coming-to-diablo-2-resurrected</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/terror-zones-are-coming-to-diablo-2-resurrected"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T11:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diablo 2: Resurrected has launched a public test realm for the upcoming 2.5 patch that boasts an all-new "experimental" feature: Terror Zones.

As well as a "variety of bug fixes to address feedback the community has provided" Blizzard, Terror Zones see you take up monsters at least two levels higher than you (or their original level) for extra XP and loot in the hope we'll stop "repeatedly farming" Baal, Diablo, or Nihlathak.

"The journey to level 99 is a celebrated experience for players and quite the milestone if achieved - a rite of passage, even," Blizzard explains in the patch notes. "We want to offer an alternative to repeatedly farming Baal, Diablo, or Nihlathak. We also want the journey to level 99 to be accessible to a larger population of players, full of variety, and most importantly, challenging - this is where Terror Zones come in. As we get into details, please note that players can choose to opt-out of Terror Zones if desired.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NBA 2K23 has "all-new ways to play in MyTEAM"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/nba-2k23-has-all-new-ways-to-play-in-myteam</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/nba-2k23-has-all-new-ways-to-play-in-myteam"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T11:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NBA 2K23 has "all-new ways to play in MyTEAM", including Triple threat Online: Co-op and Clutch Time single player, as well as the ability to remove contracts. 

2K also confirmed that the annual $250,000 MyTEAM Unlimited tournament is back this year, too, with two tracks: one for last-gen consoles, and another for PS5 and Xbox Series X/S consoles.

Triple Threat Online: Co-op - a new mode to MyTEAM - allows players to partner with friends for 3v3 co-op "across different variations" of gameplay. There's also Unlimited, which allows players that reach the top tier to start over and unlock "even more rewards" via Season Points, and Clutch Time Single Player enables you to "jump into a single player version of Clutch Time, a fast-paced mode with a 4-point line, to take your best starting five and compete against the AI".
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indie mining game Dome Keeper gets a September release date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/indie-mining-game-dome-keeper-gets-a-september-release-date</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/indie-mining-game-dome-keeper-gets-a-september-release-date"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T10:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indie mining action game Dome Keeper will release on 27th September.

In anticipation of the full release - which will be coming to Steam - developer Bippinbits will be taking down its free playable demo on 5th September, so don't hang about if you've been meaning to try it.

Dome Keeper - once known as Dome Romantik - boasts "beautiful updated pixel art, atmospheric music and sound" and sees you defend your dome from wave after wave of hostile attacks in this roguelike survival miner. Inbetween attacks, you need to dig beneath the surface in search of valuable resources which can be used to make upgrades to help you stay alive and "make it to the next world".
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix's new Resident Evil show has already been cancelled]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/netflixs-new-resident-evil-show-has-already-been-cancelled</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/netflixs-new-resident-evil-show-has-already-been-cancelled"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T10:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In news that's unlikely to surprise you, Netflix has cancelled its Resident Evil series after just a single season.

The show - which stars Ella Balinska, Tamara Smart, and Lance Reddick - only debuted on 14th July, but Deadline reports that "as the drama did not have a particularly strong showing on Netflix's Top 10 and cost vs. viewing is the streamer's leading renewal criterion", Netflix has declined to order a second series.

On Rotten Tomatoes, the show is currently sitting at 55 per cent for critics, with an audience score of 27 per cent. On Metacritic, it's even worse, boasting a critic score of 53 and a user score of 1.5. Ouch.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: 14-foot Giant Squid Washes Ashore in Cape Town]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/friday-squid-blogging-14-foot-giant-squid-washes-ashore-in-cape-town.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/friday-squid-blogging-14-foot-giant-squid-washes-ashore-in-cape-town.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T21:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s an <a href="https://www.livescience.com/giant-squid-cape-town-beach"><i>Architeuthis dux</i></a>, the second this year.</p>
<p>As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven&#8217;t covered.</p>
<p>Read my blog posting guidelines <a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2017/03/commenting_poli.html">here</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody Saves the World launching Frozen Hearth DLC next month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/nobody-saves-the-worlds-frozen-hearth-dlc-seeking-the-strongest-warriors-next-month</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/nobody-saves-the-worlds-frozen-hearth-dlc-seeking-the-strongest-warriors-next-month"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T20:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guacamelee developer Drinkbox Studios has announced Frozen Hearth, a new chunk of paid DLC heading to its action-RPG Nobody Saves the World on 13th September.


Frozen Hearth takes players to a forgotten new region, deep underground, "where the strongest warriors compete for glory in The Tempering". Here, hardy adventurers can tackle a series of puzzles and challenges intended to test their transformation skills and creativity, unlocking the new Killer Bee and Mechanic forms that can be used in the DLC and main game.


"When we shipped the original game, there were so many ideas we had to leave on the cutting room floor, and this DLC gave us a chance to bring some of them to life," Nobody Saves the World lead designer Ian Campbell explained in a statement accompanying today's announcement. "We had a blast creating even more forms, as well as puzzles and challenges that make the most of the game’s mix-and-match customisation".
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The number of companies caught up in the Twilio hack keeps growing]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876496</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876496"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T19:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2FA provider Authy, password manager LastPass, and DoorDash all experienced breaches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some day we’ll be recycling wind turbine blades into yummy gummy bears]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876374</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876374"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T19:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recyclable polymer resin could also be used for car taillights, diapers, kitchen sinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warframe's Veilbreaker update brings 50th Warframe Styanax, new story quest and more next month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/warframes-veilbreaker-update-brings-50th-warframe-styanax-new-story-quest-and-more-next-month</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/warframes-veilbreaker-update-brings-50th-warframe-styanax-new-story-quest-and-more-next-month"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Extremes has shared more on Warframe's Veilbreaker update, confirming it'll be launching for all platforms some time in September, and that players will be able to get instant free access to Styanax - the sci-fi shooter's 50th Warframe - for two weeks after its arrival.


Styanax - who gets a proper introduction in the animated Ascension Day trailer below - is described as a "mighty and herculean" Warframe whose designed is inspired by the ancient Greek warrior Astyanax. His abilities include the Axios Javelin - which can push back enemies on impact, causing damage if they hit a wall - and the Tharros Strike shield, capable of repelling enemies and reducing their shields and armour as it's swung around, regenerating Styanax's health with each successfully landed blow.

Styanax can also call on Rally Point to draw enemies to his position and regenerate the energy and shields of nearby allies (regeneration increases as the number of enemies near him grows), or deploy Final Stand - causing him to rise into the air and unleash a barrage of javelins that'll damage nearby enemies upon hitting the ground. Additional damage occurs on a direct hit.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poopy lettuce at Wendy’s still prime suspect in outbreak that just doubled]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876438</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876438"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T17:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wendy's has already pulled the suspect lettuce from its burgers and sandwiches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Walmart lists a 30TB portable SSD for $39. It is, naturally, a scam]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876366</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876366"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T17:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But the "30TB" disk does at least try to fool users in clever ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COVID coalition over, Moderna sues Pfizer and BioNTech over vaccines]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876381</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876381"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T16:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With vaccines widely available, Moderna wants to be paid for its earlier work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Purdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s next VR headset will launch in October]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876392</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876392"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T16:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The headset is likely Project Cambria, and it will debut at Connect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 ways every company can get started with an open-source software strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/?p=66657</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-26-3-ways-every-company-can-get-started-with-an-open-source-software-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T16:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future of software development does not exist without open source. However, to maintain today’s software and create the software of the future, the largest organizations and beneficiaries of open source need to expand their collaboration with the community and help it grow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Wolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sifu getting new scoring system, more modifiers in next week's big update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/sifu-getting-new-scoring-system-more-modifiers-in-next-weeks-big-summer-update</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/sifu-getting-new-scoring-system-more-modifiers-in-next-weeks-big-summer-update"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T15:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Sloclap has detailed Sifu's big summer update - which is set to bring the likes of a new scoring system and gameplay modifiers - ahead of its arrival next Wednesday, 31st August.


Top of the list of new additions for the kung-fu beat-'em-up is the aforementioned new scoring system, which will "take into account every punch, kick, sweep and finisher performed" in order to rank players based on smoothness, efficiency and variety. "Dismantle a group of enemies without getting hit," Sloclap adds, "and players will be greeted with a score worth flaunting."


Elsewhere, next week's update brings a range of modifiers designed to suit all tastes. At one end of the spectrum, struggling players will be able to significantly reduce Sifu's challenge by giving themselves the likes of infinite health, structure, and unbreakable weapons. Those looking to further test their mettle, however, can prevent themselves from picking up weapons and set enemies to ignore guarding, or go even further by reducing their character down to a single hit point and bumping enemy strength up even further.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo ThinkPad X1 Carbon Gen 10 review: A fast-but-flawed version of a great laptop]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1872564</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1872564"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T15:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel's 12th-gen CPUs make for a mixed upgrade to one of the best laptops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Last of Us Part 1 accessibility features include ability to play dialogue through DualSense as haptic feedback]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/last-of-us-part-1-accessibility-features-include-ability-to-play-dialogue-through-dualsense-as-haptic-feedback</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/last-of-us-part-1-accessibility-features-include-ability-to-play-dialogue-through-dualsense-as-haptic-feedback"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T14:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new blog post has laid out all of the upcoming accessibility features for The Last of Us Part 1 on the PlayStation 5.


This includes a new feature that will enable players to play dialogue through the console's DualSense controller as haptic feedback.


This new feature, which started off as a prototype, means that "a deaf player can feel the way a line is delivered, can feel the emphasis, along with the subtitles to give some sense of how that line is delivered," explained game director Matthew Gallant.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dead by Daylight's Resident Evil chapter now has a release date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/dead-by-daylights-resident-evil-chapter-now-has-a-release-date</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/dead-by-daylights-resident-evil-chapter-now-has-a-release-date"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T14:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dead by Daylight's Resident Evil chapter will release on 30th August.


Called Project W, it's the second Resident Evil collaboration between developer Behaviour Interactive and Capcom.


Albert Wesker will be the new Killer, while Ada Wong and Rebecca Chambers will be new Survivors.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[See first gameplay of Team Ninja's Wo Long: Fallen Dynasty in new trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/see-first-gameplay-of-team-ninjas-wo-long-fallen-dynasty-in-new-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/see-first-gameplay-of-team-ninjas-wo-long-fallen-dynasty-in-new-trailer"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T14:08:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new trailer for Team Ninja's Wo Long: Fallen Dynasty has been released, showing off gameplay for the first time.


The Soulslike game was announced during the Xbox and Bethesda Showcase in June and will be released in 2023 across Xbox consoles and PC (Game Pass on both), and PlayStation consoles.


It's led by producers Fumihiko Yasuda (Nioh) and Masaaki Yamagiwa (Bloodborne), and judging by the below trailer it certainly looks familiar.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The white Xbox Elite Series 2 controller has been sighted again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/the-white-xbox-elite-series-2-controller-has-been-sighted-again</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/the-white-xbox-elite-series-2-controller-has-been-sighted-again"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T14:06:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The long-rumoured white Xbox Elite Series 2 controller - pictured above - has been spotted again online.

Earlier this month, footage of the controller surfaced on YouTube, and pictures of its packaging were posted to Twitter back in March.

Microsoft has not made an official statement regarding the white controller's release, or even acknowledging that it is real, but more solid evidence of its existence has appeared.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liv Ngan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disney Dreamlight Valley has a free character creator available now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/disney-dreamlight-valley-has-a-free-character-creator-available-now</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/disney-dreamlight-valley-has-a-free-character-creator-available-now"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T13:48:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disney Dreamlight Valley has a free character creator you can download now ahead of the game's release.


Developed by Gameloft, it's a free-to-play Disney farming sim that has players harvesting crops and meeting a variety of Disney characters.


The character creator is available on Steam and Epic and gives players a chance to fiddle around with their own character. Kingdom Hearts fans will surely be happy.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LG’s 4K monitor physically adjusts itself so you don’t have to]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876340</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876340"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T13:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LG claims a camera and AI help ensure good ergonomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scharon Harding</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracer Group completes acquisition of Square Enix's western studios]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/embracer-group-completes-acquisition-of-square-enixs-western-studios</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/embracer-group-completes-acquisition-of-square-enixs-western-studios"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T13:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embracer Group has now completed its acquisition of Square Enix's western studios, namely Crystal Dynamics, Eidos-Montréal, and Square Enix Montréal.


Back in May, Square Enix sold off its western studios and IP (including Tomb Raider and Deus Ex) to Embracer for just $300m.



Now, three months later, the acquisition has been completed, according to a press release from Embracer.

 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a lengthy look at Square Enix's fantasy farming  sim Harvestella]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/heres-a-lengthy-look-at-square-enixs-fantasy-farming-sim-harvestella</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/heres-a-lengthy-look-at-square-enixs-fantasy-farming-sim-harvestella"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T12:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of its latest Treehouse: Live showcase, Nintendo has shared a lengthy look at Square Enix's upcoming fantasy farming sim Harvestella, showing off its story, its world exploration and combat, its farming, fishing, and more.


Harvestella - a sort of blend of Final Fantasy, Harvest Moon, and Rune Factory - begins with players waking up with a bad case of amnesia in a world where the seasons are governed by four giant crystals known as Seaslight. Unfortunately for the locals, something has gone awry and a deadly dust known as the Quietus has started seeping from the crystals, trapping people indoors and causing crops to wither and die.


And that's not the end of their problems; as players settle into a vacant house on the outskirts of Lethe Village, a huge comet falls to the earth nearby, bringing with it the armoured body of an Omen, thought to be the cause of the calamity. We see some of this in Nintendo's showcase, but the bulk of the play-through is focused around Harvestella's second chapter as players start to explore the dungeon-like Higan Canyon, with help from new pal Dianthus.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo responds to PlayStation price hike]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/nintendo-responds-to-playstation-price-hike</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/nintendo-responds-to-playstation-price-hike"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T12:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo has joined Microsoft in responding to this week's shock PlayStation 5 price hike, and said it had "no plans" to similarly bump up the Nintendo Switch's cost.


In a statement issued to Eurogamer this morning, Nintendo confirmed it had "no plans to increase the trade price of its hardware". 


The response goes further than that of Microsoft's, which last night noted Sony's dramatic decision by simply stating it was keen to "offer our fans great gaming options", before reiterating the Xbox Series X and S's launch price point.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security and Cheap Complexity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/security-and-cheap-complexity.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/security-and-cheap-complexity.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T11:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ve been saying that complexity is the worst enemy of security for a long time now. (<a href="https://www.schneier.com/essays/archives/1999/11/a_plea_for_simplicit.html">Here&#8217;s</a> me in 1999.) And it&#8217;s been true for a long time.</p>
<p>In 2018, Thomas Dullien of Google&#8217;s Project Zero <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q98foLaAfX8">talked</a> <a href="http://rule11.tech/papers/2018-complexitysecuritysec-dullien.pdf">about</a> &#8220;cheap complexity.&#8221; Andrew Appel <a href="https://freedom-to-tinker.com/2022/08/03/the-anomaly-of-cheap-complexity/">summarizes</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>The anomaly of cheap complexity.  For most of human history, a more complex device was more expensive to build than a simpler device.  This is not the case in modern computing. It is often more cost-effective to take a very complicated device, and make it simulate simplicity, than to make a simpler device.  This is because of economies of scale: complex general-purpose CPUs are cheap.  On the other hand, custom-designed, ...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Splatoon fans think they've found the franchise's flooded world map]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/splatoon-fans-think-theyve-found-the-franchises-flooded-world-map</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/splatoon-fans-think-theyve-found-the-franchises-flooded-world-map"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T11:39:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fans think they've found a world map which shows off the Splatoon series' flooded planet in full detail. 


As a reminder, Splatoon lore fans believe that Nintendo's shooter series is set in a post-apocalyptic future where the sea levels have risen and much of our current world is underwater.


Indeed, the new map - apparently uncovered from the files of Splatoon 3's World Premiere Splatfest demo - appears to support that claim. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MacBook self-repair program highlights Apple’s flawed repairability progress]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876132</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876132"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T11:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's more amenable to self-repairs, but complex processes and designs are limiting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scharon Harding</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Puzzle Bobble Everybubble! is a Nintendo Switch exclusive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/puzzle-bobble-everybubble-is-a-nintendo-switch-exclusive</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/puzzle-bobble-everybubble-is-a-nintendo-switch-exclusive"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T11:20:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Puzzle Bobble Everybubble! is a new Puzzle Bobble game exclusive to Nintendo Switch.

If you don't know what Puzzle Bobble is, it started out as a match-three arcade game based off Bubble Bobble. Players are faced with a prearranged pattern of coloured bubbles, and must fire bubbles up towards their matching colours to clear the screen before the bubbles get too low.
Bubble Bobble's Puzzle Bobble's Puzzle Bobble Everybubble! sure is one heck of a tongue twister.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liv Ngan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon planning to buy EA - report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/amazon-planning-to-buy-ea-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/amazon-planning-to-buy-ea-report"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T11:14:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Online retail giant Amazon is set to announce an offer to buy FIFA publisher EA, a new report has claimed. 

USA Today sources state that Amazon will formally announce its offer later today. There's no detail yet on how much it will bid. 


EA has recently been the subject of several takeover rumours, with Apple and Disney also claimed to be among other interested parties. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocket Report: At long last the SLS is ready, Alpha gets a launch date]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875923</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875923"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T11:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["For the uncrewed demo, the goal is to have a safe landing."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can now download a booklet from Valve chronicling "the story of Steam Deck"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/you-can-now-download-a-booklet-from-valve-chronicling-the-story-of-steam-deck</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/you-can-now-download-a-booklet-from-valve-chronicling-the-story-of-steam-deck"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T10:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To celebrate the upcoming launch of the Steam Deck in Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and Hong Kong, Valve has released a new booklet all about the company, Steam, and its handheld Steam Deck PC. 


This booklet is just over 50 pages long, and is available in Japanese, Korean, Traditional Chinese, and English. 


It covers some background information on the company, as well as an overview of Steam including "how it came to be and where it is now", and the "story of Steam Deck".
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Denuvo won't affect Switch performance, spokesperson claims]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/denuvo-wont-affect-switch-performance-spokesperson-claims</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/denuvo-wont-affect-switch-performance-spokesperson-claims"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T10:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Denuvo has clarified more details of its upcoming Nintendo Switch Emulator Protection solution, which it announced earlier this week.
In its announcement, the company invited publishers to include Denuvo's anti-tamper software in Switch games to help crack down on piracy and PC emulation. But many fans were not happy with Denuvo's involvement, worried about the effect the software may have on performance.
A Denuvo spokeperson has since responded to questions surrounding the software, as well as the driving parties behind it.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liv Ngan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big the Cat finally seen in Sonic Frontiers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/big-the-cat-finally-seen-in-sonic-frontiers</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/big-the-cat-finally-seen-in-sonic-frontiers"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T10:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've finally seen Big the Cat in Sonic Frontiers.


The big purple creature first appeared in Sonic Adventure on the Dreamcast and has since become a fan favourite character, appearing in a number of games in the series.


It's been known for a while that Big the Cat would feature, but thanks to Twitter user Bibs he's been spotted with Sonic in-game at Gamescom.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Total War, Hyenas developer Creative Assembly announces new "action project"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/total-war-hyenas-developer-creative-assembly-announces-new-action-project</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/total-war-hyenas-developer-creative-assembly-announces-new-action-project"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T10:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Creative Assembly has revealed it is working on a new "action project" that will sit alongside the likes of Total War and its long-in-the-works sci-fi shooter Hyenas.


But don't expect to hear more on this project anytime soon, Creative Assembly said today. Instead, there will be a "significant wait before further details are revealed" on this new franchise. Intriguingly, the company noted it also had plans for a separate "yet to be announced project". 


While Creative Assembly did not go into any specifics about what its new action project will look like, it did state that its studio in Sofia would be leading its development, and noted it was now looking for candidates to join the team that had "experience working on third-person titles using the Unreal 5 engine".
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need for Speed gameplay snippet leaks online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/need-for-speed-gameplay-snippet-leaks-online</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/need-for-speed-gameplay-snippet-leaks-online"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T10:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A first glimpse at gameplay from the next Need for Speed has popped up online, showing off the game's new visual style.


Reportedly due out this November, publisher EA has officially kept very quiet about its upcoming racer, which was previously delayed from 2021. 


This week, screenshots apparently from a work-in-progress build of the still-untitled game began to appear on reddit. Last night, the brief gameplay clip these images were taken from was also posted. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audi will build F1 engines, entering the sport in 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876328</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876328"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T10:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Audi is one of two VW Group brands that will enter F1 when the new rules come in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surgeon Simulator and other Bossa Studios IP bought by TinyBuild for £3m]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/surgeon-simulator-and-other-bossa-studios-ip-bought-by-tinybuild-for-3m</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/surgeon-simulator-and-other-bossa-studios-ip-bought-by-tinybuild-for-3m"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T09:51:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bossa Studios' various gaming franchises has been acquired by publisher TinyBuild for $3m.


Those franchises include Surgeon Simulator, I am Fish, and I am Bread, which will now be developed by TinyBuild to allow Bossa to focus on other projects, GamesIndustry.biz reported this morning.



TinyBuild is known for publishing indie games, including the likes of Hello Neighbor, Graveyard Keeper, Pathologic 2 and more.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget 5G wireless, SpaceX and T-Mobile want to offer Zero-G coverage]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876061</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876061"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T03:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["So it's really quite a difficult technical challenge."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Swirls]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2664/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2664/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/cloud_swirls.png" title="'Why did you get into fluid dynamics?' 'Well, SOME planet has to have the coolest clouds, odds are it's not ours, and rockets are slow.'" alt="'Why did you get into fluid dynamics?' 'Well, SOME planet has to have the coolest clouds, odds are it's not ours, and rockets are slow.'" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An herbal remedy caused the death of CA congressman’s wife]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876299</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876299"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T22:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bit of undigested white mulberry leaf was found in the woman's stomach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft responds to PlayStation 5 price hike news]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/microsoft-responds-to-playstation-5-price-hike-news</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/microsoft-responds-to-playstation-5-price-hike-news"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T21:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following Sony's announcement that it will be raising the price of PlayStation 5 in select countries, Microsoft has responded to the news, merely noting that existing Xbox Series X/S prices remain the same.


Sony announced it would be increasing the cost of PlayStation 5 - in response to "high global inflation rates, as well as adverse currency trends" - earlier today, with the price hike impacting most markets around the world, effective immediately.


That increase affects both the disc and disc-less models of PS5, and equates to £30 in the UK and €50 in Europe - with similar bumps occurring in Japan, China, Australia, Mexico, and Canada, but not the US for the time being.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US government to make all research it funds open access on publication]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876279</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876279"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T21:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Policy will go into effect in 2026, apply to everything that gets federal money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix's live-action BioShock movie will be helmed by I Am Legend director]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/netflixs-live-action-bioshock-movie-will-be-helmed-by-i-am-legend-hunger-games-director</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/netflixs-live-action-bioshock-movie-will-be-helmed-by-i-am-legend-hunger-games-director"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T19:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following Netflix's announcement earlier this year that it's adapting Irrational Games' acclaimed shooter BioShock into a live-action film, the streaming service has revealed it's now secured a writer and director for the project.


When word of the BioShock adaptation first broke in February, there was little to go on beyond the fact it was being developed alongside publisher Take-Two and Vertigo Entertainment with an eye on turning it into a cinematic universe.


Now, though, Netflix has revealed that two key roles on the project have now been filled, with Francis Lawrence having signed on in the director role. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists explore chemistry of tattoo inks amid growing safety concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876072</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876072"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T19:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Every time we looked at one of the inks, we found something that gave me pause.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flaming Espinas joins Monster Hunter Rise: Sunbreak in next free update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/flaming-espinas-coming-to-monster-hunter-rise-sunbreak-in-next-free-update</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/flaming-espinas-coming-to-monster-hunter-rise-sunbreak-in-next-free-update"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T18:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's only been a couple of weeks since Capcom dropped the first free title update for Monster Hunter Rise's Sunbreak expansion, but already the publisher is teasing Update 2, with a first look at incoming new monster variant Flaming Espinas.


Espinas returned to the Monster Hunter series back in August with the launch of Rise's Sunbreak expansion, marking the first time the creature had made the roster in a new game since its debut in 2008's Monster Hunter Frontier 2.0.


In its base form, Espinas is a Flying Wyvern capable of paralysis, poison, and fireblight, and while Capcom is yet to reveal how Title Update 2's new Flaming Espinas variant will differ, there's a look at the creature in the publisher's newly revealed teaser trailer below.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phishers who hit Twilio and Cloudflare stole 10k credentials from 136 others]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876223</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876223"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T18:27:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Already regarded among the most advanced, the attacks were also done at a massive scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shadow of the Tomb Raider is free on the Epic Games Store next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/shadow-of-the-tomb-raider-is-free-on-the-epic-games-store-next-week</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/shadow-of-the-tomb-raider-is-free-on-the-epic-games-store-next-week"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T17:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone with a hankering for some glum action-adventuring should keep an eye on the Epic Games Store next, when Shadow of the Tomb Raider - the final instalment in Square Enix's gloomy rebooted series - will be free to download, alongside Submerged: Hidden Depths.


Shadow of the Tomb Raider, if you're unfamiliar, picks up its narrative around a year after the events of 2015's Rise of the Tomb Raider, following young Lara Croft as she races through the Peruvian jungle in a bid to stop a Mayan apocalypse.


"This is a well-crafted and polished experience," Eurogamer's Aoife Wilson wrote in her Shadow of the Tomb Raider review in 2018, "and when [it] actually gives you full control and leaves you alone to seek out its quieter mysteries, it can render you wide-eyed with wonder".
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Fuchsia OS is taking over smart displays, now on its second device]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876096</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876096"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T17:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The quiet rollout of Google's secretive OS continues, but don't expect any changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GPU shortage is over. The GPU surplus has arrived!]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876083</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876083"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T17:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2021, it was nearly impossible to buy a GPU for a decent price. Not anymore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping your skillset fresh as a developer]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/?p=66604</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-25-keeping-your-skillset-fresh-as-a-developer/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T17:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’re committing 30 minutes or 3 hours a day to learning, consistency is key. Klint Finley asks 3 tech professionals at different stages in their career for more advice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Klint Finley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two swatting attempts on Marjorie Taylor Greene used bog-standard tech]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876109</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876109"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T17:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One was an "attempted swatting." The other was a "false report of a crime."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Belanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DuckDuckGo now offers anti-tracking email service to everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876093</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876093"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T15:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They're totally cool with you giving their emails out to spammy companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Purdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Flight Simulator 40th Anniversary Edition details have landed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/microsoft-flight-simulator-40th-anniversary-edition-details-have-landed</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/microsoft-flight-simulator-40th-anniversary-edition-details-have-landed"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T15:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More details about the 40th Anniversary Edition of Microsoft Flight Simulator have been released to celebrate the return of Gamescom.
Previously, a few of the aircraft to appear in it were confirmed for the special edition during the Xbox Showcase back in June.
Meanwhile, the game's first ever city update, available from today, is detailed in an Xbox blog. Five German photogrammetry cities have been added to the game: Hanover, Dortmund, Dusseldorf, Bonn and Cologne. Players can download the update for free from the game's marketplace and take in the sights of Germany from the air.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liv Ngan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umbrella Academy executive producer developing Netflix's Horizon Zero Dawn show]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/umbrella-academy-executive-producer-developing-netflixs-horizon-zero-dawn-show</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/umbrella-academy-executive-producer-developing-netflixs-horizon-zero-dawn-show"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T14:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony revealed its plans to adapt Horizon Zero Dawn for TV back in May. 


Now, it has been announced that Steve Blackman, who is the showrunner for The Umbrella Academy (as well as working on the currently in development ISS drama Orbital) will be responsible for this upcoming adaptation (via Deadline).

Blackman spoke of his enthusiasm for the Netflix project, calling Guerrilla's Horizon Zero Dawn an "exceptionally well-crafted game with wonderful characters not often seen in the rank-and-file of the gaming world."
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia blames "challenging market conditions" for Q3 forecast misses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/nvidia-blames-challenging-market-conditions-for-q3-forecast-misses</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/nvidia-blames-challenging-market-conditions-for-q3-forecast-misses"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T14:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Graphics card maker Nvidia is also feeling the sting of the current economic climate.
Its recent financial report revealed the company fell short of Wall Street's Q3 expectations, blaming "challenging market conditions" for this setback (via CNBC).

Two weeks ago, Nvidia predicted it would not meet Wall Street's finacial estimates, commenting that it had seen a significant slow down in growth driven by "disappointing" sales. At this time, Nvidia also stated it would see a decline in its gross margin.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Trilogy: a new database adapter for Ruby on Rails]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/?p=66578</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-25-introducing-trilogy-a-new-database-adapter-for-ruby-on-rails/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T14:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've open sourced Trilogy, the database adapter we use to connect Ruby on Rails to MySQL-compatible database servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Draper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California calls time on internal combustion engines from 2035]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876077</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876077"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T14:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the face of federal inaction, the Golden State acts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supermassive Games pays homage to classic slasher horror in The Devil In Me]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/supermassive-games-pays-homage-to-classic-slasher-horror-in-the-devil-in-me</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/supermassive-games-pays-homage-to-classic-slasher-horror-in-the-devil-in-me"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T14:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of its appearance at Gamescom, Eurogamer was given the chance to watch a pre-prepared keynote on The Devil In Me, the next instalment and first season finale of Supermassive Games’ The Dark Pictures Anthology. The preview, hosted by director Tom Heaton, included footage from one of the episode’s later scenes, and a look at its various gameplay improvements.

This early look began by introducing the story and main characters of The Devil In Me, and setting up its stakes. Supermassive’s latest horror chapter centres on Lonnit Entertainment, a small TV production company developing a documentary series on famous serial killers, and a gentleman named Granthem Du'Met, who inherited a hotel with reproductions of rooms from HH Holmes' infamous “Murder Castle”. Once the team arrives to meet Du'Met, however, it's clear the hotel is a much more accurate reproduction than they previously realised.
Kate Wilder, played by Jessie Buckley, stars as the show's presenter. In our preview she was described as introverted and lacking self-confidence, but with a fierce determination to do the right thing. Heaton later told me that Wilder was "quite damaged" when I asked more about the character. "She's carrying this secret most of the people on the crew don't know about at all," he said, and added that she could sometimes snap at people while attempting to process issues from the past.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liv Ngan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's Amazon Prime Gaming's September line-up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/here-is-amazon-prime-gamings-september-line-up</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/here-is-amazon-prime-gamings-september-line-up"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T14:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon has just announced its September line-up for Prime Gaming members.
September's games are: Assassin's Creed Origins, Middle-earth: Shadow of Mordor Game of the Year Edition, Football Manager 2022, The Dig, Defend the Rook, We. The Revolution, Castle on the Coast, and Word of the Law: Death Mask Collector's Edition.

Amazon has additionally teamed up with Ubisoft to offer more in-game content for Ubisoft titles, including Skull and Bones, Rainbow Six Siege and Assassin's Creed Valhalla.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liv Ngan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony reluctantly raises PS5 price, but knows it can get away with it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/eurogamer-newscast-special-playstation-5-price-rise-knows-it-can-get-away-with-it</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/eurogamer-newscast-special-playstation-5-price-rise-knows-it-can-get-away-with-it"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T13:47:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony has announced a shock price rise for the PlayStation 5, and in a Eurogamer Newscast special, we're here to discuss why the company has pulled this undoubtedly unpopular move - and why it's likely to get away with it. 

Will Sony sell fewer PS5s as a result? It seems unlikely. But it's more pressure on PlayStation, which has already had to defend its £70/$70 price point for games - including the upcoming The Last of Us: Part 1 remaster - and just this week announced an expensive-looking new PlayStation 5 controller. 
At a time when all of us are looking at our bank balance's bottom line, an extra £30 to buy a PS5 marks not just an unprecedented decision by Sony, but a troubling sign of the times. Will Microsoft now feel emboldened to follow suit, or soak up any extra costs as a point of difference? Tom Phillips, Ed Nightingale, Victoria Kennedy and Ishraq Subhan discuss.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon to close US telehealth service as it shifts sector ambitions]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876068</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876068"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T13:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech group has other ideas to gain foothold in $4 trillion health care market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Financial Times</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Monthly: August 2022 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/?p=66595</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-25-open-source-monthly-august-2022-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T13:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month's featured open source project, Open Sauced, connects contributors and maintainers through analytical insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rizel Scarlett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony raises PlayStation 5 console prices in many regions, effective immediately]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876040</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1876040"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T12:08:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[United States escapes the price hike, which ranges between 3-13% around the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HP’s new Thunderbolt 4 monitor uses contrast-rich IPS Black tech]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875918</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875918"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T12:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An option for power workers seeking deeper contrast without Mini LED or OLED prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scharon Harding</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HP’s 5K ultrawide all-in-one has workhorse specs, dual magnetic webcams]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875810</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875810"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T12:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a gimmick or two, but it's also one of the highest-specced AIOs around.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scharon Harding</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man-in-the-Middle Phishing Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/man-in-the-middle-phishing-attack.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/man-in-the-middle-phishing-attack.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T11:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here&#8217;s a <a href="https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2022/07/microsoft-details-phishing-campaign-that-can-hijack-mfa-protected-accounts/">phishing campaign</a> that uses a man-in-the-middle attack to defeat multi-factor authentication:</p>
<blockquote><p>Microsoft observed a campaign that inserted an attacker-controlled proxy site between the account users and the work server they attempted to log into. When the user entered a password into the proxy site, the proxy site sent it to the real server and then relayed the real server&#8217;s response back to the user. Once the authentication was completed, the threat actor stole the session cookie the legitimate site sent, so the user doesn&#8217;t need to be reauthenticated at every new page visited. The campaign began with a phishing email with an HTML attachment leading to the proxy server...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to expect from Apple’s September 7 “Far Out” event]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875865</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875865"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New iPhones and Watches: you bet. New Macs and iPads? Probably not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypt of the NecroDancer gets standalone rhythm game spin-off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/crypt-of-the-necrodancer-gets-standalone-rhythm-game-spin-off</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/crypt-of-the-necrodancer-gets-standalone-rhythm-game-spin-off"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T11:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypt of the NecroDancer is getting a new standalone rhythm game spin-off.


Last month developer Brace Yourself Games updated its game for the first time in five years and teased that something new was on the way.


And now we know: Rift of the NecroDancer, available to wishlist now on Steam.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation 5 tournaments to get open beta]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/playstation-5-tournaments-to-get-open-beta</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/playstation-5-tournaments-to-get-open-beta"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T11:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tournaments - a feature of the PlayStation 4 since 2016 - will finally be available to try on PS5 soon via a public beta. 


Sony has announced an "all-new on-console tournament experience" coming to PS5 "in the coming weeks, in select countries" - and you can see some of its new look just above.


When implemented, the feature will allow you to join competitions for prizes and leaderboard bragging rights, with easy access from the PS5 Control Center and Game Hub.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation VR2 playable at Tokyo Game Show via Resident Evil Village]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/playstation-vr2-playable-at-tokyo-game-show-via-resident-evil-village</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/playstation-vr2-playable-at-tokyo-game-show-via-resident-evil-village"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T11:10:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capcom has announced that Resident Evil Village for PlayStation VR 2 will be playable at Tokyo Game Show this year - the first time Sony's new headset will be available to try publicly.

The VR mode for Village, available only on PS5, was first announced during Sony's State of Play showcase in June. 
Capcom had already announced it will be at Tokyo Game Show, but it's now revealed that a demo for Village on PlayStation VR 2 will be there next month.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liv Ngan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Sonic Frontiers players receive special V-Tuber DLC costumes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/japanese-sonic-frontiers-players-receive-special-v-tuber-dlc-costumes</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/japanese-sonic-frontiers-players-receive-special-v-tuber-dlc-costumes"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T11:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lucky Sonic Frontiers players in Japan will receive special V-Tuber DLC costumes.


Sega has revealed a collaboration with Hololive VTuber Inugami Korone, which changes Sonic's glove and shoe designs as well as the appearance of the in-game mascot Coco.


The DLC was posted on reddit, though it's unclear if this will also feature elsewhere.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former NASA official on trying to stop SLS: “There was just such visible hostility”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875388</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875388"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T11:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I still don't know to this day if my boss, Charlie, was in on the whole deal."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steam hosts Ukrainian Games Festival to mark country's independence day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/steam-hosts-ukrainian-games-festival-to-mark-countrys-independence-day</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/steam-hosts-ukrainian-games-festival-to-mark-countrys-independence-day"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T10:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ukrainian Games Festival is currently being hosted on Steam.


This festival is being presented by Indie Cup, with the support of the Ukrainian Indie Developers community. 


Here, you will find broadcasts for a variety of games made by Ukrainian developers, as well as deals on titles such as The Testament of Sherlock Holmes by Frogwares and Stalker: Shadow of Chernobyl by GSC Games World.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eFootball 2023 out today, with AC Milan and Inter in tow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/efootball-2023-out-today-with-ac-milan-and-inter-in-tow</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/efootball-2023-out-today-with-ac-milan-and-inter-in-tow"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T10:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Konami has released eFootball 2023 across PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, Xbox Series X and S, PC and mobile.


eFootball's second year kicks off as an update to the existing free-to-play game, with the summer's transfers reflected in team lineups.


eFootball 2023 sees the return of officially-licensed Italian clubs AC Milan and Inter, as well as the addition of Liga BBVA MX, which brings all 18 Mexican clubs, their players and the Estadio Azteca to the game.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like Square Enix is opening a new studio in the west]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/looks-like-square-enix-is-opening-a-new-studio-in-the-west</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/looks-like-square-enix-is-opening-a-new-studio-in-the-west"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T10:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Square Enix may be opening a new studio in the west, shortly after selling its previous western studios to Embracer.


Studio Onoma is part of an application on the Canadian Trademarks Database, with the applicant Square Enix Newco.


According to the application, Studio Onoma will both develop and publish video game software, in addition to working on merchandise like strategy guides, posters, clothing, toys, and action figures.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new Fear Effect is a third-person cover shooter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/the-new-fear-effect-is-a-third-person-cover-shooter</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/the-new-fear-effect-is-a-third-person-cover-shooter"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T10:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fear Effect Reinvented just re-emerged with its first gameplay trailer - and the promise of a release date sooner than we think.


The video below shows off how different this new Fear Effect looks and plays compared to the originals. 

Square Enix announced Fear Effect Reinvented back in 2017 with a release window of 2018. Obviously that sailed by.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Souls 3 servers are finally back online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/dark-souls-3-servers-are-finally-back-online</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/dark-souls-3-servers-are-finally-back-online"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T10:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FromSoftware has finally managed to get Dark Souls 3 back online, seven months after PC PvP servers had to be shut down.
Back in January, PC servers for all Dark Souls games were shuttered due to security issues - and remained down for months. In July, at the 183 day mark, there were signs that Dark Souls 3 could be back online soon - but still no fix.
Now, at well over 200 days, the PC servers for Dark Souls 3 are now live again. Rejoice!
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liv Ngan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation 5 price increase announced, by £30 in UK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/playstation-5-price-increase-announced-by-30-in-uk</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/playstation-5-price-increase-announced-by-30-in-uk"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T08:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony has increased the PlayStation 5 price, effective immediately, in most markets around the world. 


The console's cost will rise by £30 in the UK and €50 in Europe, to £480/€550, or £390/€450 for the console's disc-less digital version.


Elsewhere around the world, Japan, China, Australia, Mexico and Canada will also see price rises. But the US will not see a price rise at this time.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.25: Pod Security Admission Controller in Stable]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/25/pod-security-admission-stable/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/25/pod-security-admission-stable/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Tim Allclair (Google), Sam Stoelinga (Google)
The release of Kubernetes v1.25 marks a major milestone for Kubernetes out-of-the-box pod security
controls: Pod Security admission (PSA) graduated to stable, and Pod Security Policy (PSP) has been
removed.
PSP was deprecated in Kubernetes v1.21,
and no longer functions in Kubernetes v1.25 and later.
The Pod Security admission controller replaces PodSecurityPolicy, making it easier to enforce predefined
Pod Security Standards by
simply adding a label to a namespace. The Pod Security Standards are maintained by the K8s
community, which means you automatically get updated security policies whenever new
security-impacting Kubernetes features are introduced.
What’s new since Beta?
Pod Security Admission hasn’t changed much since the Beta i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Oz emailed Trump admin. to push notoriously useless COVID treatment]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875999</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875999"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T23:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The celebrity doctor played an early role in the push for an ineffective drug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Spanish Stonehenge” emerges from watery grave for second time in last 3 years]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875286</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875286"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T22:36:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dolmen of Guadalperal dates back to between 2000 and 3000 BCE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's ten minutes of new Forspoken gameplay footage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/heres-ten-minutes-of-new-forspoken-gameplay-footage</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/heres-ten-minutes-of-new-forspoken-gameplay-footage"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T22:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a not exactly inspiring showing earlier this month, Square Enix has once again reached deep into its Forspokeon promotional sack, this time pulling out a ten-minute trailer showcasing new gameplay from its upcoming open-world fantasy adventure.


Forspoken casts players in the role of Frey Holland - played by Ella Balinska - an "ordinary young woman who must harness her magical abilities to survive" in a "beautiful yet cruel" world of Athia. We get a much better closer at that world in Square's latest trailer, which includes a glimpse of the city of Cipal, Athia's only safe haven, where refugees gather to escape the corrupting force of the Break. 


Here, players can speak to citizens to take on quests and trade before heading out to explore Athia's more dangerous regions, including Praenost - a barren desert where the only signs of life are corrupted enemies - and the lush region of Avoalet with its dangerously mutated beasts.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supermassive's Dark Pictures Anthology: The Devil in Me gets November release date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/supermassives-dark-pictures-anthology-the-devil-in-me-gets-november-release-date</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/supermassives-dark-pictures-anthology-the-devil-in-me-gets-november-release-date"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T20:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supermassive Games has announced a release date for its latest Dark Pictures Anthology entry The Devil in Me, which is coming to Xbox, PlayStation, and PC on 18th November.


The Devil in Me will be the fourth instalment in Supermassive's Dark Pictures series - following on from Man of Medan, Little Hope, and House of Ashes - and tells the story of a group of film makers trapped in a replica of H. H. Holmes' infamous 'Murder Castle' hotel.


Based on everything shown so far, The Devil in Me looks to be something of a departure from previous anthology entries, trading their supernatural overtones for a more grounded, grisly horror inspired by the likes of the Saw and Hostel movies.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neill Blomkamp's battle royale Off the Grid is an NFT game, unfortunately]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/neil-blomkamps-battle-royale-off-the-grid-is-an-nft-game</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/neil-blomkamps-battle-royale-off-the-grid-is-an-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T20:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[District 9 director Neill Blomkamp is making a video game! I knew that. But what I didn't know is it's one of those blockchain / NFT games.

Sigh.

This evening's The Future Games Show ended with a fancy CGI trailer showing off the world of Off the Grid, a free-to-play third-person shooter battle royale from new developer Gunzilla Games.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s best deals: HyperX Cloud Alpha Wireless, Google Chromecast, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875452</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875452"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T20:27:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealmaster also has the Pixel 6a, Xbox gift cards, and Samsung microSD cards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Dunn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Layers of Fears remake shows off "new story chapter" in latest trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/bloober-team-shows-off-layers-of-fears-remakes-new-story-chapter-in-latest-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/bloober-team-shows-off-layers-of-fears-remakes-new-story-chapter-in-latest-trailer"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T19:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in June, Bloober Team - the developer behind The Medium, Observer, and Blair Witch - announced it was remaking Layers of Fear 1 & 2 as a single "psychedelic horror chronicle", and now the studio has shared a first look at a "brand-new story chapter" in its latest trailer.


Layers of Fears, as the remake is officially (and ridiculously) known, is being co-developed with Anshar Studios, and will see the original Layers of Fear, its Inheritance DLC, and Layers of Fear 2 rebuilt in Unreal Engine 5, complete with new visuals, gameplay, and expanded plot lines said to "cast a new light on the overarching narrative" as players face "spine-chilling madness that extends over generations."


The first Layers of Fear game, if you're unfamiliar, charted the story of a painter on the verge of completing his masterpiece while Layers of Fear 2 told the tale of an actor making a movie onboard a labyrinthine ocean liner, with both games serving up some striking psychedelic imagery as each protagonist began to lose their grip on reality.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great War: Western Front is a new WW1 strategy game from the developer of Command & Conquer Remastered]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/the-great-war-western-front-is-a-new-ww1-strategy-game-from-the-developer-of-command-conquer-remastered</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/the-great-war-western-front-is-a-new-ww1-strategy-game-from-the-developer-of-command-conquer-remastered"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T19:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Petroglyph, the developer behind the excellent Command & Conquer Remastered, has announced a World War 1 strategy game due out next year.


The Great War: Western Front, set for launch on PC at some point in 2023, lets you play as both Theatre Commander and Field Commander in a dual-role.


Theatre Commander presents turn-based grand-strategy gameplay as you direct the deployment of forces, perform research and manage your resources across the Western Front.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cheap, high capacity, and fast: New aluminum battery tech promises it all]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875891</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875891"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T19:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The big catch is that it has to be at roughly the boiling point of water to work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use déjà vu to bridge realities in hard sci-fi psychological thriller The Gap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/use-deja-vu-to-bridge-realities-in-hard-sci-fi-psychological-thriller-the-gap</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/use-deja-vu-to-bridge-realities-in-hard-sci-fi-psychological-thriller-the-gap"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An intriguing-sounding psychological thriller called The Gap was announced during the Future Games Show this evening.
It's described as a hard sci-fi first-person narrative game set in 2045, not that the sci-fi elements are particularly apparent from the debut trailer. This shows you, a neuroscientist called Joshua Hayes, waking up on the floor of presumably your own apartment, with a voice - and written messages on the walls - telling you not to trust anyone. But you can't remember what is going on.
Hayes suffers from a rare genetic disorder that affects his memory, so the focus in the game is trying to recover those memories by re-experiencing them. The catalyst for this is déjà vu, triggered by objects that act like a bridge to a parallel reality to experience memories again. But there's tragedy hiding in your past, too.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Purchese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plex imposes password reset after hackers steal data for >15 million users]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875864</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875864"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T17:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intruders access personal information for the majority of its 30 million users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Far out”: Apple confirms iPhone-focused launch event on September 7]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875846</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875846"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T16:52:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New iPhones and Apple Watches reportedly on tap, while iPads and Macs will wait.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comedian George Lopez sues Pandora for $5.5M for “brazen” copyright infringement]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875815</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875815"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T16:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A federal court will begin reviewing the case by the end of this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Belanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everywhere developer responds to "NFT/Crypto" speculation, following vague game reveal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/everywhere-developer-defends-nftcrypto-job-postings-after-vague-game-reveal</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/everywhere-developer-defends-nftcrypto-job-postings-after-vague-game-reveal"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T16:15:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developer of Everywhere, the new project from former Grand Theft Auto producer Leslie Benzies, has issued a statement in response to reports highlighting the fact it is currently hiring for multiple positions related to the blockchain.


Build A Rocket Boy, which is based in Edinburgh, currently lists three positions based on blockchain development on its website, including a senior backend programmer, smart contract developer and test engineer.


Is Everywhere a blockchain game? Does it include NFTs? What, actually, is Everywhere? These questions were all floating around the internet this morning, after a particularly vague reveal for the game last night during Gamescom's Opening Night Live ceremony, where we saw a trailer for the title that gave little away. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel sees huge sales growth, has 2% of North American market]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875791</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875791"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T16:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's hardware division is still shockingly small, but it's making progress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pentiment preview: Obsidian’s historical, religiously charged murder mystery]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875731</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1875731"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lead dev on Obsidian's first game since Microsoft acquisition: "We can do this now."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamescom Opening Night Live special]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/eurogamer-newscast-gamescom-opening-night-live-special</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/eurogamer-newscast-gamescom-opening-night-live-special"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T15:46:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week on the Eurogamer Newscast, we're picking out our favourite bits - and not so favourites - from this week's big Gamescom Opening Night Live showcase. 

It's a relatively quiet year for Gamescom - though it is lovely to see the show back on its feet and filled with sweaty attendees - and it's fair to say this was reflected in last night's showings. We got a big reveal for Dead Island 2 - which is not set on an island - and a release date for Return to Monkey Island, but otherwise, surprises were thin on the ground, and there were a lot of CGI trailers.


Those aside, and ignoring Kojima shilling his podcast, we still got an array of interesting games to look forward to over the next 12 months, even if not all of them were AAA-sized or from franchises you might have heard of. I particularly liked the look of Moonbreaker, Atlus Fallen and Where Winds Meet, games I'd never heard of before last night. But what did everyone else think? Tom Phillips, Ed Nightingale, Victoria Kennedy and Liv Ngan discuss.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox's Phil Spencer wants to see fewer platform exclusives, more cross-play in future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/xboxs-phil-spencer-wants-to-see-fewer-platform-exclusives-more-cross-play-in-future</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/xboxs-phil-spencer-wants-to-see-fewer-platform-exclusives-more-cross-play-in-future"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T15:27:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox boss Phil Spencer has said he'd like to see more game releases that are not tied down to one specific platform, which will in turn allow for more cross-play opportunities.


Chatting to Bloomberg, Spencer stated that platform exclusives are something we were all going to see "less and less of" in future, as he hopes for an industry that encourages people to feel safe and included "regardless of what device" they play on.


Spencer said he also wanted to see more cross-play possibilties on the market. "Maybe you happen in your household to buy an Xbox and I buy a PlayStation and our kids want to play together and they can't because we bought the wrong piece of plastic to plug into our television," he explained. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Denuvo may start appearing in Switch games]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/denuvo-may-start-appearing-in-switch-games</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/denuvo-may-start-appearing-in-switch-games"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T15:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company behind controversial anti-piracy software Denuvo has announced an "innovative solution" to the piracy of Nintendo Switch games on PC.
Irdeto today published a press release about its Nintendo Switch Emulator Protection solution, as a call to developers and publishers who may be interested in including it with their games. In its statement, Irdeto targets not only first-party and second-party Switch games, but ports of PC games too.

"Nintendo consoles have long suffered from piracy issues and the Switch is no different," the company wrote. "Even if a game is protected against piracy on its PC version, the released version on Switch can be emulated from day one and played on PC, therefore bypassing the strong protections offered on the PC version."
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liv Ngan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary F1 car added to Gran Turismo 7 in August update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/legendary-f1-car-added-to-gran-turismo-7-in-august-update</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/legendary-f1-car-added-to-gran-turismo-7-in-august-update"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T14:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The August update for Gran Turismo 7 is now available, adding a legendary F1 car.


The McLaren MP4/4 marked the end of the Turbo era and was driven by Ayrton Senna in 1988 to win the drivers' championship. It's now available to drive in-game.


Three other cars have also been included: the Pontiac GTO 'The Judge' '69, the Porsche Cayman GT4 '16, and the De Tomaso Mangusta (Christian Dior).
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bungie to end controversial deletions of older Destiny 2 expansions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/bungie-to-end-controversial-deletions-of-older-destiny-2-expansions</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/bungie-to-end-controversial-deletions-of-older-destiny-2-expansions"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T14:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bungie has announced it will ditch its practice of ritually shedding past Destiny 2 expansions.


No content will be lost from expansions from this point forward, Bungie pledged last night during its packed Destiny 2 announcement livestream.


However, the game's fabled Content Vault will still continue to gobble up some stuff, including season content beyond its expansion's launch year.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Is Responsible for My Surprise Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=12940</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/sagemaker_is_responsible_for_my_surprise_bill/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting an AWS surprise bill for Amazon SageMaker Canvas is a strange and concerning occurrence for The Duckbill Group's Chief Cloud Economist.
The post Amazon SageMaker Is Responsible for My Surprise Bill appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Techland highlights changes coming to Dying Light 2 Stay Human]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/techland-highlights-changes-coming-to-dying-light-2-stay-human</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/techland-highlights-changes-coming-to-dying-light-2-stay-human"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T13:48:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In its first Community Update, Techland has revealed changes coming to Dying Light 2 Stay Human.


So far the improvements are mainly visual. A new Colour Grading option has been added that allows players to change to a "gritty" look similar to the 2019 gameplay presentations.


Other visual improvements include new screen space ambient occlusion implementation, image clarity improvements including temporal anti-aliasing and texture filtering, and the ability to toggle Chromatic Aberration.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here are more games confirmed for Xbox Game Pass]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/here-are-more-games-confirmed-for-xbox-game-pass</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/here-are-more-games-confirmed-for-xbox-game-pass"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T11:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At last night's Gamescom Opening Night Live, a number of games were confirmed as coming to Xbox and PC Game Pass.


As already announced, Tinykin, Midnight Fight Express, Immortals Fenyx Rising and Immortality are on their way to the service this month.



But more games are coming as shown in the below montage, many of which are day one releases.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Talk developer delays next game, alleges publisher PQube misused funds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/coffee-talk-developer-delays-next-game-alleges-publisher-pqube-misused-funds</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/coffee-talk-developer-delays-next-game-alleges-publisher-pqube-misused-funds"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T11:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toge Productions, the Indonesian indie developer behind Coffee Talk, has today issued a damning statement announcing a delay to its next project due to issues with publisher PQube.


The lengthy public announcement, made this morning via Twitter, accuses PQube of misusing money gained from a diversity fund. Toge Productions claims it should have received this money - part of a scheme from a "well known console platform" - to help finance its upcoming project A Space For The Unbound.


"The diversity fund was a grant fund intended to help underrepresented game developers, especially during the pandemic," Toge Productions wrote. "However, instead of giving those funds to the developers as the grant was intended, PQube Games intentionally withheld information about the grant and used it as a leverage for their own commercial gain. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dead Island 2's zombie hordes can be distracted by your voice thanks to Amazon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/dead-island-2s-zombie-hordes-can-be-distracted-by-your-voice-thanks-to-amazon</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/dead-island-2s-zombie-hordes-can-be-distracted-by-your-voice-thanks-to-amazon"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T11:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A swanky new gaming feature announced by Amazon at Gamescom will let you interact with Dead Island 2 using your voice. This feature is known as Alexa Game Control, and it pretty much does what it says on the tin. 


With Alexa Game Control in use, players will be able to control aspects of their game via Amazon's voice activated software. Amazon states that the feature will work with "any microphone or headset connected to their PC or console," and therefore "players do not need an Echo device to play games with their voice". You will, however, need an Amazon account (but not necessarily a Prime one).


Along with this announcement, Amazon also revealed how this new feature will be implemented in Dambuster Studios' upcoming zombie slasher, Dead Island 2. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mudge Files Whistleblower Complaint against Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/mudge-files-whistleblower-complaint-against-twitter.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/mudge-files-whistleblower-complaint-against-twitter.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T11:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Peiter Zatko, aka Mudge, has filed a whistleblower complaint with the SEC against Twitter, claiming that they violated an eleven-year-old FTC settlement by having lousy security. And he should know; he was Twitter&#8217;s chief security officer until he was fired in January.</p>
<p>The <i>Washington Post</i> has the <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/interactive/2022/twitter-whistleblower-sec-spam/">scoop</a> (with documents) and companion <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2022/08/23/peiter-mudge-zatko-twitter-whistleblower/">backgrounder</a>. This <a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2022/08/23/tech/twitter-whistleblower-peiter-zatko-security/index.html">CNN story</a> is also comprehensive.</p>
<p>EDITED TO ADD: Another <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/08/23/technology/twitter-whistleblower-security.html">news article</a>. Slashdot <a href="https://slashdot.org/story/22/08/23/205224/ex-twitter-exec-blows-the-whistle-alleging-reckless-and-negligent-cybersecurity-policies">thread</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamescom 2023 has already been announced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/gamescom-2023-has-already-been-announced</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/gamescom-2023-has-already-been-announced"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T11:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gamescom 2022 Opening Night Live only happened last night, but Geoff Keighley has already announced when Gamescom 2023 is set to take place.
This morning, Keighley took to Twitter to post the announcement.
"Give me a minute but Gamescom 2023 dates have been announced - including Opening Night Live," he tweeted, alongside a picture of a banner from the show floor with the dates for next year printed on.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liv Ngan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Cup runners-up Croatia finally in FIFA 23 after 10-year absence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/world-cup-runners-up-croatia-finally-in-fifa-23-after-10-year-absence</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/world-cup-runners-up-croatia-finally-in-fifa-23-after-10-year-absence"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T10:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World Cup runners-up Croatia are in FIFA 23 after a decade-long absence from the series.


The Croatian football association confirmed the national team will appear in FIFA 23 in a tweet.


EA also confirmed the news in a tweet.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Under the Waves is an underwater story about grief and ocean preservation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/under-the-waves-is-an-underwater-story-about-grief-and-ocean-preservation</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/under-the-waves-is-an-underwater-story-about-grief-and-ocean-preservation"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T10:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Submerged story-led game Under the Waves stood out last night during Gamescom's Opening Night Live, where a first trailer for the project was shown. 


Set beneath the North Sea in an alternate 1970s world, the project will channel the personal losses of its dozen developers at indie outfit Parallel Studio. 


Under the Waves' development is being assisted by Quantic Dream, the studio famous for various lawsuits, and also Heavy Rain, Beyond: Two Souls and Detroit: Becom Human. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Masahiro Sakurai launches new YouTube channel on game development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/masahiro-sakurai-launches-new-youtube-channel-on-game-development</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/masahiro-sakurai-launches-new-youtube-channel-on-game-development"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T10:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smash Bros creator Masahiro Sakurai has started a new YouTube channel on game development.


Yesterday he posted his final screenshot from Super Smash Bros Ultimate, hinting that something new was on the way.


Launching today is Masahiro Sakurai on Creating Games, with a new video available now.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pentiment secures November release date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/pentiment-secures-november-release-date</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/pentiment-secures-november-release-date"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T09:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Obsidian Entertainment has announced that Pentiment, its narrative adventure RPG that takes place in 16th century Bavaria, will be coming to PC and Xbox on 15th November.


As is to be expected, Pentiment will be available on PC Game Pass and Xbox Game Pass upon its release. For those not subscibed to these services, it is currently listed for £14.99 on Steam.


Throughout Pentiment, players will take on the mantle of Andreas Maler, "a very clever journeyman artist who gets caught up in a series of murders and scandals that spans 25 years in the fictional town of Tassing and Kiersau Abbey".
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tetherball Configurations]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2663/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2663/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/tetherball_configurations.png" title="Ground-pole-ball-pole can be fun if you shake the first pole to get the second one whipping around dangerously, but the ball at the joint gets torn apart pretty fast." alt="Ground-pole-ball-pole can be fun if you shake the first pole to get the second one whipping around dangerously, but the ball at the joint gets torn apart pretty fast." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: PodSecurityPolicy: The Historical Context]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/podsecuritypolicy-the-historical-context/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/podsecuritypolicy-the-historical-context/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mahé Tardy (Quarkslab)
The PodSecurityPolicy (PSP) admission controller has been removed, as of
Kubernetes v1.25. Its deprecation was announced and detailed in the blog post
PodSecurityPolicy Deprecation: Past, Present, and Future,
published for the Kubernetes v1.21 release.
This article aims to provide historical context on the birth and evolution of
PSP, explain why the feature never made it to stable, and show why it was
removed and replaced by Pod Security admission control.
PodSecurityPolicy, like other specialized admission control plugins, provided
fine-grained permissions on specific fields concerning the pod security settings
as a built-in policy API. It acknowledged that cluster administrators and
cluster users are usually not the same people, and that creating workloads …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Subnautica dev unveils "analogue" turn-based tactics game Moonbreaker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/subnautica-dev-unveils-analogue-turn-based-tactics-game-moonbreaker</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/subnautica-dev-unveils-analogue-turn-based-tactics-game-moonbreaker"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T21:10:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two games of terrifying deep sea survival, Subnautica developer Unknown Worlds is heading in a very different direction for its next project - a tabletop-inspired turn-based tactics game going by the name Moonbreaker, entering Steam early access on 29th September.


On a fundamental level, Moonbreaker, which has been in development for around five years, is surprisingly straightforward; each game sees players - either working against a human or AI opponent - strategising their way around a board, using careful positioning to their advantage as they work to annihilate the opposing player's Captain.


So far so straightforward, but the complexity arrives when you begin factoring in the tactical options available to players during a match, including the likes of cover - which can either impenetrable or penetrable with an accuracy cost - plus Captains, crew members, ship assists, and resource management.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Surge developer unveils Atlas Fallen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/the-surge-developer-unveils-atlas-fallen</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/the-surge-developer-unveils-atlas-fallen"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T20:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Atlas Fallen is a new fantasy action RPG from The Surge developer Deck 13, set for release on PC, PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S in 2023.


We got a first look at Atlas Fallen tonight during Gamescom Opening Night Live, via a flashy CGI trailer which shows off its sand-covered semi-open world and superpowered beasties.


Stick with the trailer - not that it isn't easy on the eyes - and there's a glimpse of what looks like actual gameplay right at the end. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hideo Kojima launching new Spotify podcast Brain Structure next month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/hideo-kojima-launching-new-spotify-podcast-brain-structure-next-month</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/hideo-kojima-launching-new-spotify-podcast-brain-structure-next-month"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T20:13:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hideo Kojima - the man behind the likes of Death Stranding, Metal Gear Solid, and PT - has once again popped up at the German Geoffs (AKA Gamescom Opening Night Live) for a bit of the old self-promotion, this time to announce a new podcast series known as Brain Structure.


Brain Structure, which will launch as a Spotify exclusive starting in September, appears to be seperate from Kojima's Japan-only Radioverse podcast, which began in February and promised to bring listeners a variety of guests discussing "deep topics related to games and movies that cannot be heard anywhere else".


This new Spotify podcast seems broadly similar in nature though, featuring appearances from "very special guests from various fields", including, perhaps inevitably, Geoff Keighely, who'll have his own regular entertainment news section.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Medieval China-set action RPG Where Winds Meet announced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/medieval-china-set-action-rpg-where-winds-meet-announced</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/medieval-china-set-action-rpg-where-winds-meet-announced"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T20:06:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brand new game Where Winds Meet was announced at Gamescom Opening Night Live.


The game is from developer Everstone Games and is an open world action RPG set in the Ten Kingdoms period of medieval China.


The game was revealed with a stunning looking trailer that showed off its lush setting of bamboo forests, snow covered mountains, and other surreal areas.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peaceful puzzler Dorfromantik coming to Switch in September]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/peaceful-puzzler-dorfromantik-coming-to-switch-in-september</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/peaceful-puzzler-dorfromantik-coming-to-switch-in-september"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T19:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dorfromantik, the peaceful puzzle game from German developer Toukana Interactive, is coming to Nintendo Switch next month.


The game has already proven popular on Steam and will hit Nintendo's console on 29th September.


To celebrate the launch, a new cherry blossom themed biome with unique architecture and scenery will be added.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gotham Knights release date shifts forwards slightly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/gotham-knights-release-date-shifts-forwards-slightly</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/gotham-knights-release-date-shifts-forwards-slightly"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T19:46:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Batman spin-off Gotham Knights got a fresh showing at Gamescom Opening Night Live this evening, with a new trailer and a new release date. 


Flashy footage from the game gave us our first proper look at Harley Quinn, who looks to be a major antagonist for Gotham Knights' four heroes, alongside Mr Freeze, Clayface and the Court of Owls. 


The trailer concluded with the reveal of a new launch date: 21st October, four days earlier than previously planned. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a look at The Expanse: A Telltale Series, 2023 release window confirmed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/heres-a-look-at-telltales-the-expanse-a-telltale-series-2023-release-window-confirmed</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/heres-a-look-at-telltales-the-expanse-a-telltale-series-2023-release-window-confirmed"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T19:41:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Gamescom Opening Night Live, we were treated to a closer look at The Expanse: A Telltale Series. 


Along with this new teaser, which also comes with some behind the scenes chat with actress Cara Gee and the game's development team and can be seen below, we now also have a release window - summer 2023.

The developers have said that this new game will be unlike any previous Telltale titles, thanks to the introduction of "several new gameplay elements". 
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Talking to the former Fallout 76 lead about their new studio and occult RPG Wyrdsong]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/talking-to-the-former-fallout-76-lead-about-their-new-studio-and-occult-rpg-wyrdsong</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/talking-to-the-former-fallout-76-lead-about-their-new-studio-and-occult-rpg-wyrdsong"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T19:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeff Gardiner, a Bethesda veteran of 15 years and most recently the project lead on Fallout 76, has announced a new studio and open-world occult RPG with it.
The studio is Something Wicked Games and the project is Wyrdsong, pronounced "weirdsong", or at least that's how Gardiner pronounced it on a phone call to me. It's going to be set in Portugal around the forming of the Knights Templar.
Something Wicked was co-founded with Obsidian veteran Charles Staples in April this year, who led design on Outer Worlds. And the studio is funded by NetEase courtesy of a $13.2m "seed" investment, which means it's not all the money Something Wicked will need but a wadge to get going with.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Purchese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sonic Frontiers confirmed for a November release in new story trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/sonic-frontiers-confirmed-for-a-november-release-in-new-story-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/sonic-frontiers-confirmed-for-a-november-release-in-new-story-trailer"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T18:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sonic Frontiers will be released across all platforms on 8th November this year.


A new story trailer for the game was shown at the Gamescom Opening Night Live, despite the release date leaking before the show.



And that trailer has it all: giant robots, cute companion robots, creepy young child robots, and the return of Amy Rose who appears to have been kidnapped. Check it out below.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Funcom's open-world survival MMO Dune: Awakening gets first trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/funcoms-open-world-survival-mmo-dune-awakening-gets-first-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/funcoms-open-world-survival-mmo-dune-awakening-gets-first-trailer"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T18:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Funcom has released a first cinematic trailer for Dune: Awakening, a new "open-world survival MMO" inspired by Frank Herbert's novels and Denis Villeneuve's Academy Award-winning film, that's heading to PS5, Xbox Series X/S, and PC.


Dune: Awakening was first teased back in 2019, when Funcom announced it had signed a deal with Legendary Studios to make "at least" three games set in Frank Herbert's Dune universe. One of those eventually turned out to be Dune: Spice Wars and the other, described as an "open-world multiplayer game" from Funcom Oslo, we can now call Dune: Awakening.


Today's announcement doesn't bring any gameplay, but Funcom says it'll combine the "grittiness and creativity of survival games with the social interactivity of large-scale, persistent multiplayer games" in a "vast and seamless Arrakis shared by thousands of players".
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Return to Monkey Island gets September release date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/return-to-monkey-island-gets-september-release-date</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/return-to-monkey-island-gets-september-release-date"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T18:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Gamescom Opening Night Live, it was revealed that Return to Monkey Island will be coming to Nintendo Switch and PC on 19th September. That's 'Talk like a pirate day', me hearties. 
You can preorder the game now (it is listed for £19.49 on Steam) and in doing so get yourself some new horse armour for your piratical inventory.
Along with this news, delivered by Stan, of course, there was also tropical music a plenty, colourful set pieces, and a good dose of banter. You can see what you think for yourself below. 
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here is some more gore from The Callisto Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/here-is-some-more-gore-from-the-callisto-protocol</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/here-is-some-more-gore-from-the-callisto-protocol"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T18:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of its release this December, we have been given another, gory, teaser for The Callisto Protocol. 


Debuted at Gamescom Opening Night Live, this new footage is as bloody and unpleasant as you would expect. There are mutations getting shoved into rotors, there is blood splattering the surfaces left, right and centre, and there are those kinds of noises that you do not want to ever hear when you are home alone at night (or any time for that matter). 


As well as the standard shooting and squelching, we also get to see some Tomb Raider-esque slipping and sliding down a water way. Of course, there are things to avoid, so this can only end well... See what you think to it all for yourself below.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Tales from the Borderlands coming this October]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/new-tales-from-the-borderlands-coming-this-october</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/new-tales-from-the-borderlands-coming-this-october"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T18:27:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following on from a leak earlier this month, Gearbox has officially unveiled its upcoming game, New Tales from the Borderlands. As we sort of already knew, it is coming on 21st October across Xbox Series X/S, Xbox One, PlayStation 5, PS4, Nintendo Switch and PC (via Steam and Epic).


This standalone, choice based, narrative is set in the "perpetually war-torn Promethea" and will see players deciding the fates of "three underdogs out to make mayhem in their business". And what of these underdogs? Well, they are altruistic scientist Anu (pictured above), her ambitious "streetwise" brother Octavio, and the fierce, frogurt-flinging Fran.


You can see the trailer, which was shown during Gamescom Opening Night Live, for New Tales from the Borderlands below.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation announces DualSense Edge controller with removable thumbsticks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/playstation-announces-dualsense-edge-controller-with-removable-thumbsticks</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/playstation-announces-dualsense-edge-controller-with-removable-thumbsticks"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T18:23:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony has confirmed its previously-rumoured "pro" controller, officially named the DualSense Edge Wireless Controller. 


A brief teaser for the pad appeared tonight during Gamescom Opening Night Live, and showcased its removable analogue stick units and rear buttons. 


No release information or pricing details were announced today.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lords of the Fallen reboot announced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/the-lords-of-the-fallen-reboot-announced</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/the-lords-of-the-fallen-reboot-announced"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T18:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A spiritual successor to Lords of the Fallen was announced at tonight's Opening Night Live at Gamescom with a new cinematic trailer.


Now with a The at the start, The Lords of the Fallen will continue the dark fantasy Soulslike RPG legacy of the original 2014 game, taking place a thousand years later.


Most notably, the game will have a two-player uninterrupted online co-op option.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-GTA producer reveals new game Everywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/ex-gta-producer-reveals-new-game-everywhere</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/ex-gta-producer-reveals-new-game-everywhere"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T18:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish developer Build A Rocket Boy has announced its new game Everywhere at Gamescom's Opening Night Live.


The studio was set up by former Grand Theft Auto producer Leslie Benzies, with other industry veterans recently joining.



Everywhere "seamlessly blends gameplay, adventure, creativity, and discovery in an all-new multiworld gaming experience that redefines how players connect with one another and the digital world around them," reads a press release.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Destiny 2's Neptune-set Lightfall expansion launches February 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/destiny-2s-neptune-set-lightfall-expansion-launches-in-february-next-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/destiny-2s-neptune-set-lightfall-expansion-launches-in-february-next-year"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T17:37:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bungie has given Destiny 2's long-awaited Lightfall expansion its first proper reveal, sharing a huge heap of gameplay details - from its Neptune setting to its new grapple-hook-like Strand ability - ahead of its now-confirmed launch date of 28th February next year.


Lightfall, which was initially announced back in June 2020, will be Destiny 2's penultimate expansion, coming between this year's The Witch Queen and the game's finale expansion The Final Shape. As such, Bungie is calling it the "beginning of the end", and it continues an escalating narrative that will bring Destiny's Light and Darkness Saga to a close.


It finally gives a name and a face to Destiny 2's much-teased big bad, The Witness, and will take players to Neptune's capital city. This gleaming metropolis is, thanks to Calus' Shadow Legion, now Cabal-occupied territory, and players will need to deal with their new Pyramid-enhanced tech - including suppression devices, which can diminish Guardians' abilities - plus a new Pyramid unit known as the Tormentor.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox Gamescom booth lists bizarre Pinocchio game Lies of P for Game Pass]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/xbox-gamescom-booth-lists-bizarre-pinocchio-game-lies-of-p-for-game-pass</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/xbox-gamescom-booth-lists-bizarre-pinocchio-game-lies-of-p-for-game-pass"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T15:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE 8pm UK: Tonight's Opening Night Live showcase has confirmed Lies of P will launch directly into Xbox Game Pass when it arrives at some point in 2023.
Here's a fresh trailer:
ORIGINAL STORY 4pm UK:
Microsoft's Gamescom booth has demo stations for several upcoming titles apparently coming to Game Pass, as detailed in photos posted to Twitter by Xbox exec Aaron Greenberg. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There's a new Sackboy game in the works]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/theres-a-new-sackboy-game-in-the-works</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/theres-a-new-sackboy-game-in-the-works"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T14:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ultimate Sackboy is a new LittleBigPlanet spin-off, and it's headed to your mobile phone. 


An endless runner, the game looks to be a follow-up to Run Sackboy Run! - the PlayStation Vita and mobile game launched back in 2015.


While still formally unannounced by Sony, a Google Play listing for Ultimate Sackboy on Android is already visible - though curiously this dates back to June.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Battlefield 2042 overhauls Specialists with new class-like system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/battlefield-2042-overhauls-specialists-with-new-class-like-system</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/battlefield-2042-overhauls-specialists-with-new-class-like-system"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T14:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DICE has announced a series of revamps coming to the beleaguered Battlefield 2042, including a rework of the game's unpopular Specialists.


In a lengthy blog post, DICE has detailed how it will bring "classes back to Battlefield" by reintroducing the "classic and familiar" Assault, Recon, Support and Engineer as groups in which existing Specialists will sit as "unique sub-classes".


Each of these classes will be tweaked to restrict gadget usage, enabling players to "better assess the threat", and assign new class traits. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch allows Partners to stream on rival platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/twitch-allows-partners-to-stream-on-rival-platforms</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/twitch-allows-partners-to-stream-on-rival-platforms"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T13:46:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch has updated its Partner Exclusivity policy, meaning streamers can now livestream on multiple platforms - just not simultaneously.


Previously, streamers who reach Partner status on the platform were tied to only livestreaming on Twitch.


Now Twitch Partners are also able to stream on rival platforms like YouTube and Facebook too, although simulcasting is not allowed there.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo livestream to reveal Splatoon 3, Harvestella gameplay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/nintendo-livestream-to-reveal-splatoon-3-harvestella-gameplay</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/nintendo-livestream-to-reveal-splatoon-3-harvestella-gameplay"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T13:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo has announced a last-minute livestream to take place this Thursday, 25th August, featuring fresh Splatoon 3 gameplay and a look at Harvestella. 


Tune in at 5.30pm UK time for a "deep dive" into Splatoon 3's single-player mode plus more details and strategies for this weekend's upcoming Splatfest World Premiere demo. 


Following that, we'll see "world-first gameplay" for Harvestella, the farming role-playing game being made by Final Fantasy maker Square Enix.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Tomb Raider Anniversary mod adds Angel of Darkness assets to the game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/new-tomb-raider-anniversary-mod-adds-angel-of-darkness-assets-to-the-game</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/new-tomb-raider-anniversary-mod-adds-angel-of-darkness-assets-to-the-game"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T13:19:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new mod for Tomb Raider Anniversary adds a variety of assets from Angel of Darkness to its successor.


The mod in question comes from Raq on Nexxus Mods. Raq has made it so a multitude of items in Anniversary now get an Angel of Darkness makeover. This includes everything from characters to weapons. 


With this mod in play, you can replace the athletic Lara Croft with Margot Carvier, Angel of Darkness' demure academic from the Louvre's Department of Medieval and Renaissance Studies.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The full lineup for Git Merge 2022 revealed]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/?p=66571</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-23-the-full-lineup-for-git-merge-2022-revealed/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T13:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the full lineup of talks and workshops for this year’s Git Merge conference in Chicago. 17 talks, 3 workshops, 1 panel, and some great company!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Reilly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yakuza creator quit Sega because he didn't "want to become CEO"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/yakuza-creator-quit-sega-because-he-didnt-want-to-become-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/yakuza-creator-quit-sega-because-he-didnt-want-to-become-ceo"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T11:57:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toshihiro Nagoshi has discussed the new project he's working on and the reason for his departure from Sega.
Nagoshi, known as the father of the Super Monkey Ball and Yakuza series, left Sega in 2021 after 32 years at the company to join Chinese technology company NetEase. He later announced Nagoshi Studio, a subsidiary under NetEase Games, which would allow him to "do something different".
In an interview with German gaming site 4Players, Nagoshi said it had not been creative differences that had led him to leave Sega, but that during his last few years at the company he was promoted to executive and management roles - something he wasn't interested in.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liv Ngan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mount and Blade 2: Bannerlord coming to PlayStation, Xbox this October]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord-coming-to-playstation-xbox-this-october</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/mount-and-blade-2-bannerlord-coming-to-playstation-xbox-this-october"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T11:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taleworlds Entertainment has revealed that Mount and Blade 2: Bannerlord - a swords and shields battler with no fantasy elements - will be coming to PlayStation 4, PS5, Xbox One and Xbox Series X/S on 25th October.


In addition to this, and following its stint in early access, the game will also get its full release on PC at the same time. 

To accompany this news, here is a new trailer for you to enjoy.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracer stock price falls following Saints Row reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/embracer-stock-price-falls-following-saints-row-reviews</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/embracer-stock-price-falls-following-saints-row-reviews"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T11:31:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disappointing Saints Row reviews have hit publisher Embracer's stock price.


Today's launch of the Saints Row reboot has been seen as the first big test for Embracer's AAA studio talent, following the company's enormous and still-ongoing spree of acquisitions over the past couple of years. 


But yesterday's Saints Row embargo lift was met with a lacklustre response from many outlets. Eurogamer's own review stated the game "won't set the world alight", but noted that it still holds some "pleasant surprises". 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Signal Phone Numbers Exposed in Twilio Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/signal-phone-numbers-exposed-in-twilio-hack.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/signal-phone-numbers-exposed-in-twilio-hack.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T11:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Twilio was hacked earlier this month, and the phone numbers of 1,900 Signal users <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/08/15/signal-phone-number-exposed-twilio/">were</a> <a href="https://support.signal.org/hc/en-us/articles/4850133017242">exposed</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>Here&#8217;s what our users need to know:</p>
<ul>
<li>All users can rest assured that their message history, contact lists, profile information, whom they&#8217;d blocked, and other personal data remain private and secure and were not affected.
<li>For about 1,900 users, an attacker could have attempted to re-register their number to another device or learned that their number was registered to Signal. This attack has since been shut down by Twilio. 1,900 users is a very small percentage of Signal&#8217;s total users, meaning that most were not affected...</li></li></ul></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elden Ring's voiceless Goldmask has a voice after all]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/elden-rings-voiceless-goldmask-has-a-voice-after-all</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/elden-rings-voiceless-goldmask-has-a-voice-after-all"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T10:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It turns out Elden Ring character Goldmask does in fact have a voice line after all.


The character is a mere husk of a man with a golden mask on his face. He's so enlightened he doesn't ever speak and instead just points towards the towering Erdtree with a "...".


Except, thanks to datamining, he does actually have a voice line hidden away in the Network Test version of the game.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20m brawlers have already battled it out in MultiVersus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/20m-brawlers-have-already-battled-it-out-in-multiversus</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/20m-brawlers-have-already-battled-it-out-in-multiversus"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T10:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New figures reveal that Warner Bros. has welcomed over 20 million brawlers to MultiVersus, doubling its numbers since the start of August.


In an interview with GamesBeat, Warner Bros. Interactive Entertainment's president David Haddad said:


"We had a fantastic first half of the year, really driven by the results of Lego Star Wars: The Skywalker Saga. And we're so excited to get off to such a great start in the second half with MultiVersus.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Masahiro Sakurai shares final Smash Bros Ultimate screenshot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/masahiro-sakurai-shares-final-smash-bros-ultimate-screenshot</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/masahiro-sakurai-shares-final-smash-bros-ultimate-screenshot"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T10:34:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Super Smash Bros Ultimate director Masahiro Sakurai has shared his final daily screenshot.


Since December 2019, Sakurai has been sharing screenshots from the debug version of the game each day.


Earlier this month he noted he'd soon be running out of screenshots. Now that day has come.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disgaea 7 announced for next year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/disgaea-7-announced-for-next-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/disgaea-7-announced-for-next-year"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T10:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disgaea 7 has just been announced by developer Nippon Ichi Software for Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4 and PS5.
First details of the game were published by the PlayStation Japan blog, which also shared a fresh announcement trailer, below.

The setting for Disgaea 7 is a world called the Hinomoto Netherworld Cluster, which is heavily inspired by Japanese history and culture. 
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liv Ngan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony narrows PlayStation VR2 launch window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/sony-narrows-playstation-vr2-launch-window</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/sony-narrows-playstation-vr2-launch-window"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T10:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We now have a slightly better idea when PlayStation VR2 will arrive: in "early 2023". 


A 2023 launch had been speculated based on recent reports eyeing Sony's financial forecast and production pipeline. 


As for when exactly "early 2023" will mean... Sony is staying schtum for now. We also still have no idea how much the headset itself will cost.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PSA: It's time to remove unauthorised items from your Elden Ring inventory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/psa-its-time-to-remove-unauthorised-items-from-your-elden-ring-inventory</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/psa-its-time-to-remove-unauthorised-items-from-your-elden-ring-inventory"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T10:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PSA: If you have any unauthorised items in your Elden Ring inventory, you may want to get rid of them sharpish.


As noted in the latest patch, unauthorised items will be given [ERROR] in the name to identify them, which may lead to a warning or penalty on your account.



The game's official Twitter account notes that this process will start "within a few days".
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steam Deck production outperforms Valve estimates, as shipping ramps up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/steam-deck-production-outperforms-valve-estimates-as-shipping-ramps-up</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/steam-deck-production-outperforms-valve-estimates-as-shipping-ramps-up"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T09:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's good news for some customers waiting to hear more about their Steam Deck reservations.


The latest from Valve states production on the handheld PC has "outperformed [the company's] estimates", a result of which has meant that some with "Q4" reservations may well get their deck sooner than expected.


Valve's Lawrence Yang tweeted: "Hi all, a few of you may have received an order email for your 'Q4 window' Steam Deck reservation today. This wasn't a mistake! 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sonic Frontiers trailer reveals November release date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/sonic-frontiers-trailer-reveals-november-release-date</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/sonic-frontiers-trailer-reveals-november-release-date"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T09:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Sonic Frontiers trailer has been spotted, with an 8th November release date attached.


We were expecting to see more of Sonic Frontiers at Gamescom's Opening Night Live ceremony tonight. Instead, a Japanese trailer briefly popped up this morning - though it has now been pulled offline.

Regardless, the internet never forgets. And, as shared by Nibel, the 8th November release date is now out in the wild.
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monster Hunter Rise now sold over 11m copies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/monster-hunter-rise-now-sold-over-11m-copies</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/monster-hunter-rise-now-sold-over-11m-copies"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T09:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monster Hunter Rise has now sold over 11m copies across Switch and PC.


Recent sales of the game have been driven by a bundle with brand new expansion Sunbreak,  Capcom said in a press release.


Moreover, Sunbreak alone has sold 4m copies worldwide since its release at the end of June.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes v1.25: Combiner]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/kubernetes-v1-25-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/23/kubernetes-v1-25-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kubernetes 1.25 Release Team
Announcing the release of Kubernetes v1.25!
This release includes a total of 40 enhancements. Fifteen of those enhancements are entering Alpha, ten are graduating to Beta, and thirteen are graduating to Stable. We also have two features being deprecated or removed.
Release theme and logo
Kubernetes 1.25: Combiner
The theme for Kubernetes v1.25 is Combiner.
The Kubernetes project itself is made up of many, many individual components that, when combined, take the form of the project you see today. It is also built and maintained by many individuals, all of them with different skills, experiences, histories, and interests, who join forces not just as the release team but as the many SIGs that support the project and the community year-round.
With this rel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation planning Gravity Rush film - report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/playstation-planning-gravity-rush-film-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/playstation-planning-gravity-rush-film-report"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T17:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation is planning to adapt the excellent Gravity Rush into a movie, it has been reported. 

Deadline states that the Japan Studio title is the latest to be added to a long, long line of projects in the works at  PlayStation Productions.


So far, director Anna Mastro (who helmed Disney+ series Secret Society of Second Born Royals) and script writer Emily Jerome (Panopticon) are attached.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Game Awards returns this December]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/the-game-awards-returns-this-december</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/the-game-awards-returns-this-december"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T16:40:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Game Awards 2022 will be held on 8th December, it has been announced.


The video game industry's annual winter trailer fest, which also includes some awards, will broadcast live from the Microsoft Theater in Los Angeles, and be livestreamed online.


This year's show will include a new category for Best Adaptation, which will award "shows, movies, books, podcasts, comics and more" which "authentically adapt" video game source material.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft Steve regrows beard after more than a decade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/minecraft-steve-regrows-beard-after-more-than-a-decade</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/minecraft-steve-regrows-beard-after-more-than-a-decade"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T16:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft's default player skin Steve has finally regrown its original beard, after 13 years.


Developer Mojang has updated the character designs for both Steve and Alex for the first time in over a decade. The changes add extra 3D elements to both of their blocky models - and return Steve's OG face fuzz.


Steve's beard was lost back in 2009, as part of a move to make Minecraft's default skin more gender-neutral. It wasn't until 2014 that the ponytailed Alex made an appearance.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest Return to Monkey Island clip shines light on streamlined UI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/latest-return-to-monkey-island-clip-shines-light-on-new-hint-system</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/latest-return-to-monkey-island-clip-shines-light-on-new-hint-system"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T15:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another Monday, another Return to Monkey Island clip for us all to pore over.


The latest clip from creator Ron Gilbert shows the game's new streamlined UI, with prompts appearing on-screen as hero Guybrush Threepwood explores the Scumm Bar on Melee Island.


When the cursor moves across the screen in this clip, messages such as "Time to talk to the pirate leaders" and "Smells good in there" pop up. The interactions shown do not appear intrusive, and seem to offer a clever way of keeping the story moving along.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamer completes Elden Ring one-handed level one run]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/streamer-completes-elden-ring-one-handed-level-one-run</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/streamer-completes-elden-ring-one-handed-level-one-run"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T15:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch streamer Miss Mikkaa has beaten Elden Ring single-handedly.


No really - she's beaten all Remembrances with just one hand and at level one.


And that includes the formidable Malenia.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tintin game to adapt Cigars of the Pharaoh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/tintin-game-to-adapt-cigars-of-the-pharaoh</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/tintin-game-to-adapt-cigars-of-the-pharaoh"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T15:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A video game version of Tintin classic Cigars of the Pharaoh will launch for PC, plus Nintendo Switch, PlayStation and Xbox consoles in 2023. 


The project will adapt one of the best early Tintin comic books, from a time when the young reporter (and Snowy the dog) were not yet accompanied by sidekick Captain Haddock. 


The project - developed by Madrid-based adventure game maker Pendulo Studios, and published by French company Microids - was first mentioned by Microids back in April 2020, before all went quiet. We've been waiting to hear more ever since. Now, here's a teaser trailer:
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cities Skylines gets pedestrianisation in new Plazas and Promenades expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/cities-skylines-gets-pedestrianisation-in-new-plazas-and-promenades-expansion</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/cities-skylines-gets-pedestrianisation-in-new-plazas-and-promenades-expansion"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paradox Interactive has unveiled new Cities Skylines expansion Plazas and Promenades expansion, coming to PC, Xbox, and PlayStation "soon".


Plazas and Promenades - the 11th major expansion for developer Colossal Order's acclaimed city builder - brings a new pedestrianisation focus to the game, giving budding urban planners the tools needed to add pedestrian-only streets, pedestrian zones, and zone-specific policies.


The latter include the likes of Slow Driving (which implements a 20mph speed limit for all non-highway roads within a pedestrian zone), Sugar Ban (which increases citizen lifespan at the expense of happiness), and Music (increasing happiness but also increasing noise pollution).
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft shuts down Marvel Blade game gossip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/ubisoft-shuts-down-marvel-blade-game-gossip</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/ubisoft-shuts-down-marvel-blade-game-gossip"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T14:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft has denied reports it is making a game based on Marvel's infamous vampire hunter Blade. 


The reports were sparked by photos - originally posted to Instagram back in July - that showed actors in Ubisoft-branded mo-cap suits apparently working on a Marvel project.


The images resurfaced yesterday thanks to YouTuber and regular Ubisoft leaker JorRaptor, who pointed out a clapperboard which listed director Bassam Tariq - who is also directing Marvel's 2023 Blade reboot.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trans Twitch streamer Keffals in hiding after doxxing attack follows swatting incident]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/trans-twitch-streamer-keffals-in-hiding-after-doxxing-attack-follows-swatting-incident</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/trans-twitch-streamer-keffals-in-hiding-after-doxxing-attack-follows-swatting-incident"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T14:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trans Twitch streamer Clara "Keffals" Sorrenti has been doxxed following a swatting incident earlier this month.


Sorrenti posted a video after the event describing how she was "terrorised" by police when they arrived at her home with assault rifles.


She's since moved to a hotel but has now been doxxed by a transphobic hate group known as Kiwi Farms.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Wordle starter suggested by The New York Times]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/new-wordle-starter-suggested-by-the-new-york-times</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/new-wordle-starter-suggested-by-the-new-york-times"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T14:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordleBot, The New York Times' own official "daily Wordle companion", has suggested a new starting word for us all to try. 


As noted by The Verge, WordleBot now lists 'Slate' as the optimal starting word. 


Previously, 'Crane' was the New York Times' favourite starting suggestion, however this has been given the boot in favour of the 'S' and 'T' inclusive 'Slate'. This makes sense, as 'S' and 'T' are two of the most commonly occurring letters throughout our dictionary. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mega Drive Mini 2 gets European release date, as full game catalogue announced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/mega-drive-mini-2-gets-european-release-date-as-full-game-catalogue-announced</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/mega-drive-mini-2-gets-european-release-date-as-full-game-catalogue-announced"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T13:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sega has announced the European release date for its Mega Drive Mini 2.


For those in Europe who are keen to get their hands on the mini retro console, you will be able to do so from the 27th October. If you are keeping track, this is the same day as the Genesis Mini 2 in North America. 


To accompany this release date announcement, Sega has also lifted the lid on all the games that will be available on the console. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Black Myth: Wukong trailer prompts fans to resurface misogynistic comments from developer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/new-black-myth-wukong-trailer-resurfaces-misogynistic-comments-from-developer</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/new-black-myth-wukong-trailer-resurfaces-misogynistic-comments-from-developer"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T13:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new gameplay trailer has been released for Black Myth: Wukong.


The game grew to prominence when it was revealed in 2020, showcasing its Soulslike gameplay and basis on Chinese novel Journey To The West.


However, the new trailer has also resurfaced criticism of the game's developer for misogynistic views.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fans believe new Pokémon is a pre-evolution of Scarlet and Violet's Legendaries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/fans-believe-new-pokemon-is-a-pre-evolution-of-scarlet-and-violets-legendaries</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/fans-believe-new-pokemon-is-a-pre-evolution-of-scarlet-and-violets-legendaries"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T12:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the weekend, we got a look at a brand new Pokémon. 
This new addition is Cyclizar, and it was featured as part of a new trailer for the upcoming Pokémon Scarlet and Pokémon Violet, shown during the closing ceremony of this year's Pokémon World Championships. 
The trailer, which you can watch below, shows Cyclizar with motorbike-esque appendages that are very similar to fellow bipedal reptile-like legendary Koraidon. It also shows off a new move called "Shed Tail", which allows players to create a substitute and then "swap places with a party Pokémon in waiting". 
 Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tee off with PGA Tour 2K23 and Tiger Woods this October]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/tee-off-with-pga-tour-2k23-and-tiger-woods-this-october</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/tee-off-with-pga-tour-2k23-and-tiger-woods-this-october"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We now have release dates for the various editions of upcoming golfing sim PGA Tour 2K23, which features Tiger Woods as its cover athlete.


First up are the PGA Tour 2K23 Deluxe Edition and the Tiger Woods Edition. These will both be released on 11th October. The standard edition will then be released a few days later on the 14th October. 


You can see a new live-action trailer below.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyundai Uses Example Keys for Encryption System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/hyundai-uses-example-keys-for-encryption-system.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/hyundai-uses-example-keys-for-encryption-system.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T11:38:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is a <a href="https://www.theregister.com/2022/08/17/software_developer_cracks_hyundai_encryption/">dumb crypto mistake</a> I had not previously encountered:</p>
<blockquote><p>A developer says it was possible to run their own software on the car infotainment hardware after discovering the vehicle&#8217;s manufacturer had secured its system using keys that were not only publicly known but had been lifted from programming examples.</p>
<p>[&#8230;]</p>
<p>&#8220;Turns out the [AES] encryption key in that script is the first AES 128-bit CBC example key listed in the NIST document <a href="https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-38a.pdf">SP800-38A</a> [PDF]&#8221;.</p>
<p>[&#8230;]</p>
<p>Luck held out, in a way. &#8220;Greenluigi1&#8221; found within the firmware image the RSA public key used by the updater, and searched online for a portion of that key. The search results pointed to a common public key that shows up in online tutorials like &#8220;...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK National Grid reportedly plans cheaper energy if you avoid peak-time use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/uk-national-grid-reportedly-plans-cheaper-energy-if-you-avoid-peak-time-use</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/uk-national-grid-reportedly-plans-cheaper-energy-if-you-avoid-peak-time-use"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T11:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discounts on energy bills will reportedly be offered to UK households which avoid electricity usage during peak times.


This could mean rebates for those who avoid using consumer goods such as computers and games consoles between the hours of 5pm and 8pm each evening, BBC News wrote.


The scheme is reportedly being planned by the National Grid electricity system operator (ESO) for those with smart meters, with full details to be set out in the next two weeks after consultation with energy companies and UK regulator Ofgem.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony sued for £5bn for "ripping people off" on PlayStation Store]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/sony-sued-for-5bn-for-ripping-people-off-on-playstation-store</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/sony-sued-for-5bn-for-ripping-people-off-on-playstation-store"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T11:14:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony is being sued for £5bn, accused of "ripping people off" on its online store.


The legal claim is led by ex-managing director of Which UK Alex Neill and was filed with the Competition Appeal Tribunal last week.


It claims by charging a 30 percent commission on digital games and in-game purchases on the PlayStation Store, Sony is in breach of competition law.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Last of Us' new Trophy list won't make you complete the game on harder difficulties]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/the-last-of-us-new-trophy-list-wont-make-you-complete-the-game-on-harder-difficulties</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/the-last-of-us-new-trophy-list-wont-make-you-complete-the-game-on-harder-difficulties"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T10:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of its release this September, the Trophy list for The Last of Us Part 1's PlayStation 5 remake has leaked. 


Please be aware, the below article contains story spoilers for The Last of Us. Read at your own discretion.


A series of shots showing off the remake's Trophy list has been shared by Twitter account Naughty Dog Central. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite cosmetics are coming to Destiny 2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/fortnite-cosmetics-are-coming-to-destiny-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/fortnite-cosmetics-are-coming-to-destiny-2"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T10:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Destiny 2 will host a series of Fortnite cosmetics, a recent datamine of the game has revealed. 


Themed armour sets for each of Destiny's three classes have been leaked, each showcasing a look based on a classic Fortnite skin (thanks, Ginsor). 


Bungie is yet to confirm the collaboration, which seems likely to be made official tomorrow night during its big Destiny 2 livestream. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Original GTA developer hit with copyright strikes against prototype videos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/original-gta-developer-hit-with-copyright-strikes-against-prototype-videos</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/original-gta-developer-hit-with-copyright-strikes-against-prototype-videos"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T10:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A developer from the original Grand Theft Auto game has reportedly had prototype videos hit with a copyright strike from Rockstar Games.


Mike Dailly, one of the founders of DMA Design (now Rockstar North), has tweeted he's removed any GTA videos due to the strikes.


"I see Rockstar are going full fuckers mode again, issuing copyright strikes to any GTA video they can find - including both my prototype videos. So now they're trying to block all release of anyone's work on a game - and any old development footage," he tweeted yesterday.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First footage of HBO's The Last of Us TV adaptation released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/first-footage-of-hbos-the-last-of-us-tv-adaptation-released</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/first-footage-of-hbos-the-last-of-us-tv-adaptation-released"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T08:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We now have our first look at HBO's upcoming adaptation of The Last of Us.


Shared as part of a collection of teasers for the service's new season, this clip was brief but enticing. It comes with the obligatory dramatic music as it shows us snippets of Pedro Pascal's Joel running through the streets with someone who I won't name to avoid spoilers, Bella Ramsay as Ellie and Nick Offerman as Bill. While we don't see any of the series' infected enemies, we do get a brief snap of some fungal like spores on a wall, hinting at the devastation the world is in. 


The entire HBO clip, which can be seen below, also gives us small teasers for shows such as The Idol, Doom Patrol and Pennyworth. However, if you want to jump straight to The Last of Us, that begins at around the 1:43 mark. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Kennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physics Safety Tip]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2662/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2662/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/physics_safety_tip.png" title="In general, avoid exposure to any temperatures, pressures, particle energies, or states of matter that physicists think are neat." alt="In general, avoid exposure to any temperatures, pressures, particle energies, or states of matter that physicists think are neat." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/22/sig-storage-spotlight/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/22/sig-storage-spotlight/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frederico Muñoz (SAS)
Since the very beginning of Kubernetes, the topic of persistent data and how to address the requirement of stateful applications has been an important topic. Support for stateless deployments was natural, present from the start, and garnered attention, becoming very well-known. Work on better support for stateful applications was also present from early on, with each release increasing the scope of what could be run on Kubernetes.
Message queues, databases, clustered filesystems: these are some examples of the solutions that have different storage requirements and that are, today, increasingly deployed in Kubernetes. Dealing with ephemeral and persistent storage, local or remote, file or block, from many different vendors, while considering how to provide the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MultiVersus tops Elden Ring to become July's best-selling game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/multiversus-tops-elden-ring-to-become-julys-best-selling-game</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/multiversus-tops-elden-ring-to-become-julys-best-selling-game"/>
        <updated>2022-08-21T16:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MultiVersus has knocked Elden Ring off the top spot of the month's best-selling games.

NPD Group reports (thanks, NME) that despite being free-to-play - albeit with in-game purchases - MultiVersus is the highest-grossing game of July 2022, due in part to its Founder Packs promotion. 

It may not sound like a particularly impressive feat but to put it into perspective, since its release in February, Elden Ring has been the best-selling game every month but one.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find out how F1 Manager's "cutting-edge" motion capture "brings the game to life"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/find-out-how-f1-managers-cutting-edge-motion-capture-brings-the-game-to-life</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/find-out-how-f1-managers-cutting-edge-motion-capture-brings-the-game-to-life"/>
        <updated>2022-08-21T16:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontier has released another instalment of its F1 Manager behind-the-scenes series, this time focussing on how its "cutting-edge motion capture technology has been used to recreate those dramatic moments during a race weekend".

The video also showcases how the team worked alongside the BWT Alpine F1 Team to capture a real F1 pit stop, which you will see "brought to life in the game".

It's a fascinating glimpse into how games are made, and the lengths developers go to to try and create an authentic sim experience. Check it out below:
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft+ may be launching on Xbox soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/ubisoft-may-be-launching-on-xbox-soon</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/ubisoft-may-be-launching-on-xbox-soon"/>
        <updated>2022-08-21T15:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It looks like Ubisoft+ - Ubisoft's own game subscription service - may finally be on the way to Xbox.

Up until now, Ubisoft+ has only been available to players on PC, but a service that scrapes Xbox's backend and spotted by our friends at VGC has reportedly found an Ubisoft+ logo in the system, hinting that Ubisoft+ may be coming soon.

A prior announcement confirmed that Ubisoft+ - unlike EA Play - would not be part of Xbox Game Pass, and this is unlikely to have changed, particularly as a cut-down version of the Ubisoft sub, Ubisoft+ Classics, is available within the upper tiers of Sony's rival PS Plus. We'll have to wait until we get a formal announcement to confirm that either way, though.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This new Attacker puts the Swarm in Rainbow Six Siege's upcoming Operation Brutal Swarm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/this-new-attacker-puts-the-swarm-in-rainbow-six-sieges-upcoming-operation-brutal-swarm</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/this-new-attacker-puts-the-swarm-in-rainbow-six-sieges-upcoming-operation-brutal-swarm"/>
        <updated>2022-08-21T15:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft has pulled back the curtain to give a sneaky peek at what's to come in Rainbow Six Siege's next update, Operation Brutal Swarm.

Though details are light - more will be revealed in an upcoming livestream set for 21st August - we do learn more about new a 1 Health and 3 Speed Attacker Grim, a Singaporean with one goal: "to get the job done".

"Grim's experience in the EOD taught him how easily things can blow up when a target's position and proximity is unknown," Ubisoft teases in a blog update. "That's where the Kawan Hive Launcher comes in, with no reload and a low fire rate the launcher allows for versatile gameplay, using Intel-Gathering and Area Denial to counter roamers, make entry, and protect objectives.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sega is now turning Space Channel 5 and Comix Zone into movies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/sega-is-now-turning-space-channel-5-and-comix-zone-into-movies</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/sega-is-now-turning-space-channel-5-and-comix-zone-into-movies"/>
        <updated>2022-08-21T11:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sega is giving two more of its classic titles the movie treatment: Space Channel 5 and Comix Zone.

No doubt inspired by the runaway success of the Sonic movies, Sega looks set to adapt the two games alongside Picturestart, which is also working on the upcoming Borderlands movie (which is seemingly now in post-production).

Dance game Space Channel 5 will be retitled Channel 5 and, according to Hollywood Reporter, "tell the story of a hapless fast-food worker who is recruited by a freedom reporter from the future to save the world from aliens using the one thing that unites all people on the planet: our love of silly viral dances". 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New job ad hints that Netflix is "rapidly expanding new gaming offerings"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/new-job-ad-says-netflix-is-rapidly-expanding-new-gaming-offerings</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/new-job-ad-says-netflix-is-rapidly-expanding-new-gaming-offerings"/>
        <updated>2022-08-21T10:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix is looking to "rapidly expand" the "new gaming offerings" available on its cloud gaming service.

That's according to a new job advertisement put out by the company that seeks a new senior software engineer with "experience with game development".

As well as finding someone with all the necessary coding skills, Netflix hopes the new recruit will also have some experience in "Unity or Unreal game engines" and says it is "rapidly expanding new gaming offerings" on its global streaming service. 
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Fantasy 14 hopes this poster will persuade you to "voluntarily return" any "accidental" lottery deposits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/final-fantasy-14-hopes-this-poster-will-persuade-you-to-voluntarily-return-any-accidental-lottery-deposits</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/final-fantasy-14-hopes-this-poster-will-persuade-you-to-voluntarily-return-any-accidental-lottery-deposits"/>
        <updated>2022-08-21T10:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Final Fantasy 14 is hoping that a cute poster will persuade players to "voluntarily return" any mistaken housing lottery deposits.

In a broader update about the 6.2 patch, the Final Fantasy 14 development team finally confirmed plans "to address a recent issue with the housing lottery system".

"An NPC by which players may voluntarily return the deposit they were accidentally refunded has been added," the update states, above an image of three cute apology posters starring Namazu and Lalafell.
 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: The Language of the Jumbo Flying Squid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/friday-squid-blogging-the-language-of-the-jumbo-flying-squid.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/friday-squid-blogging-the-language-of-the-jumbo-flying-squid.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T21:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The jumbo flying squid (<i>Dosidicus gigas</i>) uses its color-changing ability <a href="https://bigthink.com/life/cannibal-squid-speak/">as a language</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>In 2020, however, marine biologists discovered that jumbo flying squid are surprisingly coordinated. Despite their large numbers, the squid rarely bumped into each other or competed for the same prey. The scientists hypothesized that the flickering pigments allowed the squid to quickly communicate complex messages, such as when it was preparing to attack and what it was targeting.</p>
<p>The researchers observed that the squid displayed 12 distinct pigmentation patterns in a variety of sequences, similar to how humans arrange words in a sentence. For example, squid darkened while pursuing prey and then shifted to a half light/half dark pattern immediately before striking. The researchers hypothesized that these whole-body pigment changes signaled a precise action, such as &#8220;I&#8217;m about to attack.&#8221;...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Age Milestone Privileges]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2661/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2661/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/age_milestone_privileges.png" title="If you reach 122, you get complete unrevertible editorial control over Jeanne Calment's Wikipedia article." alt="If you reach 122, you get complete unrevertible editorial control over Jeanne Calment's Wikipedia article." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brainstorming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2022/brainstorming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2022/brainstorming/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development satire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USB “Rubber Ducky” Attack Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/usb-rubber-ducky-attack-tool.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/usb-rubber-ducky-attack-tool.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T11:45:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The USB Rubber Ducky is getting <a href="https://www.theverge.com/23308394/usb-rubber-ducky-review-hack5-defcon-duckyscript">better and better</a>.</p>
<blockquote><p>Already, previous versions of the Rubber Ducky could carry out attacks like <a href="https://github.com/hak5/usbrubberducky-payloads/tree/master/payloads/library/credentials/-RD-Credz-Plz">creating a fake Windows pop-up box</a> to harvest a user&#8217;s login credentials or <a href="https://github.com/hak5/usbrubberducky-payloads/tree/master/payloads/library/exfiltration/chrome-exfil">causing Chrome to send all saved passwords to an attacker&#8217;s webserver</a>. But these attacks had to be carefully crafted for specific operating systems and software versions and lacked the flexibility to work across platforms.</p>
<p>The newest Rubber Ducky aims to overcome these limitations. It ships with a major upgrade to the DuckyScript programming language, which is used to create the commands that the Rubber Ducky will enter into a target machine. While previous versions were mostly limited to writing keystroke sequences, DuckyScript 3.0 is a feature-rich language, letting users write functions, store variables, and use logic flow controls (i.e., if this&#8230; then that)...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Stargazing, solutions and staycations: the Kubernetes 1.24 release interview]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/18/stargazing-solutions-and-staycations-the-kubernetes-1.24-release-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/18/stargazing-solutions-and-staycations-the-kubernetes-1.24-release-interview/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Craig Box (Google)
The Kubernetes project has participants from all around the globe. Some are friends, some are colleagues, and some are strangers. The one thing that unifies them, no matter their differences, are that they all have an interesting story. It is my pleasure to be the documentarian for the stories of the Kubernetes community in the weekly Kubernetes Podcast from Google. With every new Kubernetes release comes an interview with the release team lead, telling the story of that release, but also their own personal story.
With 1.25 around the corner, the tradition continues with a look back at the story of 1.24. That release was led by James Laverack of Jetstack. James was on the podcast in May, and while you can read his story below, if you can, please do listen to it i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Discussions is now available on GitHub Enterprise Server]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/?p=66541</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-17-github-discussions-is-now-available-on-github-enterprise-server/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T16:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of GitHub Enterprise Server 3.6, enterprise customers will now be able to use GitHub Discussions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evi Liu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Unexpected Love Letter to Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=12894</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/an_unexpected_love_letter_to_azure/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure's Computer Vision can generate alt text in a sophisticated way that's a game-changer for making accessibility and inclusivity frictionless.
The post An Unexpected Love Letter to Azure appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Enterprise Server 3.6 is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/?p=66529</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-17-github-enterprise-server-3-6-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T13:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Discussions and Audit Log Streaming, new automation features, and security enhancements are available now in GitHub Enterprise Server 3.6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melody Mileski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zoom Exploit on MacOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/zoom-exploit-on-macos.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/zoom-exploit-on-macos.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T11:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/8/12/23303411/zoom-defcon-root-access-privilege-escalation-hack-patrick-wardle">vulnerability</a> was reported to Zoom last December:</p>
<blockquote><p>The exploit works by targeting the installer for the Zoom application, which needs to run with special user permissions in order to install or remove the main Zoom application from a computer. Though the installer requires a user to enter their password on first adding the application to the system, Wardle found that an auto-update function then continually ran in the background with superuser privileges.</p>
<p>When Zoom issued an update, the updater function would install the new package after checking that it had been cryptographically signed by Zoom. But a bug in how the checking method was implemented meant that giving the updater any file with the same name as Zoom&#8217;s signing certificate would be enough to pass the test&#8212;so an attacker could substitute any kind of malware program and have it be run by the updater with elevated privilege...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gen Z]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2660/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2660/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/gen_z.png" title="Curdled milk, of a peculiar kind, made after a Bulgarian recipe and called &quot;yaghurt,&quot; is now a Parisian fad and is believed to be a remedy against growing old. A correspondent who has tried it, says he would prefer to die young. (1905, The Elk Falls Journal)" alt="Curdled milk, of a peculiar kind, made after a Bulgarian recipe and called &quot;yaghurt,&quot; is now a Parisian fad and is believed to be a remedy against growing old. A correspondent who has tried it, says he would prefer to die young. (1905, The Elk Falls Journal)" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://festivus.dev/kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://festivus.dev/kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Kramer decided to use Kubernetes for his website. Jerry tries to explain what that entails. Kramer is adamant to do it all himself.
Kubernetes. pic.twitter.com/SEt6wVklmq
— den (@DennisCode) August 18, 2022]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering Festivus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 Transparency Report: January to June]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/?p=66458</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-16-2022-transparency-report-january-to-june/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re reporting on a six-month period rather than annually to increase our level of transparency. For this report, we’ve continued with the more granular reporting we began in our 2021 reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rose Coogan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remotely Controlling Touchscreens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/remotely-controlling-touchscreens-2.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/remotely-controlling-touchscreens-2.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-16T11:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is more of a demonstration than a real-world vulnerability, but researchers can use electromagnetic interference to <a href="https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/9833718">remotely control touchscreens</a>.</p>
<p>From a <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/g5vyq3/researchers-use-invisible-finger-to-remotely-control-touchscreens">news article</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s important to note that the attack has a few key limitations. Firstly, the hackers need to know the target&#8217;s phone passcode, or launch the attack while the phone is unlocked. Secondly, the victim needs to put the phone face down, otherwise the battery and motherboard will block the electromagnetic signal. Thirdly, the antenna array has to be no more than four centimeters (around 1.5 inches) away. For all these reasons the researchers themselves admit that the &#8220;invisible finger&#8221; technique is a proof of concept that at this point is far from being a threat outside of a university lab.  ...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The next step for LGTM.com: GitHub code scanning!]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/?p=66506</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-15-the-next-step-for-lgtm-com-github-code-scanning/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T15:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, GitHub code scanning has all of LGTM.com’s key features—and more! The time has therefore come to announce the plan for the gradual deprecation of LGTM.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bas van Schaik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$23 Million YouTube Royalties Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/23-million-youtube-royalties-scam.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/23-million-youtube-royalties-scam.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T14:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Scammers were able to convince YouTube that other peoples&#8217; music was their own. They <a href="https://mashable.com/article/youtube-copyright-royalties-heist">successfully stole $23 million</a> before they were caught.</p>
<p>No one knows how common this scam is, and how much money total is being stolen in this way. Presumably this is not an uncommon fraud.</p>
<blockquote><p>While the size of the heist and the breadth of the scheme may be very unique, it&#8217;s certainly a situation that many YouTube content creators have faced before. YouTube&#8217;s Content ID system, meant to help creators, has been weaponized by bad faith actors in order to make money off content that isn&#8217;t theirs. While some false claims are just mistakes caused by automated systems, the MediaMuv case is a perfect example of how fraudsters are also purposefully taking advantage of digital copyright rules...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Meet Our Contributors - APAC (China region)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/15/meet-our-contributors-china-ep-03/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/15/meet-our-contributors-china-ep-03/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors & Interviewers: Avinesh Tripathi, Debabrata Panigrahi, Jayesh Srivastava, Priyanka Saggu, Purneswar Prasad, Vedant Kakde
Hello, everyone 👋
Welcome back to the third edition of the "Meet Our Contributors" blog post series for APAC.
This post features four outstanding contributors from China, who have played diverse leadership and community roles in the upstream Kubernetes project.
So, without further ado, let's get straight to the article.
Andy Zhang
Andy Zhang currently works for Microsoft China at the Shanghai site. His main focus is on Kubernetes storage drivers. Andy started contributing to Kubernetes about 5 years ago.
He states that as he is working in Azure Kubernetes Service team and spends most of his time contributing to the Kubernetes community project. Now he is the mai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://festivus.dev/javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://festivus.dev/javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Kramer tries to explain how JavaScript works to Jerry and George. George is surprised to find out that his car runs JavaScript.
JavaScript. pic.twitter.com/YnPslr8g68
— den (@DennisCode) August 16, 2022]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering Festivus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Speaking Engagements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/upcoming-speaking-engagements-22.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2022/08/upcoming-speaking-engagements-22.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-14T17:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is a current list of where and when I am scheduled to speak:</p>
<ul>
<li>I&#8217;m speaking as part of a Geneva Centre for Security Policy course on <a href="https://www.gcsp.ch/courses/cyber-security-context-international-security">Cyber Security in the Context of International Security</a>, online, on September 22, 2022.</li>
<li>I&#8217;m speaking at <a href="https://www.avantec.ch/inside/">IT-Security INSIDE 2022</a> in Zurich, Switzerland, on September 22, 2022.</li>
</ul>
<p>The list is maintained on <a href="https://www.schneier.com/events/">this page</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation Struggles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2022/automation-struggles/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2022/automation-struggles/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development satire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Enhancing Kubernetes one KEP at a Time]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/11/enhancing-kubernetes-one-kep-at-a-time/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/11/enhancing-kubernetes-one-kep-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ryler Hockenbury (Mastercard)
Did you know that Kubernetes v1.24 has 46 enhancements? That's a lot of new functionality packed into a 4-month release cycle. The Kubernetes release team coordinates the logistics of the release, from remediating test flakes to publishing updated docs. It's a ton of work, but they always deliver.
The release team comprises around 30 people across six subteams - Bug Triage, CI Signal, Enhancements, Release Notes, Communications, and Docs.  Each of these subteams manages a component of the release. This post will focus on the role of the enhancements subteam and how you can get involved.
What's the enhancements subteam?
Great question. We'll get to that in a second but first, let's talk about how features are managed in Kubernetes.
Each new feature requ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Small Addition To The Product Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://festivus.dev/product-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://festivus.dev/product-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Small Addition To The Product Roadmap Kramer pitches a small but irrelevant feature to be added to the product roadmap. Jerry hesitates. George is worried about the AWS bill.
Small addition to the product roadmap. pic.twitter.com/0janK7bylL
— den (@DennisCode) August 11, 2022]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering Festivus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Pages now uses Actions by default]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/?p=66464</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-10-github-pages-now-uses-actions-by-default/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As GitHub Pages, home to 16 million websites, approaches its 15th anniversary, we’re excited to announce that all sites now build and deploy with GitHub Actions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Patterson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Was Wrong: Why AWS Can’t End the re:Invent Service Release Tidal Wave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=12880</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/why_amazon_cant_end_the_release_tidal_wave/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The frenzy of AWS product releases around re:Invent is terrible for its users. But upending AWS's cultural cornerstones would be even worse for customers.
The post I Was Wrong: Why AWS Can’t End the re:Invent Service Release Tidal Wave appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://festivus.dev/code-reviews/</id>
        <link href="https://festivus.dev/code-reviews/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code Reviews Kramer tries to get Jerry to merge a pull request that automates some infrastructure work. Jerry hesitates, but merges it. He owns the code now.
Code reviews. pic.twitter.com/tAlkfpyk7o
— den (@DennisCode) August 11, 2022]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering Festivus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependabot now alerts for vulnerable GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/?p=66406</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2022-08-09-dependabot-now-alerts-for-vulnerable-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T15:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions gives teams access to powerful, native CI/CD capabilities right next to their code hosted in GitHub. Starting today, GitHub will send a Dependabot alert for vulnerable GitHub Actions, making it even easier to stay up to date and fix security vulnerabilities in your actions workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brittany O'Shea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine 3.13.12, 3.14.8, 3.15.6 and 3.16.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.13.12-3.14.8-3.15.6-3.16.2-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.13.12-3.14.8-3.15.6-3.16.2-released.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine 3.13.12, 3.14.8, 3.15.6 and 3.16.2 released]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alpine Linux News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[S3 Intelligent-Tiering: What It Takes To Actually Break Even]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=12863</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/s3-intelligent-tiering-breaking-even/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-05T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Cloud Economists, we're often asked when it makes sense for an object to be in Amazon S3's Intelligent-Tiering (S3-IT) storage class. The answer, as is unfortunately often the case in the world of consulting, is "it depends".
The post S3 Intelligent-Tiering: What It Takes To Actually Break Even appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Rasmussen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes Removals and Major Changes In 1.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/04/upcoming-changes-in-kubernetes-1-25/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/04/upcoming-changes-in-kubernetes-1-25/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Kat Cosgrove, Frederico Muñoz, Debabrata Panigrahi
As Kubernetes grows and matures, features may be deprecated, removed, or replaced with improvements for the health of the project. Kubernetes v1.25 includes several major changes and one major removal.
The Kubernetes API Removal and Deprecation process
The Kubernetes project has a well-documented deprecation policy for features. This policy states that stable APIs may only be deprecated when a newer, stable version of that same API is available and that APIs have a minimum lifetime for each stability level. A deprecated API is one that has been marked for removal in a future Kubernetes release; it will continue to function until removal (at least one year from the deprecation), but usage will result in a warning being displayed. R…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/02/sig-docs-spotlight-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/08/02/sig-docs-spotlight-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Purneswar Prasad
Introduction
The official documentation is the go-to source for any open source project. For Kubernetes,
it's an ever-evolving Special Interest Group (SIG) with people constantly putting in their efforts
to make details about the project easier to consume for new contributors and users. SIG Docs publishes
the official documentation on kubernetes.io which includes,
but is not limited to, documentation of the core APIs, core architectural details, and CLI tools
shipped with the Kubernetes release.
To learn more about the work of SIG Docs and its future ahead in shaping the community, I have summarised
my conversation with the co-chairs, Divya Mohan (DM),
Rey Lejano (RL) and Natali Vlatko (NV), who ran through the
SIG's goals and how fellow contributors can help.
A su…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>