<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-09T00:38:45.781Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.5.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Die Hard's John McClane teased for Call of Duty: Warzone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148912</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-die-hards-john-mcclane-teased-for-call-of-duty-warzone"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T20:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 1980s action movie heroes are coming en masse to Warzone. After this week's tease that Rambo will be added to the battle royale, Activision has indicated Die Hard's John McClane is on his way, too.
Activision even created a website for a fictional air conditioning repair company called Nakatomi Duct Cleaning, offering its services in Verdansk.
The website says "A NAKATOMI CORP DIVISION MASTERING A/C DUCT CLEANING SINCE 1988", but the current Warzone map is set in 1984. Nah... I'm applying too much logic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capcom made a huge chalk lycan on a hill in Somerset to promote Resident Evil Village]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148911</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-capcom-made-a-huge-chalk-artwork-of-a-lycan-on-a-hill-in-somerset-to-promote-resident-evil-village"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T19:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, if you pottered along to the Mendip Hill near Cheddar, Somerset, you'd probably have caught a glimpse of something a bit off: a huge chalk artwork of a lycan.
Local press reported the strange image on Monday, 3rd May after it popped up overnight - and seemingly had no idea what it was about or who made it.
Its true nature was revealed when Resident Evil Village came out on Friday - it was a Capcom PR stunt. And a pretty cool one, I'll admit.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modder's Nier: Automata HD texture pack finally complete after four years of development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148910</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-modders-nier-automata-hd-texture-pack-finally-complete-after-four-years-of-development"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T18:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A modder has released their final Nier: Automata HD texture pack after four years of development.
GPUnity's texture pack mod began life soon after Nier: Automata launched on PC in March 2017. They've continued to work on the mod since then, and now, four years later, released the final version.
Nier: Automata's PC version is infamous for a raft of technical issues that were fixed by modders, including a constant stutter tick due to the game running at around 59 frames per second (this is something explored …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: The role-playing game’s afoot in charming black comedy Murder Bury Win]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1759895</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1759895"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T18:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not an instant classic like  Clue,  but it's fun, very solid indie fare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sega: No plans for Lost Judgment on PC "at this time"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148909</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-sega-no-plans-for-lost-judgment-on-pc-at-this-time"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Sega announced Lost Judgment for PlayStation 5, PlayStation 4, Xbox Series X and S, and Xbox One - but there was no word of a PC version.
It seemed an odd omission - Tojo Dojo noticed the Yakuza spin-off sequel was briefly listed as coming to PC on the official countdown website that was home to the Lost Judgment announcement. Even after mention of PC was removed from the website, fans spotted mention of the Steam logo in the Lost Judgment website source code.
Unfortunately, it appears Lost Judgm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivian’s electric truck features include air compressor and AC outlets]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763611</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763611"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T17:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's got storage compartments galore, plus an extending truck bed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple brass discussed disclosing 128-million iPhone hack, then decided not to]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763592</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763592"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T16:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emails entered into Epic Games lawsuit show execs contradicting Apple talking points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance re-release on Nintendo Switch delayed at the last minute]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148906</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-baldurs-gate-dark-alliance-re-release-on-nintendo-switch-delayed-at-the-last-minute"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T15:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance's re-release on Nintendo Switch was delayed at the last minute.
The re-release of the much-loved 20 year-old action RPG went ahead as planned yesterday on Xbox One, where it costs a pricey £29.99, and PlayStation 4, where for some reason it costs a fiver cheaper at £24.99.
But even though the official Black Isle Studios Twitter page said yesterday that the Switch version would arrive in a couple of hours, the game failed to materialise on the Nintendo eShop.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Titanfall 2 Gauntlet world record broken twice in two weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148905</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-titanfall-2-gauntlet-world-record-broken-twice-in-a-week"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T15:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Titanfall 2 enjoying an Apex Legends-powered resurgence, so is its superb Gauntlet.
Respawn's wall-hopping assault course tasks players with completing one lap as quickly as possible - and nearly five years after Titanfall 2 came out, speedrunners are breaking world records again.
In October 2019, speedrunner Cash Mayo set an incredible time of 11.7 seconds, shaving a fraction off Mayo's previous world record of 11.9 seconds:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["The Yakuza series has been transformed into a turn-based RPG," says dev]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148879</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-the-yakuza-series-has-been-transformed-into-a-turn-based-rpg-says-dev"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T11:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking to IGN, Yakuza creator Toshihiro Nagoshi and producer Kazuki Hosokawa confirmed the plan for the two series:
"The Yakuza series has been transformed into a turn-based RPG. On the other hand, over the years, Ryu ga Gotoku Studio has accumulated resources and know-how of making flashy and exhilarating action games that are effortless to enjoy. We decided that we should let our signature action gameplay live on through Lost Judgment."
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil Village is off to a flyer on Steam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148875</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-resident-evil-village-is-off-to-a-flyer-on-steam"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil Village is off to a flyer on Steam.
It saw 101,726 peak concurrents on launch day, 7th May.
That makes Capcom's latest comfortably the biggest PC launch for any Resident Evil game. According to SteamCharts, Resident Evil 7 managed an all-time peak of 18,211 concurrents, Resident Evil 6 peaked with 11,836, and the most recent release, the Resident Evil 3 remake, hit 32,635. Only the Resident Evil 2 remake, which saw a concurrents peak of 74,024, comes close.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raven is trying to raise Call of Duty: Warzone's skill ceiling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148870</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-call-of-duty-warzone-developer-says-its-battle-royale-is-close-to-a-balance-homeostasis"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T10:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Warzone developer Raven has said it is close to a "balance homeostasis", where most weapon options are "at the very least viable" - leaving it to focus on raising the skill ceiling of the game.
The developer shared its balance change philosophy as part of the patch notes for a Warzone update that went live this week.
Raven spoke openly about the difficulty it faces making sweeping changes to the Warzone meta, as popular guns are inevitably affected.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It began as an AI-fueled dungeon game. Then it got much darker]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763513</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763513"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T10:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI algorithm created disturbing stories, including sex scenes involving children.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sniper Ghost Warrior Contracts 2 gets PS5 delay due to "unforeseen technical issues"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-sniper-ghost-warrior-contracts-2-gets-ps5-delay-due-to-unforeseen-technical-issues</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-sniper-ghost-warrior-contracts-2-gets-ps5-delay-due-to-unforeseen-technical-issues"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T21:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CI Games has announced a delay for the PlayStation 5 version of its upcoming long-distance shooter Sniper Ghost Warrior Contracts 2, resulting from "unforeseen technical issues".
Sniper Ghost Warrior Contracts 2 - which features a "dramatic single-player campaign set in modern day Middle East" - was originally due on PlayStation 5 on 4th June, arriving alongside versions for PS4, Xbox One, Xbox X/S and PC. However, despite the PS5 edition's delay to a currently unspecified future point, other platforms will…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 “Sun Valley” will do away with Windows 95 era icons]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763533</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763533"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T21:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The results are more subtle than you might expect from a 25+ year visual update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: COVID Relief Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/friday-squid-blogging-covid-relief-funds.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/friday-squid-blogging-covid-relief-funds.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T21:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A town in Japan built a giant squid statue with its COVID relief grant.
One local told the Chunichi Shimbun newspaper that while the statue may be effective in the long run, the money could have been used for &#8220;urgent support,&#8221; such as for medical staff and long-term care facilities.
But a spokesperson for the town told Fuji News Network that the statue would be a tourist attraction and part of a long term strategy to help promote Noto&#8217;s famous flying squid.

I am impressed by the town&#821…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony faces lawsuit over alleged “monopoly pricing” of PlayStation downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763530</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763530"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T20:19:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proposed class action says Sony's moves have increased prices for PlayStation games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Returnal reinstating pre-rollback fixes in new patch tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-returnal-reinstating-pre-rollback-fixes-in-new-patch-tomorrow</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-returnal-reinstating-pre-rollback-fixes-in-new-patch-tomorrow"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T20:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Housemarque is releasing a new patch for PlayStation 5-exclusive roguelite Returnal tomorrow, 8th May, which will, among other things, reinstate all pre-rollback fixes that briefly went live earlier this week.
On Wednesday, Housemarque was forced to pull Returnal's 1.3.3 patch after players began reporting it was corrupting save games. The developer later released version 1.3.4, which rolled back to Returnal's most recent stable build - a move that enabled some affected players to resume their pro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[96% of US users opt out of app tracking in iOS 14.5, analytics find]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763464</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763464"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the first data on user behavior exceeds advertisers' worst fears.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ajit Pai promised cheaper Internet—real prices rose 19 percent instead]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763472</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763472"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Home-Internet prices rose four times faster than inflation in Trump era.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skullgirls 2nd Encore's next DLC fighter Umbrella has a ravenous sentient brolly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-skullgirls-2nd-encores-next-dlc-fighter-umbrella-has-a-ravenous-sentient-brolly</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-skullgirls-2nd-encores-next-dlc-fighter-umbrella-has-a-ravenous-sentient-brolly"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Hidden Variable has unveiled the latest DLC character to join the roster of acclaimed fighters Skullgirls 2nd Encore and the free-to-play Skullgirls Mobile: the sou'westered, be-wellied Umbrella and her sentient brolly chum, Hungern.
Umbrella, the second DLC character to arrive as part of Skullgirls 2nd Encore's season pass (following on from March's Annie), is described as a small, slow character with limited movement that's able to take some "big swings" thanks Hungern.
Indeed, while the perpetu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Autopilot director contradicts Musk’s self-driving timeline]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763422</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763422"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk described full autonomy as "basically a solved problem" in 2016.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acclaimed post-apocalyptic city builder Frostpunk is heading to mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-acclaimed-post-apocalyptic-city-builder-frostpunk-is-heading-to-mobile</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-acclaimed-post-apocalyptic-city-builder-frostpunk-is-heading-to-mobile"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer 11 Bit Studios' superb post-apocalyptic city builder Frostpunk is coming to iOS and Android devices "later this year".
Frostpunk initially launched on PC in 2018 before making its way to Xbox and PlayStation the following year. It's a fascinating, frequently gruelling, and wonderfully atmospheric experience, delivering a captivating blend of brutal survival sim, city builder, and rich narrative as players attempt to survive - through the slow expansion their settlement, and with plenty of tough mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google wants people to use 2FA, so it’s just going to turn it on for them]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763423</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763423"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-tech-savvy users always use the defaults, and the default will soon be 2FA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook and Big Pharma exploited disease “awareness” for personalized marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763427</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763427"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visiting medical sites, patient support groups, and more feed the algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did our ancestors kill all the island megafauna?]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763424</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763424"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T15:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Study adds data to a long-running argument.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDPR in talks to use The Witcher 3 mods in official next-gen version]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-the-witcher-3s-next-gen-version-might-use-fan-made-mods</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-the-witcher-3s-next-gen-version-might-use-fan-made-mods"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T14:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ray-tracing, faster load times and more. But rather unexpectedly, it seems some of these improvements are coming from the community, as CDPR has confirmed that it is in talks with those who made mods for the 2015 game. 
Kotaku spotted that mod creator Halk Hogan, responsible for The Witcher 3 HD Reworked project, had announced he'd received an "official message from CDPR about cooperation", and that "it's very likely HDRP will be included in the official next generation update". CDPR then confirmed to Kotak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is an Edge Location in AWS? A Simple Explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/what-is-an-edge-location-in-aws-a-simple-explanation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/what-is-an-edge-location-in-aws-a-simple-explanation/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS edge locations are designed to deliver services with as less latency as possible. Learn more about edge locations, use cases, and where they might make sense for your organization.
The post What is an Edge Location in AWS? A Simple Explanation appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in AWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valheim modders are fleshing out the game's unused biomes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-valheim-modders-are-fleshing-out-the-games-unused-biomes</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-valheim-modders-are-fleshing-out-the-games-unused-biomes"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you've finished all the biomes and bosses currently available in Valheim - what now? Well, you could wait for the next official update from Iron Gate: but the next biome is quite a few updates away, so you may be waiting a while to explore the Mistlands in all their glory. 
Alternatively, you can just install a bunch of mods. Here's a video of me exploring a rejuvenated Ashlands, and running away performing a tactical retreat when I realised that the enemies are actually quite difficult. Thank goodness I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pokémon Go is finally holding a Gible Community Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-pokemon-go-is-finally-holding-a-gible-community-day</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-pokemon-go-is-finally-holding-a-gible-community-day"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T13:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gible, one of Pokémon Go's most popular and sought-after creatures, will flood the game for six hours on 6th June's Community Day. 
The much-requested event is a big announcement for the game, and by far the best Community Day candidate offered to players for several years. 
Pokémon Go players have recently criticised the calibre of creatures spotlighted in the game's Community Days. The monthly event, which began in January 2018, started by offering powerful or rare creatures such as Dratini, Larvitar and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching Cybersecurity to Children]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/teaching-cybersecurity-to-children.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/teaching-cybersecurity-to-children.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T13:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new draft of an Australian educational curriculum proposes teaching children as young as five cybersecurity:
The proposed curriculum aims to teach five-year-old children &#8212; an age at which Australian kids first attend school &#8212; not to share information such as date of birth or full names with strangers, and that they should consult parents or guardians before entering personal information online.
Six-and-seven-year-olds will be taught how to use usernames and passwords, and the pitfalls of click…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Fantasy 7 Remake Intergrade exclusive to PS5 for at least six months]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-final-fantasy-7-remake-intergrade-exclusive-to-ps5-for-at-least-six-months</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-final-fantasy-7-remake-intergrade-exclusive-to-ps5-for-at-least-six-months"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T13:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Final Fantasy 7 Remake Intergrade is exclusive to PlayStation 5 for at least six months, a new trailer for the game has confirmed.
The trailer, below, includes over three minutes of footage of Intergrade, the visually enhanced edition of the original featuring a brand new Yuffie episode.
Final Fantasy 7 Remake Intergrade comes out on 10th June, so the earliest we'd see this version of the game on other platforms - PC and Xbox, for example - would be 10th December. Or perhaps Intergrade is also coming to Pla…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM creates the world’s first 2 nm chip]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763407</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763407"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T11:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM's new 2 nm process offers transistor density similar to TSMC's next-gen 3 nm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unsolved mysteries of the Warhammer 40k universe with loremaster Dan Abnett]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762186</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762186"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T11:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best-selling author goes deep—like, real deep—on wild and crazy Warhammer questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil Village concept art reveals early plan to include fan-favourite character]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-resident-evil-village-concept-art-reveals-early-plan-to-include-fan-favourite-character</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-resident-evil-village-concept-art-reveals-early-plan-to-include-fan-favourite-character"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil Village was once planned to feature a fan-favourite character from the series, before the story changed direction. 
This character would have popped up in disguise as a plague doctor - as you'll see in the concept art, below - before finally revealing their true identity.
(There are no spoilers for Village here, but if you'd like to play through without knowing this character doesn't appear, look away now.)
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why hasn’t Waymo expanded its driverless service? Here’s my theory]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762459</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762459"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suburban ride-hailing is a lousy business to be in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conan Exiles confirmed for Xbox Game Pass]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-conan-exiles-confirmed-for-xbox-game-pass</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-conan-exiles-confirmed-for-xbox-game-pass"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conan Exiles is coming soon to Xbox Game Pass, developer Funcom has announced.
The exact date will be announced shortly, but we do know the survival game will be available to Xbox Game Pass subscribers on PC and Xbox.
Conan Exiles celebrates its three-year anniversary tomorrow, 8th May. The Isle of Siptah expansion launches proper on PC, Xbox and PlayStation on 27th May. This expansion was first released on PC in early access form in September.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gunpoint and Heat Signature developer shows off fresh gameplay of Tactical Breach Wizards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-gunpoint-and-heat-signature-developer-shows-off-fresh-gameplay-of-tactical-breach-wizards</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-gunpoint-and-heat-signature-developer-shows-off-fresh-gameplay-of-tactical-breach-wizards"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gunpoint and Heat Signature developer Tom Francis has shown off fresh gameplay of Tactical Breach Wizards.
The turn-based tactics game revolves around wizards who wear modern-day tactical gear. Breaching and clearing rooms of enemies is the bulk of the gameplay, but there's an upgrade your wizards mechanic and a conspiracy plot to fuss over, too.
The video below sees Francis narrate seven minutes of new gameplay. I think Tactical Breach Wizards looks pretty good! There is some decent combo potential here, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite now has an old-school toon Meowscles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-fortnite-now-has-an-old-school-toon-meowscles</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-fortnite-now-has-an-old-school-toon-meowscles"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite's latest creation is an old-school cartoon version of Meowscles, its fan-favourite buff cat.
Toon Meowscles is obviously inspired by the early Disney, Steamboat Willie cartoon style, with the similar bouncy limbs and the now-familiar Mickey Mouse white gloves. (I asked Donlan about this and he pointed me to the work of Oswald and Mickey animator Ub Iwerks, specifically.)
Here's his cartoon debut, which will play if you log into Fortnite today:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hardspace: Shipbreaker launches big story update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-hardspace-shipbreaker-launches-big-story-update</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-hardspace-shipbreaker-launches-big-story-update"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T09:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hardspace: Shipbreaker just got a big story update.
Blackbird Interactive's first-person spaceship laser-cutting game launched the Salvage Your Future update after almost a year in early access.
This includes new ships, a new salvaging tool, a new game mode and other gubbins. It's the most substantial change to the campaign yet, the developer said, with a complete revamp of the story and progression.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Effect: Legendary Edition has an option for those original, terrible Mako controls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-mass-effect-legendary-edition-has-an-option-for-those-original-terrible-mako-controls</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-mass-effect-legendary-edition-has-an-option-for-those-original-terrible-mako-controls"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T09:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The original Mass Effect's terrible Mako truck controls have been preserved as an option in the upcoming Mass Effect: Legendary Edition, developer BioWare has said. 
Improvements to the Mako are among one of many gameplay improvements added to the aging Mass Effect 1 as part of the Legendary Edition. These are things BioWare has been trumpeting for a while.
Now, via PC Gamer, we've heard the authentic experience is still in there - if you really want to recapture how bad it was.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost Judgment leaks on PlayStation Store ahead of official reveal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-lost-judgment-leaks-on-playstation-store-ahead-of-official-reveal</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-lost-judgment-leaks-on-playstation-store-ahead-of-official-reveal"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lost Judgment has leaked on the PlayStation Store ahead of its official reveal later today.
VGC reports Japanese Twitter user @kenichiro_taka spotted Lost Judgment on the PlayStation 5 store, but pulled their tweet as it began to spread.
The store page listed Lost Judgment as coming out on 24th September in Japan.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vaccinated]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2460/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2460/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Humble Bundle reinstating charitable donation sliders following outcry over removal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-humble-bundle-reinstating-charitable-donation-sliders-following-outcry-over-removal</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-humble-bundle-reinstating-charitable-donation-sliders-following-outcry-over-removal"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T21:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humble Bundle has reversed its controversial decision to remove charity sliders from its bundle pages - a move that would have significantly reduced the percentage of payments players were able to donate charity.
Humble Bundle has long permitted customers to choose how they want to split their bundle payments between a charity, a game's publisher, and Humble Bundle itself, even allowing them to donate 100% of their money to charity if they so choose - a split determined by shifting a number of sliders.
It's…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What cats’ love of boxes and squares can tell us about their visual perception]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762974</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762974"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T21:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Vision has evolved to answer questions having to do with boundaries and contours."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World of Warcraft: Burning Crusade Classic arrives in June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-world-of-warcraft-burning-crusade-classic-arrives-in-june</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-world-of-warcraft-burning-crusade-classic-arrives-in-june"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World of Warcraft Classic, Blizzard's retro version of the long-running MMO, will be expanding to include the game's first expansion, The Burning Crusade, on 1st June at 11pm BST/6pm PT.
As you'd expect, The Burning Crusade's arrival will see World of Warcraft Classic receive all the features delivered in the original expansion, meaning the introduction of Blood Elves and the Draenei as playable races, flying mounts, an increased level cap of 70, arena PvP, and more.
WoW's map will also expand to include ne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9,000 fliers may have had reused swabs jammed up their noses in Indonesia]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763266</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763266"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T20:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five workers were arrested for washing and reusing cotton swabs for testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paramount+ hits 36 million subscribers, will stream sci-fi movie Infinite]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763196</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763196"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T19:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streaming service commits to one original movie every week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World of Warcraft: Burning Crusade re-returns on June 1, requires “cloning”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763224</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763224"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T19:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're already in WoW Classic, you have a decision to make starting May 18.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s best tech deals: New iPad Pro, Amazon devices, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763057</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763057"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T19:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealmaster also has deals on wireless headphones and lots of video games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest ISPs paid for 8.5 million fake FCC comments opposing net neutrality]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763191</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763191"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T18:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ISP-funded astroturfing used millions of real names and faked consent records.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sea level rise uncertainties: Why all eyes are on Antarctica]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763103</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763103"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T18:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Latest models project a bumpy road with big risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sci-fi horror spruce-up Observer: System Redux comes to PS4 and Xbox One in July]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-sci-fi-horror-spruce-up-observer-system-redux-heading-to-ps4-and-xbox-one</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-sci-fi-horror-spruce-up-observer-system-redux-heading-to-ps4-and-xbox-one"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T18:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Observer: System Redux, the enhanced edition of Layers of Fear developer Bloober Team's acclaimed sci-fi horror, will be making the leap to PlayStation 4 and Xbox One on 16th July.
The original Observer, released back in 2017, tells the story of detective Daniel Lazarski (voiced by the late Rutger Hauer) as he investigates a dilapidated Kraków apartment block, circa 2084, in search of his estranged son. What follows is a compelling blend of dystopian investigation adventure and hallucinatory nightmare as La…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Assistant is now a Google messaging service]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763075</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763075"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T17:59:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Broadcast" now works on speakers, displays, and phones for your whole family.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers peek at proprietary data of US particle physics lab Fermilab]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763117</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763117"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T17:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exposed systems paved way for researchers to access code, messages, passwords, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metro Exodus heading to PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S in enhanced form this June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-metro-exodus-heading-to-playstation-5-and-xbox-series-x-s-in-enhanced-form-this-june</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-metro-exodus-heading-to-playstation-5-and-xbox-series-x-s-in-enhanced-form-this-june"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T17:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metro Exodus, the acclaimed third instalment in developer 4A Games horror-tinged first-person shooter series, will be making its way to Xbox Series X/S and PlayStation 5 on 18th June.
Exodus once again catapults players into a post-apocalyptic Russia - a predominantly subterranean world of survival inspired by the novels of celebrated author Dmitry Glukhovsky - this time adding open-ended overground sandbox environments to complement the series' traditionally linear slaying and scavenging. Eurogamer liked i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s carbon pollution now surpasses all developed countries combined]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763109</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763109"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T16:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As China's coal-reliant economy has boomed, so, too, have its emissions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stranger Things hints at return of Eleven’s “Papa” in new teaser]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763089</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763089"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T16:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matthew Modine, who played Dr. Martin Brenner, was spotted on set earlier this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Earliest known burial in Africa is that of a small, fragile child]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763016</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763016"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T16:20:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early humans in Kenya buried a dead child with tremendous care 78,000 years ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft announces The Division free-to-play spin-off Heartland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-ubisoft-announces-the-division-free-to-play-spin-off-heartland</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-ubisoft-announces-the-division-free-to-play-spin-off-heartland"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft has announced Tom Clancy's The Division: Heartland, a standalone free-to-play game due for PC, PlayStation and Xbox sometime vaguely in "2021-22".
It's being developed by Ghost Recon studio Red Storm Entertainment, and you can already register your interest in joining playtests. 
Another The Division game is also in development for mobile, Ubisoft said, while its previously-announced The Division film starring Jessica Chastain and Jake Gyllenhaal, in development with Netflix, is also still on the ca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20 year-old action RPG Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance re-releases on console tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-20-year-old-action-rpg-baldurs-gate-dark-alliance-rereleases-on-console-tomorrow</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-20-year-old-action-rpg-baldurs-gate-dark-alliance-rereleases-on-console-tomorrow"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T15:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance re-releases on all consoles tomorrow - 20 years after it came out.
The action RPG launches on Xbox One, Xbox Series X and S, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, and Nintendo Switch on 7th May with up to 4K support. There's also support for local two-player co-op. It costs £29.99. IGN has an exclusive on the trailer, below:
This re-release is the work of Interplay Entertainment, which is still knocking about after all these years. But it's not the same company that developed the origin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rambo is coming to Call of Duty: Warzone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-rambo-is-coming-to-call-of-duty-warzone</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-rambo-is-coming-to-call-of-duty-warzone"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T14:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Warzone is getting a surprise guest character: Rambo.
The official Call of Duty Twitter account published a not so subtle tease for the iconic soldier joining Warzone, referencing "SURVIVORJOHN#1009062".
And then:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo warns global chip shortage to hit Switch production]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763073</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763073"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T13:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo follows rival Sony in saying supply crunch threatens console sales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASCAR ditches decades of tradition for its Next Gen race car]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763026</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763026"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T13:13:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cup cars will run centerlock wheels, sequential transmissions, and flat floors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assassin's Creed Valhalla datamine points to mythical realm of Muspelheim]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-assassins-creed-valhalla-datamine-points-to-further-expansion-plans</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-assassins-creed-valhalla-datamine-points-to-further-expansion-plans"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mention of Muspelheim as a DLC location, spotted by reliable Assassin's Creed leaker J0nathan, lines up with early concept art for the hellish world released by Ubisoft and made for Valhalla - even though the realm does not feature in the final game. 
In Norse mythology, Muspelheim is home to fire giants and the demonic Surtur. (If you've watched Thor Ragnarok, Surtur is the big flaming guy with the horny helmet.) 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Story of Colossus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/the-story-of-colossus.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/the-story-of-colossus.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nice video of a talk by Chris Shore on the history of Colossus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World waits to see where a Chinese booster will come down]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762950</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762950"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T10:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 20-ton booster is big enough that some parts are likely to reach the ground.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft confirms it's never turned a profit on sale of Xbox consoles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-microsoft-confirms-its-never-made-profit-from-sale-of-an-xbox-console</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-microsoft-confirms-its-never-made-profit-from-sale-of-an-xbox-console"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T10:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Epic Games v Apple trial is continuing to surface interesting titbits of information about the inner workings of the games industry, and the latest is that Microsoft has never made profit from the sale of console hardware. This may not be the most surprising news of all time, given consoles are in the games industry have traditionally been sold at a loss - but you rarely hear companies admit this out loud. 
Xbox vice president Lori Wright was called in as a third-party witness for the trial, where she w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fix for critical Qualcomm chip flaw is making its way to Android devices]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763019</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763019"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T10:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Higher-end devices made by Google, Samsung, LG, Xiaomi, and OnePlus are affected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Effect deluxe edition comics, art books, soundtracks made free]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-mass-effect-deluxe-edition-comics-art-books-soundtracks-made-free</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-mass-effect-deluxe-edition-comics-art-books-soundtracks-made-free"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of Mass Effect: Legendary Edition's launch on 14th May, BioWare has made a treasure trove of bonus content available to freely download. 
This includes bits and pieces previously packed in the deluxe edition versions of Mass Effect 2 and 3, such as digital art books for each game and the first issues of both Mass Effect: Redemption and Mass Effect: Invasion comic books.
An 88-track soundtrack for the entire trilogy is also featured, including a new track for the Legendary Edition titled Resynthesis. 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Returnal patch pulled after corrupting saves]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-returnal-patch-pulled-after-corrupting-saves</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-returnal-patch-pulled-after-corrupting-saves"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T09:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patch 1.3.3 for PlayStation 5-exclusive roguelite Returnal was pulled by developer Housemarque last night after it was found to have corrupted saves.
Housemarque later released a follow-up patch (1.3.4) that fixed the save-related issues caused by the previous update, but the developer said those affected by the previous update (you'd get the CE-100028-1 error popup) would have to re-download the game.
"Our sincerest apologies," Housemarque tweeted.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch passes 84m sold, as company records record profits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-nintendo-switch-passes-84m-sold-as-company-records-record-profits</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-06-nintendo-switch-passes-84m-sold-as-company-records-record-profits"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T08:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo's 2020 was one for the record books. The company earned its best ever operating profit of $6bn, and its second-best year of revenue, at $16.6bn.
Nintendo Switch now sits at 84.59m consoles and 587.1m games sold. (By comparison, Wii, Nintendo's top-selling home console, shifted 101m consoles. Wii U struggled to hit 14m.)
But Nintendo also expects a decline in profit and revenue for the current financial year, ending 31st March 2022, unable to match the same level of pandemic-boosted sales seen by Sw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Severe vulnerabilities in Dell firmware update driver found and fixed]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762922</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762922"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T23:39:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dell firmware update driver 2.3 can be exploited to gain kernel-level privilege.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter’s latest robo-nag will flag “harmful” language before you post]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762846</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762846"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T23:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follows Twitter's effort to make you read the news before you share it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SpaceX successfully lands a Starship test flight]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762970</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762970"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T22:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given that it's meant to be the basis for a lunar lander, landing it is good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google tries to resurrect Android tablets with “Entertainment Space”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762752</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762752"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T22:29:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google brings a TV-like media-aggregation interface to tablet home screens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden backs plan to accelerate vaccine production by waiving patents]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762850</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762850"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T22:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts disagree on whether patents are a bottleneck for vaccine production.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Effect Legendary Edition's switchable frame rate and resolution options detailed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-bioware-details-mass-effect-legendary-editions-switchable-frame-rate-and-resolution-options</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-bioware-details-mass-effect-legendary-editions-switchable-frame-rate-and-resolution-options"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Effect Legendary Edition - which bundles up remastered versions of BioWare's beloved space opera trilogy - is a little over a week away from release, and, ahead of its arrival, the studio has detailed frame rate and resolution options for all platforms.
As revealed in BioWare's latest blog post, players on console will have the option to switch between two separate gameplay modes - Favour Quality and Favour Framerate - at any time.
Both are fairly self explanatory, with Favour Quality designed to achie…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At trial, Epic and Apple squeeze Microsoft over Xbox, xCloud restrictions]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762866</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762866"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T21:35:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questions over Xbox restrictions, xCloud's iOS struggles serve as comparison points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study: Using Apple’s Night Shift to improve your sleep? Don’t bother]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762865</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762865"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T21:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The test was done with iPhones, but many gadgets have a similar feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data leak makes Peloton’s Horrible, No-Good, Really Bad Day even worse]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762827</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762827"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T20:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Faulty API let anyone grab users’ private data, including weight and gender.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Appeals court allows parents to sue Snap over 100 mph car crash]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762775</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762775"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T20:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The parents argued a Snapchat filter encouraged their boys to drive recklessly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back 4 Blood details its deck-building card system in latest trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-back-4-blood-details-its-deck-building-card-system-in-new-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-back-4-blood-details-its-deck-building-card-system-in-new-trailer"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T20:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back 4 Blood isn't shying away from comparisons to co-operative zombie FPS classic Left 4 Dead - developer Turtle Rock Studios is responsible for both, after all - but the team is aiming to deliver more than a carbon copy of its earlier game. And one of its innovations comes in the form of an intriguing deck-building card system, which it's now detailed in its latest trailer.
Borrowing one of Left 4 Dead's most innovative features - an AI-driven Game Director - Back 4 Blood works behind the scenes to monito…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD’s upcoming flagship GPUs should be 3x faster than RX 6900XT]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762822</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762822"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T20:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the rumors can be believed, GPU performance will triple sometime next year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chip shortage continues, US asks Taiwan to prioritize automakers]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762801</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762801"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T18:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ford, Renault, and Stellantis warn that Q2 production will be heavily affected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blue Origin isn’t pricing its first launch seat—it’s auctioning it]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762790</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762790"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T18:22:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeff Bezos' rocket co. targets July 20 for its first crewed launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mighty morphin’ flat-packed pasta takes on 3D shapes as it cooks]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762605</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762605"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T18:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New approach could lead to more sustainable packaging, transportation, and storage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hands-on: We hammered Plume’s newest Superpod design with all-new Wi-Fi testing]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762145</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762145"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you can stomach a subscription, Plume’s Superpods offer unmatched performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 1 + 2 gets June release date on Switch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-tony-hawks-pro-skater-1-2-gets-june-release-date-on-switch</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-tony-hawks-pro-skater-1-2-gets-june-release-date-on-switch"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T17:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 1 + 2, last year's well-received remaster of the skateboarding classics, will finally be making its way to Switch on 25th June.
Something of a bittersweet last hoorah for Skylanders studio Vicarious Visions - who were merged into Blizzard earlier this year - Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 1 + 2 brings together characters and levels, all suitably spruced up for the modern era, from the first two Tony Hawk's games.
Eurogamer's Martin Robinson loved Vicarious Visions' masterful reworking of the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Returnal has some handy debug cheat codes if you connect a keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-returnal-has-some-handy-debug-cheat-codes-if-you-connect-a-keyboard</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-returnal-has-some-handy-debug-cheat-codes-if-you-connect-a-keyboard"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T16:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Returnal, as you won't need telling if you've been  braving its trials this week, isn't an easy game. But it turns out a little bit of help (albeit not of the entirely above-board kind) has been left lingering within the game in the form of some newly discovered debug cheat codes - just don't expect them to stick around for very much longer.
As discovered by YouTuber TheRandomizer - and elaborated upon elsewhere - players can slightly ease their progress through Housemarque's tough-as-nails sci-fi shooter b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube’s TikTok clone, “Shorts,” is out of beta and open for all US users]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762710</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762710"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T16:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shorts are coming, and the feature is getting a premium spot in the YouTube app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peloton recalls treadmills after 6-year-old’s death, CEO admits “mistake”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762736</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762736"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T16:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consumer Product Safety Commission said recall decision took “intense negotiation."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plug in a PS5 keyboard to access Returnal’s hidden “debug mode” codes]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762732</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762732"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T15:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But some players fear Housemarque may patch out the codes soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Spectre-Like Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/new-spectre-like-attacks.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/new-spectre-like-attacks.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T15:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There&#8217;s new research that demonstrates security vulnerabilities in all of the AMD and Intel chips with micro-op caches, including the ones that were specifically engineered to be resistant to the Spectre/Meltdown attacks of three years ago.
Details:
The new line of attacks exploits the micro-op cache: an on-chip structure that speeds up computing by storing simple commands and allowing the processor to fetch them quickly and early in the speculative execution process, as the team explains in a writeup…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stadia staff join Jade Raymond at Haven Studios]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-stadia-staff-join-jade-raymond-at-haven-studios</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-stadia-staff-join-jade-raymond-at-haven-studios"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T15:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At least half a dozen more Google Stadia staff have found a new home at Haven Studios, the developer set up by former Stadia games exec Jade Raymond. 
The list notably includes Corey May, who like Raymond once helped define the early Assassin's Creed series. May served as scriptwriter, lead writer and then narrative director on numerous Assassin's Creed games over the course of a 12-year span, and worked with Raymond on the series' first couple of entries.
At Stadia, May served as its head of creative servi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starlink can serve 500,000 users easily, several million “more of a challenge”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762714</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762714"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T15:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "only limitation is high density of users in urban areas," Musk said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Total War: Warhammer 3 gameplay details and images leak ahead of big reveal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-total-war-warhammer-3-gameplay-details-and-images-leak-ahead-of-big-reveal</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-total-war-warhammer-3-gameplay-details-and-images-leak-ahead-of-big-reveal"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T15:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Total War: Warhammer 3 gameplay details and images have leaked online ahead of the game's big reveal.
The hotly-anticipated strategy game's official gameplay reveal is set for 5pm on 13th May, but someone posted screenshots and details to 4chan - before they were deleted.
That didn't stop redditor Hollownerox from compiling the information, and for the images to make their way to reddit.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil Village review: Apparently, good horror takes more than a village]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762185</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762185"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T15:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We had high hopes for "RE4 + RE7," but pumped-up combat isn't enough for this sequel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamescom 2021 ditches hybrid plan, goes all digital]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-gamescom-2021-ditches-hybrid-plan-goes-all-digital</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-gamescom-2021-ditches-hybrid-plan-goes-all-digital"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T14:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The people behind Gamescom have ditched plans for a hybrid event and announced its 2021 show will be digital only.
Gamescom will now be online and free for all, the German Games Industry Association announced.
"This decision was made after extensive discussions with partners and exhibitors," Gamescom said. "Thus, the organisers take into account the current situation, in which too many companies are unable to participate in physical events this year due to the still difficult development. In this way, they …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Portals Are an Anti-Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/developer-portals-are-an-anti-pattern/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/developer-portals-are-an-anti-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer portals can be used to enforce standardization and to enable multi-cloud use cases. But they also have some serious issues and should be avoided in most cases. 
The post Developer Portals Are an Anti-Pattern appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in AWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla loses huge customer for emissions credits in Europe and the US]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762701</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762701"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T14:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stellantis paid Tesla $2.4 billion for credits between 2019-2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook Oversight Board upholds ban on former President Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762657</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762657"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T13:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the ban was permissible, its open-ended nature was not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lady Dimitrescu as Thomas the Tank Engine is the headline act in Resident Evil Village's burgeoning mod scene]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-lady-dimitrescu-as-thomas-the-tank-engine-is-the-headline-act-in-resident-evil-villages-burgeoning-mod-scene</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-lady-dimitrescu-as-thomas-the-tank-engine-is-the-headline-act-in-resident-evil-villages-burgeoning-mod-scene"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T12:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil Village isn't out yet, but its mod scene has already kicked off.
NexusMods' Village page is filling up quick with eye-catching mods for Village's ongoing demo, and, yes, the one I'm going to pull out is about Lady Dimitrescu.
The Count Theodora mod, created by Crazy Potato, replaces Lady Dimitrescu's head with Thomas the Tank Engine. It is as nightmarish as it sounds. Check out Crazy Potato's video, below, to see it in action:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AirTag review: They work great—maybe a little too great]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1760614</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1760614"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T12:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple made the most privacy-friendly tracker, but that's not saying much.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends' Legacy season got off to a popular but rocky start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-apex-legends-legacy-season-got-off-to-a-popular-but-rocky-start</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-apex-legends-legacy-season-got-off-to-a-popular-but-rocky-start"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T11:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The much-anticipated Legacy update for Apex Legends arrived last night, and while Apex saw record numbers of Steam players and a huge audience on Twitch, it wasn't exactly a smooth launch. The high demand meant many couldn't get into matches, while players also reported problems with the in-game menus and marketplace. 
Legacy went live at 6pm UK last night, but as you can see from the Twitter thread by Respawn below, it took about eight hours for Respawn to iron out all the problems with the servers. Follow…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of Returnal's first big patch, Housemarque warns players to turn PS5 auto-updates off "to keep your run"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-ahead-of-returnals-first-big-patch-housemarque-warns-players-to-turn-ps5-auto-update-off-to-keep-your-run</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-ahead-of-returnals-first-big-patch-housemarque-warns-players-to-turn-ps5-auto-update-off-to-keep-your-run"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Housemarque has warned Returnal players to turn auto-update off on their PlayStation 5 ahead of the release of the game's first big patch tonight.
The developer tweeted to say Returnal players should to this "to keep your run".
The warning comes amid calls from some Returnal players for Housemarque to add a save and quit option to the roguelite.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detective Pikachu star pours cold water on those sequel plans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-detective-pikachu-star-pours-water-on-those-sequel-plans</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-detective-pikachu-star-pours-water-on-those-sequel-plans"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plans for a Detective Pikachu film sequel were in the works following the successful launch of Pokémon's live-action big screen debut but now, on the film's second anniversary, we have our clearest indicator yet we won't see a Detective Pikachu 2 after all. 
Here is the film's star (no, not Pikachu) Justice Smith, being asked if he'd still be up for it:
"I would love to participate in Detective Pikachu 2. I don't know if it's going to happen," Smith told Inverse. "I think we have to just kind of bury our ho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Agricomb” is the perfect tool for measuring gases from cow burps]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1753395</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1753395"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More precise measurements could help boost yields and enable design of cleaner farms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blizzard continues to lose millions of players, but new games are coming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-blizzard-continues-to-lose-millions-of-players-but-new-games-are-coming</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-blizzard-continues-to-lose-millions-of-players-but-new-games-are-coming"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blizzard has lost another two million players across its titles.
Reporting its latest financial results, Activision Blizzard said Blizzard specifically saw 27m monthly active users in the first quarter of 2021.
As MassivelyOP points out, that's down from the 29m MAUs Blizzard had in the previous quarter. In fact, Blizzard has lost almost 29 percent of its overall active player base in three years.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Games and Xbox discussed dropping Xbox Live Gold requirement for F2P games last year, emails reveal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-epic-games-and-xbox-discussed-dropping-xbox-live-gold-requirement-for-f2p-games-last-year-emails-reveal</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-epic-games-and-xbox-discussed-dropping-xbox-live-gold-requirement-for-f2p-games-last-year-emails-reveal"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Games head honcho Tim Sweeney petitioned Xbox boss Phil Spencer to ditch Microsoft's Xbox Live Gold requirement for free-to-play games last summer. 
The exchange is one of several revealing, private emails sent between company top brass made public as part of the ongoing Apple vs Epic Games trial. 
Last August, Sweeney emailed Spencer to suggest Microsoft drop the F2P Xbox Live Gold firewall and time it alongside Fortnite's Marvel season launch and permanent V-Bucks price-drop.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Activision commits to autumn 2021 for Sledgehammer's WW2 Call of Duty game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-activision-commits-to-autumn-2021-for-sledgehammers-ww2-call-of-duty-game</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-05-activision-commits-to-autumn-2021-for-sledgehammers-ww2-call-of-duty-game"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T09:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Activision has committed to an autumn 2021 release for this year's Call of Duty game.
During a financial call last night, Activision confirmed for the first time that Call of Duty WW2 developer Sledgehammer is leading development of this year's title.
Eurogamer has already reported Sledgehammer is making Call of Duty WW2 Vanguard.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 2020]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2459/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2459/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden shifts strategy as national vaccination rate continues to slow]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762571</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762571"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T22:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vaccinations have been steadily declining since mid-April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA has selected its deep space hardware—now comes the fun part]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762028</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762028"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T21:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["This isn’t a dream any more."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix IT exec forced employees to use products from vendors that bribed him]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762444</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762444"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T20:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jury finds ex-Netflix VP guilty of awarding tech contracts in exchange for bribes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new abnormal is warming up the US government’s new climate norms]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762457</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762457"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T20:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US's expected weather are based on a 30-year average, updated once a decade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Witcher 3 director leaves CD Projekt following investigation into workplace bullying]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-witcher-3-director-leaves-cd-projekt-following-investigation-into-workplace-bullying</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-witcher-3-director-leaves-cd-projekt-following-investigation-into-workplace-bullying"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T20:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Konrad Tomaszkiewicz, who served as game director on CD Projekt's acclaimed The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt, has resigned from the company following an investigation into workplace bullying.
As reported by Bloomberg, Tomaszkiewicz had been the focus of a months-long investigation into allegations of bullying at CD Projekt.
Despite the investigation ultimately finding him not guilty, Tomaszkiewicz told co-workers in an email announcing his resignation, as seen by Bloomberg, "a lot of people are feeling fear, stress…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic thinks EGS could make up 35-50% of the PC gaming market by 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762403</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762403"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T20:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Epic v. Apple gives us our deepest look yet into the economics of Epic's storefront.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Spectre attack once again sends Intel and AMD scrambling for a fix]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762393</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762393"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T19:07:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new transient execution variant is the first exploit micro-ops caches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s best deals: $40 Nintendo Switch games, Kindle Paperwhite, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762201</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762201"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T18:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealmaster also has deals on true wireless earbuds and Garmin running watches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frontier exits bankruptcy, claims it will double fiber-to-the-home footprint]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762320</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762320"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T17:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontier plans 3 million new fiber lines—but 8M others would be stuck on copper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16-bit sci-fi classic Flashback is getting (another) sequel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-16-bit-sci-fi-classic-flashback-is-getting-another-sequel</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-16-bit-sci-fi-classic-flashback-is-getting-another-sequel"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Microids has revealed it's working on a direct sequel to 16-bit sci-fi classic Flashback - something of a surprising announcement, given it already has one.
The original Flashback, released by Delphine Software in 1992, followed the far-flung future adventures of agent Conrad B. Hart on the trail of shapeshifting aliens attempting to infiltrate human society - an investigation that, much like Delphine's earlier Another World, took the form of a platform-puzzler, complete with strikingly cinematic …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: Shadow and Bone is a worthy adaptation of the Grishaverse novels]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1760925</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1760925"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T17:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Cursed had a love child with The X-Men—who was then raised by Doctor Zhivago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers raise bats in helium-rich air to check how they sense sound]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762292</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762292"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T16:45:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bats seem to have an innate sense of the speed of sound—and can't adjust it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye again, Flash—Microsoft makes removal from Windows 10 mandatory]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762277</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762277"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T16:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows "Update for Removal of Adobe Flash Player" becomes mandatory this July.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the next Patent Office director could shape the patent system]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1761779</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1761779"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T16:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Obama created "death squads" for bad patents—Trump's nominees curtailed them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4,700 Amazon employees had unauthorized access to private seller data]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762278</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762278"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T15:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shoddy security allowed various employees to use info to their advantage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[League of Legends Netflix series launches this autumn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-league-of-legends-netflix-series-launches-this-autumn</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-league-of-legends-netflix-series-launches-this-autumn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T15:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arcane, the animated League of Legends spin-off series, debuts on Netflix this autumn. 
This is the first League of Legends show, though the latest of many Netflix video game adaptations. 
The streaming service describes it as an "event series", which suggests it won't run for multiple seasons like Castlevania. Here's a quick glimpse:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stadia’s VP and head of product leaves Google]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762224</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762224"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:47:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's embattled Stadia division loses one of its highest-profile executives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Remotely Hacked from a Drone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/tesla-remotely-hacked-from-a-drone.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/tesla-remotely-hacked-from-a-drone.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:41:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an impressive hack:
Security researchers Ralf-Philipp Weinmann of Kunnamon, Inc. and Benedikt Schmotzle of Comsecuris GmbH have found remote zero-click security vulnerabilities in an open-source software component (ConnMan) used in Tesla automobiles that allowed them to compromise parked cars and control their infotainment systems over WiFi. It would be possible for an attacker to unlock the doors and trunk, change seat positions, both steering and acceleration modes &#8212; in short, pretty much wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite planned basketball, survival simulator modes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-fortnite-planned-basketball-survival-simulator-modes</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-fortnite-planned-basketball-survival-simulator-modes"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The details are the latest to come to light as part of documentation revealed in the Epic Games vs Apple courtroom drama, and which fit into previous leaks. 
Plans for an NBA tie-in mode, including a LeBron James skin, are detailing an internal report dated June 2020 - though leaks suggest these are still coming.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft gives FPS boost to 74 more Xbox Series X/S games]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-another-74-xbox-series-x-s-games-get-fps-boost</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-another-74-xbox-series-x-s-games-get-fps-boost"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has announced that another 74 games have been given the FPS Boost treatment, bringing the total number of boosted titles up to 97. 
The new set of 74 games includes several Assassin's Creed titles (including Unity, The Ezio Collection, Rogue Remastered and 3 Remastered), three Far Cry games (5, New Dawn and Primal), and a bunch of Lego games such as Batman 3, Jurassic World, Marvel Super Heroes and Star Wars: The Force Awakens. Oh, and also Alien Isolation at 60fps. You can find the full list of b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starship flight attempt for Tuesday afternoon is scrubbed [Updated]]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762199</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762199"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After four failures, SpaceX is really hoping to stick the landing this time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Porsche and Penske: Two of racing’s most famous names join forces again]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762203</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762203"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pair will run teams in WEC and IMSA, and there will be customer cars, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite earned $9bn in two years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-fortnite-earned-usd9bn-in-two-years</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-fortnite-earned-usd9bn-in-two-years"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T13:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite generated $9.1bn in revenue across 2018 and 2019, new documents from the ongoing Epic vs Apple lawsuit have shown.
This breaks down to $5.4bn in 2018 and a further $3.7bn in 2019, as reported in Epic's internal financial presentation dated January 2020 (thanks, The Verge).
In terms of how that all translates into profit, Epic has previously said it made $5.5bn overall profit across those two years, and a further whopping $5.1bn profit just in 2020. This is profit across the whole of the business, i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Martian’s Andy Weir is back to form with Project Hail Mary]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1761902</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1761902"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some quick and spoiler-free thoughts on the new book, out today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony working on Discord integration for PlayStation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-discord-playstation-integration</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-discord-playstation-integration"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to team up with friends on both PlayStation and PC, there's good news for you, as Sony has announced a partnership with Discord to put the voice chat system on PlayStation Network. 
In a blog post, Sony Interactive Entertainment president Jim Ryan announced that Sony is already working on integrating the service into PlayStation Network, and plans on bringing "the Discord and PlayStation experiences closer together on console and mobile starting early next year". Sony has also made a minority in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Document reveals how much Epic paid for each free game on its store up to Sep 2019]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-document-reveals-how-much-epic-paid-for-each-free-game-on-its-store-up-to-sep-2019</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-document-reveals-how-much-epic-paid-for-each-free-game-on-its-store-up-to-sep-2019"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T11:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Epic versus Apple trial keeps on giving: this time we know how much Epic paid on a per title basis for the free games released during the first nine months of the Epic Games Store's life.
A document spotted and tweeted by GameDiscoverCo founder Simon Carless lists all the free games released on the Epic Games Store in the nine months to September 2019 - and how much Epic paid for each of them.
The list tells us, for example, Epic paid $1.4m to get Subnautica as a free game. Team Meat's wonderful Super M…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Epic v Apple trial opened with a public phone line, and chaos ensued]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-the-epic-v-apple-trial-started-with-a-bunch-of-people-yelling-free-fortnite</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-the-epic-v-apple-trial-started-with-a-bunch-of-people-yelling-free-fortnite"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T10:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a bunch of juicy information coming out of the Epic Games v Apple trial right now, with news that Sony charges publishers cross-play fees being just one of the main headlines. But before anyone had the chance to hear this, the trial started with a rather chaotic conference call. A public line for the trial allowed anyone to dial in to listen to the proceedings - and this was quickly flooded by rowdy Fortnite fans. 
As reported by The Verge, the phone line saw more than 200 people dial in to listen t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite planned Metroid crossover, Ariana and Lady Gaga concerts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-fortnite-planned-metroid-crossover-ariana-and-lady-gaga-concerts</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-fortnite-planned-metroid-crossover-ariana-and-lady-gaga-concerts"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T10:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One particularly-revealing document dating from June 2020 looks ahead to Fortnite's now-concluded bounty hunter season, which ran from December 2020 to March this year, and reveals it was once planned to include Nintendo's Samus alongside Xbox's Master Chief and PlayStation's Kratos.
Many fans had wondered whether Nintendo would join in Fortnite's new series of Gaming Legends characters, which now also includes Aloy from Horizon Zero Dawn, Ryu and Chun-Li from Street Fighter, as well as Lara Croft. Epic's d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic's "fully loaded" Borderlands 3 deal cost $146m, secured six months of PC exclusivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-epics-fully-loaded-borderlands-3-deal-cost-usd146m-for-six-months-of-pc-exclusivity</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-epics-fully-loaded-borderlands-3-deal-cost-usd146m-for-six-months-of-pc-exclusivity"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T09:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We know Epic is burning through hundreds of millions of dollars trying to get its store off the ground. Thanks to its ongoing trial with Apple, we now know just how much is changing hands for some of the big games.
A document released as part of the trial, tweeted by GameDiscoverCo founder Simon Carless, shows Epic paid $146m in advances to secure six months of PC Borderlands 3 exclusivity from 13 September 2019.
The eye-catching deal ensured Gearbox's shooter did not launch on rival PC platform Steam until…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic boss says Sony charges publishers a cross-play fee in certain circumstances]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-epic-boss-says-sony-charges-publishers-a-cross-play-fee-in-certain-circumstances</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-epic-boss-says-sony-charges-publishers-a-cross-play-fee-in-certain-circumstances"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T08:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Epic boss Tim Sweeney has said Sony requires compensation from publishers for cross-play in certain circumstances.
In explosive comments made during the opening day of the Epic vs Apple trial, Sweeney said Epic agreed to the fees in order to get crossplay going in Fortnite.
"In certain circumstances Epic will have to pay additional revenue to Sony," Sweeney said, as reported by The Verge.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Pokémon Snap sold nearly triple the boxed copies of Returnal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-new-pokemon-snap-sold-nearly-triple-the-boxed-copies-of-returnal</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-04-new-pokemon-snap-sold-nearly-triple-the-boxed-copies-of-returnal"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T08:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pokémon photography game was top of this week's GfK Chart-Track physical games chart, while the PlayStation 5 exclusive Returnal was second.
Even looking at the raw money made, New Pokémon Snap (RRP £44.99) made double what Returnal (RRP £70) did.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDA reportedly plans to authorize Pfizer’s COVID vaccine for teens 12-15 in days]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762150</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762150"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T23:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pfizer previously reported the vaccine was safe and effective in adolescents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic vs. Apple opening arguments suggest a bitter battle over iOS’ future]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762079</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762079"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T23:10:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Epic says it's "suing for change." Apple says Epic "just doesn't want to pay."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another Google AI leader has defected to Apple]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762074</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762074"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T21:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He will work under John Giannandrea, who also left Google for Apple.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Technica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying the Person Behind Bitcoin Fog]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/identifying-the-person-behind-bitcoin-fog.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/identifying-the-person-behind-bitcoin-fog.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T14:36:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The person behind the Bitcoin Fog was identified and arrested. Bitcoin Fog was an anonymization service: for a fee, it mixed a bunch of people&#8217;s bitcoins up so that it was hard to figure out where any individual coins came from. It ran for ten years.
Identifying the person behind Bitcoin Fog serves as an illustrative example of how hard it is to be anonymous online in the face of a competent police investigation:
Most remarkable, however, is the IRS&#8217;s account of tracking down Sterlingov using th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bubble Wrap]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2458/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2458/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Skyrim Grandma is now a Skyrim follower - thanks to a mod]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-02-the-skyrim-grandma-is-now-a-skyrim-follower-thanks-to-a-mod</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-02-the-skyrim-grandma-is-now-a-skyrim-follower-thanks-to-a-mod"/>
        <updated>2021-05-02T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shirley Curry, better known as the Skyrim Grandma, is now available as a follower in Skyrim via a mod.
Curry is available as a follower via the Shirley - A Skyrim Follower mod, which is now available to download from Nexus Mods for Skyrim Special Edition and Skyrim VR, and from Bethesda.net for PC and Xbox.
"She'll join you on your adventures, but don't expect her to simply carry your burdens!" reads the official blurb.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil Village demo goes live on all platforms - and yes, PC users have already worked out how to reset the timer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-02-resident-evil-village-demo-goes-live-on-all-platforms-and-yes-pc-users-have-already-worked-out-how-to-reset-the-timer</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-02-resident-evil-village-demo-goes-live-on-all-platforms-and-yes-pc-users-have-already-worked-out-how-to-reset-the-timer"/>
        <updated>2021-05-02T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Resident Evil Village demo is now live across all platforms.
The demo is available to play on PlayStation 5, PlayStation 4, Xbox Series X and S, Xbox One, Steam and Stadia.
This demo was originally supposed to be available for just 24 hours, but Capcom extended it to last until the end of the week.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internal Microsoft document reveals plan to slash cut on Xbox game sales, too]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-02-confidential-microsoft-document-reveals-plan-to-slash-its-cut-on-xbox-games-too</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-02-confidential-microsoft-document-reveals-plan-to-slash-its-cut-on-xbox-games-too"/>
        <updated>2021-05-02T11:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Microsoft has said it will not change its revenue share from Xbox game sales, after an internal document suggested it had planned to do just that.
In a statement issued to The Verge, Microsoft said: "We will not be updating the revenue split for console publishers."
It looks like Microsoft had a change of heart from just a few months ago, when the internal document was put together. More on that in the story below.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Six blurry seconds of Elden Ring leak online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-02-six-blurry-seconds-of-elden-ring-leak-online</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-02-six-blurry-seconds-of-elden-ring-leak-online"/>
        <updated>2021-05-02T10:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six blurry seconds of Elden Ring have leaked on the internet.
VGC reports the short clip emerged from 4Chan, before ending up all over social media.
The clip, which ResetEra is currently hosting, features the same Bandai Namco internal watermark seen in the footage that leaked in March.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saints Row The Third Remastered hits Steam late May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-02-saints-row-the-third-remastered-hits-steam-late-may</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-02-saints-row-the-third-remastered-hits-steam-late-may"/>
        <updated>2021-05-02T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saints Row The Third Remastered hits Steam on 22nd May.
Confirmation comes from the official Saints Row Twitter account.
The Saints Row The Third remaster came out in May 2020 on console and PC via the Epic Games Store. Now Epic's standard one year of PC exclusivity is up, Volition's game can hit Steam.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EA is selling FIFA 21 cosmetics outside loot boxes for the first time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-fifa-21-sells-cosmetics-outside-loot-boxes-for-the-first-time</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-fifa-21-sells-cosmetics-outside-loot-boxes-for-the-first-time"/>
        <updated>2021-05-01T19:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EA is selling FIFA 21 cosmetics outside loot boxes for the first time.
The FIFA 21 Ultimate Team store was updated today, 1st May, to include a new Stadium tab. You can buy a tifo, a stadium theme, and a new home and away kit individually, or all available items in a bundle.
These cosmetics are available direct purchase, which is the first time EA has done this. Previously, cosmetics could only be earned through objectives or via Ultimate Team's controversial loot boxes.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riot to record Valorant voice chat to combat toxic behaviour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-riot-to-record-valorant-voice-chat-to-combat-toxic-behaviour</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-riot-to-record-valorant-voice-chat-to-combat-toxic-behaviour"/>
        <updated>2021-05-01T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Riot has announced its plan to record Valorant voice chat in order to combat toxic behaviour.
In a post on its website, Riot said it's updating its privacy notice to allow it to record and evaluate voice comms when a report for disruptive behaviour is submitted in its competitive multiplayer shooter.
If a violation is detected, Riot vowed to take action and remove the data "when it is no longer needed for reviews".
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raven gives all Call of Duty: Warzone players the Tortured & Rescued Adler skin for free after botched Hunt for Adler event]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-raven-gives-all-call-of-duty-warzone-players-the-tortured-and-rescued-adler-skin-for-free-after-botched-hunt-for-adler-event</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-raven-gives-all-call-of-duty-warzone-players-the-tortured-and-rescued-adler-skin-for-free-after-botched-hunt-for-adler-event"/>
        <updated>2021-05-01T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raven Software has given all Call of Duty: Warzone players the Tortured &amp; Rescued Adler skin for free after botching the Hunt for Adler event.
The Hunt for Adler event, which went live alongside season three and the release of the Verdansk '84 map, rewarded players with the Tortured &amp; Rescued Adler skin upon completion of a series of challenges.
But the event ran into a series of issues, with the associated challenges not tracking as intended, and the intel required to obtain sometimes spawning outs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BioWare teases Grey Wardens for Dragon Age 4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-bioware-teases-grey-wardens-for-dragon-age-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-bioware-teases-grey-wardens-for-dragon-age-4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-01T15:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dragon Age fans will know the Grey Wardens well. The warrior group are the stars of Dragon Age: Origins, fighting the horrible darkspawn throughout the fantasy world of Thedas. It's the Grey Wardens who lead the charge against each Blight, ensuring the survival of the world. In Origins, the player is initiated into the Grey Wardens via a ritual called the Joining, which involves imbibing darkspawn blood. My wife took a fondness to Alistair, a reluctantly heroic Grey Warden and... well... you know. It's a Bi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scavengers' early access made available to all today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-scavengers-early-access-made-available-to-all-today</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-scavengers-early-access-made-available-to-all-today"/>
        <updated>2021-05-01T14:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Scavengers early access is being made available to all today.
Midwinters' free-to-play third-person battle royale hybrid launched in early access form this week, but was only playable via a Twitch Drops event.
But the event ran into issues. Keys could only be claimed by watching the game on Twitch for 30 minutes, and some who tuned in did not receive their keys. Eventually, Scavengers ran out of Steam keys to give out to people, forcing Midwinter to send out Epic Games Store keys instead. Coupled with t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Warzone's "Big Bertha" meta and the state of solos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-call-of-duty-warzones-big-bertha-meta-and-the-state-of-solos</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-call-of-duty-warzones-big-bertha-meta-and-the-state-of-solos"/>
        <updated>2021-05-01T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Warzone players are using the 6x6 cargo truck vehicle to great effect in what's dubbed the "Big Bertha meta".
This vehicle is pretty much a rolling fortress, and is big enough to give you significant cover across the battle royale's map. It can also tank damage for most of the match.
The Big Bertha meta is particularly popular in solos, when you're playing Warzone on your own against 149 other solo players. You can see players heading straight for a Big Bertha upon parachuting out of a chopper…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paradox temporarily shelves Imperator: Rome to focus on other projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-paradox-temporarily-shelves-imperator-rome-to-focus-on-other-projects</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-01-paradox-temporarily-shelves-imperator-rome-to-focus-on-other-projects"/>
        <updated>2021-05-01T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paradox has temporarily shelved Imperator: Rome to focus on other projects.
In a post on its forum titled "update of the organisation at PDS", the company outlined various internal changes made to its main development studio earlier this year.
The 150-person strong strategy studio is now split into three distinct studios: PDS Green, PDS Red, and PDS Gold. Each team is in charge of maintaining existing games and developing new games set to be announced at PDXCON, the company's upcoming showcase event.
Read m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: On Squid Coloration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/friday-squid-blogging-on-squid-coloration.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/friday-squid-blogging-on-squid-coloration.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T21:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nice excerpt from Martin Wallin&#8217;s book Squid.
As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.
Read my blog posting guidelines here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DynamoDB vs. MongoDB: A Comparison and How to Choose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/dynamodb-vs-mongodb-a-comparison/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/dynamodb-vs-mongodb-a-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T14:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A real world comparison of two wildly successful modern replacements for traditional database systems.
The post DynamoDB vs. MongoDB: A Comparison and How to Choose appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in AWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serious MacOS Vulnerability Patched]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/serous-macos-vulnerability-patched.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/serous-macos-vulnerability-patched.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T12:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple just patched a MacOS vulnerability that bypassed malware checks.
The flaw is akin to a front entrance that&#8217;s barred and bolted effectively, but with a cat door at the bottom that you can easily toss a bomb through. Apple mistakenly assumed that applications will always have certain specific attributes. Owens discovered that if he made an application that was really just a script—code that tells another program what do rather than doing it itself—and didn&#8217;t include a standard application me…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After the Pandemic]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2457/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2457/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying People Through Lack of Cell Phone Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/identifying-people-through-lack-of-cell-phone-use.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/identifying-people-through-lack-of-cell-phone-use.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T11:07:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this entertaining story of French serial criminal Rédoine Faïd and his jailbreaking ways, there&#8217;s this bit about cell phone surveillance:
After Faïd&#8217;s helicopter breakout, 3,000 police officers took part in the manhunt. According to the 2019 documentary La Traque de Rédoine Faïd, detective units scoured records of cell phones used during his escape, isolating a handful of numbers active at the time that went silent shortly thereafter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sun Also Crashes: Keeping Current]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/the-sun-also-crashes-keeping-current/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/the-sun-also-crashes-keeping-current/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you let the tech you’re skilled in become the cornerstone of your identity, you limit future career possibilities. Here’s what to do instead
The post The Sun Also Crashes: Keeping Current appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in AWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Second Click Here to Kill Everybody Sale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/second-click-here-to-kill-everybody-sale.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/second-click-here-to-kill-everybody-sale.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T01:22:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a limited time, I am selling signed copies of Click Here to Kill Everybody in hardcover for just $6, plus shipping.
I have 600 copies of the book available. When they&#8217;re gone, the sale is over and the price will revert to normal.
Order here.
Please be patient on delivery. It&#8217;s a lot of work to sign and mail hundreds of books. I try to do some each day, but sometimes I can&#8217;t. And the pandemic can cause mail slowdowns all over the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Types of Scientific Paper]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2456/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2456/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confidence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/confidence/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/confidence/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Vulnerabilities in Cellebrite]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/security-vulnerabilities-in-cellebrite.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/security-vulnerabilities-in-cellebrite.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T11:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moxie Marlinspike has an intriguing blog post about Cellebrite, a tool used by police and others to break into smartphones. Moxie got his hands on one of the devices, which seems to be a pair of Windows software packages and a whole lot of connecting cables.
According to Moxie, the software is riddled with vulnerabilities. (The one example he gives is that it uses FFmpeg DLLs from 2012, and have not been patched with the 100+ security updates since then.)
&#8230;we found that it&#8217;s possible to execute …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When AIs Start Hacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/when-ais-start-hacking.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/when-ais-start-hacking.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T11:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you don&#8217;t have enough to worry about already, consider a world where AIs are hackers.
Hacking is as old as humanity. We are creative problem solvers. We exploit loopholes, manipulate systems, and strive for more influence, power, and wealth. To date, hacking has exclusively been a human activity. Not for long.
As I lay out in a report I just published, artificial intelligence will eventually find vulnerabilities in all sorts of social, economic, and political systems, and then exploit them at unpre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virus Consulting]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2455/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2455/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: Squid-Shaped Bike Rack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/friday-squid-blogging-squid-shaped-bike-rack.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/friday-squid-blogging-squid-shaped-bike-rack.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T21:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There&#8217;s a new squid-shaped bike rack in Ballard, WA.
As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.
Read my blog posting guidelines here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Amazon Athena? An Introduction and Walkthrough]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/what-is-amazon-athena-an-introduction-and-walkthrough/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/what-is-amazon-athena-an-introduction-and-walkthrough/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Amazon Athena right for your organization? Learn about the pros and cons of the serverless query service to see if it makes sense for your use case.
The post What is Amazon Athena? An Introduction and Walkthrough appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in AWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect Fit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/perfect-fit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/perfect-fit/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.21: Metrics Stability hits GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/23/kubernetes-release-1.21-metrics-stability-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/23/kubernetes-release-1.21-metrics-stability-ga/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Han Kang (Google), Elana Hashman (Red Hat)
Kubernetes 1.21 marks the graduation of the metrics stability framework and along with it, the first officially supported stable metrics. Not only do stable metrics come with supportability guarantees, the metrics stability framework brings escape hatches that you can use if you encounter problematic metrics.
See the list of stable Kubernetes metrics here
What are stable metrics and why do we need them?
A stable metric is one which, from a consumption poin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On North Korea’s Cyberattack Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/on-north-koreas-cyberattack-capabilities.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/on-north-koreas-cyberattack-capabilities.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T11:12:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Excellent New Yorker article on North Korea&#8217;s offensive cyber capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Evolving Kubernetes networking with the Gateway API]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/22/evolving-kubernetes-networking-with-the-gateway-api/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/22/evolving-kubernetes-networking-with-the-gateway-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Mark Church (Google), Harry Bagdi (Kong), Daneyon Hanson (Red Hat), Nick Young (VMware), Manuel Zapf (Traefik Labs)
The Ingress resource is one of the many Kubernetes success stories. It created a diverse ecosystem of Ingress controllers which were used across hundreds of thousands of clusters in a standardized and consistent way. This standardization helped users adopt Kubernetes. However, five years after the creation of Ingress, there are signs of fragmentation into different but strikingly simi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[S3’s Durability Guarantees Aren’t What You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/s3s-durability-guarantees-arent-what-you-think/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/s3s-durability-guarantees-arent-what-you-think/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[S3 has insanely generous data durability guarantees. Even so, read the fine print, and you’ll realize that S3 doesn’t remove the need for backups.
The post S3&#8217;s Durability Guarantees Aren&#8217;t What You Think appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in AWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Graceful Node Shutdown Goes Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/21/graceful-node-shutdown-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/21/graceful-node-shutdown-beta/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: David Porter (Google), Mrunal Patel (Red Hat), and Tim Bannister (The Scale Factory)
Graceful node shutdown, beta in 1.21, enables kubelet to gracefully evict pods during a node shutdown.
Kubernetes is a distributed system and as such we need to be prepared for inevitable failures — nodes will fail, containers might crash or be restarted, and - ideally - your workloads will be able to withstand these catastrophic events.
One of the common classes of issues are workload failures on node shutdown or …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Annotating Kubernetes Services for Humans]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/20/annotating-k8s-for-humans/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/20/annotating-k8s-for-humans/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Richard Li, Ambassador Labs
Have you ever been asked to troubleshoot a failing Kubernetes service and struggled to find basic information about the service such as the source repository and owner?
One of the problems as Kubernetes applications grow is the proliferation of services. As the number of services grows, developers start to specialize working with specific services. When it comes to troubleshooting, however, developers need to be able to find the source, understand the service and dependen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Defining Network Policy Conformance for Container Network Interface (CNI) providers]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/20/defining-networkpolicy-conformance-cni-providers/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/20/defining-networkpolicy-conformance-cni-providers/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Matt Fenwick (Synopsys), Jay Vyas (VMWare), Ricardo Katz, Amim Knabben (Loadsmart), Douglas Schilling Landgraf (Red Hat), Christopher Tomkins (Tigera)
Special thanks to Tim Hockin and Bowie Du (Google), Dan Winship and Antonio Ojea (Red Hat),
Casey Davenport and Shaun Crampton (Tigera), and Abhishek Raut and Antonin Bas (VMware) for
being supportive of this work, and working with us to resolve issues in different Container Network Interfaces (CNIs) over time.
A brief conversation around &quot;node …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing Indexed Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/19/introducing-indexed-jobs/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/19/introducing-indexed-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aldo Culquicondor (Google)
Once you have containerized a non-parallel Job,
it is quite easy to get it up and running on Kubernetes without modifications to
the binary. In most cases, when running parallel distributed Jobs, you had
to set a separate system to partition the work among the workers. For
example, you could set up a task queue to assign one work item to each
Pod or multiple items
to each Pod until the queue is emptied.
The Kubernetes 1.21 release introduces a new field to control Job comp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Volume Health Monitoring Alpha Update]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/16/volume-health-monitoring-alpha-update/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/16/volume-health-monitoring-alpha-update/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Xing Yang (VMware)
The CSI Volume Health Monitoring feature, originally introduced in 1.19 has undergone a large update for the 1.21 release.
Why add Volume Health Monitoring to Kubernetes?
Without Volume Health Monitoring, Kubernetes has no knowledge of the state of the underlying volumes of a storage system after a PVC is provisioned and used by a Pod. Many things could happen to the underlying storage system after a volume is provisioned in Kubernetes. For example, the volume could be deleted by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/meeting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/meeting/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development satire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Three Tenancy Models For Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/15/three-tenancy-models-for-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/15/three-tenancy-models-for-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Ryan Bezdicek (Medtronic), Jim Bugwadia (Nirmata), Tasha Drew (VMware), Fei Guo (Alibaba), Adrian Ludwin (Google)
Kubernetes clusters are typically used by several teams in an organization. In other cases, Kubernetes may be used to deliver applications to end users requiring segmentation and isolation of resources across users from different organizations. Secure sharing of Kubernetes control plane and worker node resources allows maximizing productivity and saving costs in both cases.
The Kubernet…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning is a Marvelously Executed Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/machine-learning-is-a-marvelously-executed-scam/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/machine-learning-is-a-marvelously-executed-scam/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning is a Marvelously Executed Scam I&#8217;ve joked periodically that machine learning (or &#8220;ML&#8221;) adherents claim to be able to sort through vast quantities of data and find absolutely anything except a viable business model. I&#8217;d like to revisit that with a clarification: They also apparently can&#8217;t tell a story around what they do [&#8230;]
The post Machine Learning is a Marvelously Executed Scam appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in AWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Local Storage: Storage Capacity Tracking, Distributed Provisioning and Generic Ephemeral Volumes hit Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/14/local-storage-features-go-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/14/local-storage-features-go-beta/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Patrick Ohly (Intel)
The &quot;generic ephemeral
volumes&quot;
and &quot;storage capacity
tracking&quot;
features in Kubernetes are getting promoted to beta in Kubernetes
1.21. Together with the distributed provisioning
support
in the CSI external-provisioner, development and deployment of
Container Storage Interface (CSI) drivers which manage storage locally
on a node become a lot easier.
This blog post explains how such drivers worked before and how these
features can be used to make drivers simp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine 3.10.9, 3.11.11 and 3.12.7 released]]></title>
        <id>https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.10.9-3.11.11-3.12.7-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.10.9-3.11.11-3.12.7-released.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine Linux]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alpine Linux News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine 3.13.5 released]]></title>
        <id>https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.13.5-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.13.5-released.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine Linux]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alpine Linux News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/introduction/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/introduction/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: kube-state-metrics goes v2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/13/kube-state-metrics-v-2-0/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/13/kube-state-metrics-v-2-0/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Lili Cosic (Red Hat), Frederic Branczyk (Polar Signals), Manuel Rüger (Sony Interactive Entertainment), Tariq Ibrahim (Salesforce)
What?
kube-state-metrics, a project under the Kubernetes organization, generates Prometheus format metrics based on the current state of the Kubernetes native resources. It does this by listening to the Kubernetes API and gathering information about resources and objects, e.g. Deployments, Pods, Services, and StatefulSets. A full list of resources is available in the do…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing Suspended Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/12/introducing-suspended-jobs/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/12/introducing-suspended-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Adhityaa Chandrasekar (Google)
Jobs are a crucial part of
Kubernetes' API. While other kinds of workloads such as Deployments,
ReplicaSets,
StatefulSets, and
DaemonSets
solve use-cases that require Pods to run forever, Jobs are useful when Pods need
to run to completion. Commonly used in parallel batch processing, Jobs can be
used in a variety of applications ranging from video rendering and database
maintenance to sending bulk emails and scientific computing.
While the amount of parallelism and the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>