<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-13T00:46:23.846Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.6.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colonial Pipeline resumes operations after ransomware prompted closure]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764758</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764758"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T00:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Closure prompted panic buying, price hikes, and other disruptions in East Coast states.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vizio TV buyers are becoming the product Vizio sells, not just its customers]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764690</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764690"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T22:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vizio's ads, streaming, and data business grew 133 percent year-over-year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDC advisory committee recommends COVID vaccine for 12- to 15-year-olds]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764646</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764646"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T20:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formal approval of the Pfizer/BioNTech by the CDC expected within 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s 2nd-gen Echo Show offers better cameras, CPUs, and speakers]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764517</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764517"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T20:12:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Echo Show 8 features a 13mp wide-angle camera, 8-core CPU, and digital pan/zoom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better than holograms: 3D-animated starships can be viewed from any angle]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763689</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763689"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T19:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike holograms, the optical trap display produces images viewable from all angles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blizzard showing off Overwatch 2 PvP in two-hour livestream next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149489</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-blizzard-showing-off-overwatch-2-pvp-in-two-hour-livestream-next-week"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T18:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its announcement back at BlizzCon 2019, Overwatch 2's pre-release marketing has predominantly focussed on its new bits - which is to say its story campaign and co-op modes. PvP's still a major part of the package, of course, and Blizzard will finally be giving Overwatch 2's competitive multiplayer an airing more of an airing next week.
That's according to Overwatch game director Aaron Keller, making his Developer Update video debut following Jeff Kaplan's departure from Blizzard last month.
"We've bee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi and the US government bury the hatchet, settle investment ban]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764488</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764488"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T17:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's DOD called Xiaomi a "Communist Chinese military company" in mid-January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neural implant lets paralyzed person type by imagining writing]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764531</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764531"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T17:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A paralyzed individual hit 90 characters per minute, 99% accuracy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$50 monthly broadband discounts available starting today via 825 ISPs]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764525</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764525"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T16:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FCC's emergency pandemic fund is open, with 825 home and mobile ISPs participating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snap cuts off Yolo, LMK anonymous messaging apps after lawsuit over teen’s death]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764515</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764515"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T16:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawsuit alleges messaging apps were “dangerous and defective.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scarlet Nexus console demos arrive later this month, starting with Xbox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149466</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-scarlet-nexus-console-demos-arrive-later-this-month-starting-with-xbox"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're still trying to wrap your head around what "brain punk" is, then not to worry, as action-RPG Scarlet Nexus is getting some demos this month ahead of its release on 25th June. Hopefully that will help clear some things up. 
Bandai Namco has announced the demo will first land on Xbox Series X/S and Xbox One on 21st May, with PlayStation 4 and PS5 following on 28th May. There's no news on whether the demo is coming to PC, so we'll have to wait and see if it comes to the platform. 
Scarlet Nexus is se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valve’s Gabe Newell hints at vague console plans coming “this year”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764492</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764492"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indefinite tease comes during Q&#038;A with New Zealand students.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best smartwatches for every type of user]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764083</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764083"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We looked at smartwatches from every stripe, shape, and price point to find the best ones for your needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Gaskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[J&J vaccine supply has run out; Emergent says it’s working on improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764475</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764475"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T14:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vaccine production at Emergent's facility is still halted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Is Someone Else’s Job Zero]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8791</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/security-is-someone-elses-job-zero/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you attend an AWS talk about security, bump into an AWS security person in a business meeting, or are in line behind an AWS employee at a Starbucks, you&#8217;ll invariably hear the phrase &#8220;Security is Job Zero.&#8221; What does this actually mean? Cynically, I might suggest that they came up with a list of [&#8230;]
The post Security Is Someone Else’s Job Zero appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europa Universalis 4 director apologises for "long trail of low quality releases"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149443</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-europa-universalis-4-director-apologises-for-long-trail-of-low-quality-releases"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent Leviathan expansion for Europa Universalis 4 has managed to earn itself an unflattering spot amongst the lowest-ranked products on Steam, with a positive review rating of only seven percent from 3955 reviews. Players said the DLC was seriously buggy and suffered from a host of problems, and sure enough, the game's bug report megathreads quickly filled up with complaints. Paradox Tinto studio manager and game director Johan Andersson has now issued an apology for the state of the expansion and sev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox Series X/S adds OG Xbox dashboard theme]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149432</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-xbox-series-x-s-adds-og-xbox-dashboard-theme"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released a new dynamic theme for Xbox Series X/S which brings to life the retro, Matrix-inspired aesthetic of the OG Xbox. 
The animated background, named "The Original", is more akin to the loading animation you got when first turning on that chunky console rather than its actual dashboard, but the look will likely still feel familiar. 
Here's The Verge's Tom Warren with a preview - though it should now be rolling out to all Xbox Series X/S owners:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Book Sale: Beyond Fear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/book-sale-beyond-fear.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/book-sale-beyond-fear.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have 80 copies of my 2000 book Beyond Fear available at the very cheap price of $5 plus shipping. Note that there is a 20% chance that your book will have a &#8220;BT Counterpane&#8221; sticker on the front cover.
Order your signed copy here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft says it won't abandon paid AAA games for free-to-play]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149402</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-ubisoft-says-it-wont-abandon-paid-aaa-games-for-free-to-play"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T11:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking with investors, Ubisoft financial boss Frederick Duguet said the company's focus on releasing three to four big budget games per year was no longer "a proper indication of our value creation dynamics". Or, in normal speak, Ubisoft wanted its profits to grow by making even more money from other things.
On Twitter, Ubisoft's Sean Lama clarified this did not mean free-to-play games would replace AAA games. Instead, it meant Ubisoft now saw free-to-play as "an additional way to experience some of these…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Console Purchase Pilot looks like a new way to avoid Xbox Series scalping]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149389</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-microsoft-offers-new-way-to-avoid-xbox-series-scalping-through-insider-program"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T11:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since the new generation of consoles released at the end of last year, both the PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series consoles have suffered from stock shortages - and as a result of that, increased levels of scalping. The problem grew so severe that even British politicans began to pay attention. And with console shortages set to continue for the foreseeable future, it seems Microsoft is trialling a new way for customers to acquire a console - without everything being ruined by scalper bots. 
The new program,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volvo and Daimler bet on hydrogen truck boom this decade]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764362</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764362"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T10:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swedish and German groups expect fuel to challenge diesel in long-distance freight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Financial Times</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Destiny 2 cross-play accidentally switched on early]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149379</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-destiny-2-cross-play-accidentally-switched-on-early"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T10:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bungie has acknowledged the fact you can currently play with people from platforms other than your own in Destiny 2 - all a little earlier than planned. 
Reports of Destiny 2 crossplay being possible emerged last night, and were picked up by Destiny community manager Cozmo. 
Describing it as an unintended "sneak peek", Bungie said that crossplay was officially still in development, and would be disabled again in the coming days. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends update nerfs Spitfire and Bocek Bow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149363</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-apex-legends-update-nerfs-spitfire-and-bocek-bow"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T10:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends' Legacy update has now been live for over a week - after a somewhat wobbly start - and Respawn has already rolled out some balance changes for two weapons. The Spitfire and newly-added Bocek Bow, both considered overpowered by the player community, have been adjusted to make them a little less lethal. 
As explained on the Legacy patch notes page, the Spitfire's bullet damage has been reduced from 19 to 18, while gold and purple magazines will now hold 50 bullets instead of 55. The Bocek seems t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Battlefield 6 is designed for PS5 and Xbox Series X, but will also run on last-gen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149361</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-battlefield-6-is-designed-for-new-consoles-but-will-also-run-on-last-gen"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EA has discussed how Battlefield 6 will benefit from its development focus having been on current-gen consoles - PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S - even though it will also launch on last-gen hardware - PS4 and Xbox One.
The fact Battlefield 6 will not be exclusive to current-gen consoles seems somewhat obvious, in the grand scheme of things - with scalpers and low stock still prevalent and a huge, active install base for PS4 and Xbox One. But EA only made it official for the first time last night, in an e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aston Martin’s new boss tells us about the future of the company]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764324</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764324"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T23:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former AMG CEO Tobias Moers is now in charge of the British carmaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Famed Arthurian tale comes to silver screen in The Green Knight trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764204</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764204"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T22:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Honor. That is why a knight does what he does."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rare fungal infections that destroy eyeballs and kill are on the rise in India]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764334</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764334"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T21:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People with diabetes are particularly vulnerable to the aggressive fungus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware crooks post cops’ psych evaluations after talks with DC police stall]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764296</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764296"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T21:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Babuk demands $4 million, Metropolitan Police Department offers $100,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia’s RTX 3050 brings ray tracing and DLSS to $800 laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764225</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764225"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T20:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Performance-boosting DLSS on entry-level laptops could be a big deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LucasArts' 16-bit classic Zombies Ate My Neighbors heading to PC and consoles in June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149315</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-lucasarts-16-bit-classic-zombies-ate-my-neighbors-heading-to-pc-and-consoles-in-june"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T20:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LucasArts' fondly remembered 16-bit classic Zombies At My Neighbours is getting a long-awaited re-release on Xbox, PlayStation, Switch, and PC on 29th June.
Zombies Ate My Neighbors, which originally launched on SNES and Sega Mega Drive back in 1993, follows the adventures of Zeke and Julie (who can be played solo or co-operatively) as they attempt to save their neighbours from a host of B-movie monsters - zombies, werewolves, vampires, giant ants, aliens, and so on - on a journey that stretches from suburb…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Github reverses takedown of reverse-engineered GTA source code]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764252</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764252"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T19:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identical fork is restored after DMCA counterclaim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel claims its new Tiger Lake-H CPUs for laptops beat AMD’s Ryzen 5000]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764054</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764054"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T19:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flagship Core i9-11980HK allegedly beats Ryzen 9 5900HX by 11 to 26 percent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our fave gentleman thief is back for revenge in trailer for Lupin part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764063</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764063"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Viewers frustrated by part 1's maddening cliffhanger won't have much longer to wait.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTC expanding PC VR headset line-up with Vive Pro 2 this June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149310</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-htc-expanding-pc-vr-headset-line-up-with-vive-pro-2-this-june"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTC has unveiled the latest addition to its PC VR headset line-up in the form of the Vive Pro 2, which arrives on 4th June with pre-orders open now.
As its name implies, HTC's Vive Pro 2 is the direct successor to the high-end PC VR headset it released in 2018. It'll up the ante with a 5K resolution display (2448x2448 pixels per eye), a 120-degree field of view, and a 120Hz panel. By way of contrast, the original Vive Pro featured a 2880x1600 resolution, a 110-degree field of view, and a 90Hz refresh rate.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baltimore chief prosecutor asks FCC to stop negative news coverage about her]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764100</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764100"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First Amendment prevents FCC from punishing news station for its "tone."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s MagSafe wireless charger is on sale for a new low price today]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763926</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763926"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealmaster also has wireless headphones, Switch gear, and gaming monitors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After many delays, Massachusetts’ Vineyard Wind is finally approved]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764130</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764130"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new project will be over 20 times larger than anything built in the US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel and Nvidia announce new 11th-gen laptop CPUs and RTX GPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149289</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2021-05-11-new-intel-laptop-cpus-and-nvidia-gpus-announced"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bad news: your gaming laptop is officially last-gen. That's the word from Intel and Nvidia, who teamed up today to announce new mobile processors and graphics cards. Intel is debuting their Comet Lake H CPUs, bringing their 10nm process to high-performance 45W processors ideal for gaming or content creation, while Nvidia announced two new mobile graphics cards, the RTX 3050 and 3050 Ti. Here's what you need to know.
Let's cover Nvidia's announcements first, as the company is doing something a bit unusual he…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: The Samsung/AMD Exynos SoC will be out for laptops this year]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764029</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764029"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:48:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exynos with an AMD GPU is coming for laptops, but maybe not phones?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft's beleaguered pirate game Skull & Bones now won't arrive before 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149305</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-ubisofts-beleaguered-pirate-game-skull-and-bones-now-wont-arrive-before-2022"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft has confirmed its long-announced and much-postponed shared-world swashbuckler Skull &amp; Bones is now expected to release in the 2022-2023 financial year.
Originally revealed back at E3 2017, Skull &amp; Bones - which is being developed by Ubisoft Singapore - was initially due to release on Xbox, PS4, and PC sometime the following year. However, it's now been subject to two official delays, once in 2018 and another in 2019.
As part of the latter announcement, Ubisoft told fans, "We're going to batt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stargate: Timekeepers is an RTS coming to PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149252</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-stargate-timekeepers-is-an-rts-coming-to-pc"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember Stargate? 27 years after the much-loved sci-fi film came out, a new Stargate game has been announced.
Stargate: Timekeepers is a real-time strategy game set for PC and in development at Creative Forge Games, the Polish studio behind Phantom Doctrine and Hard West. It's published by Slitherine.
The teaser video below does not include gameplay, but we do get to see a Stargate. It's all very '90s.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EA swerves E3 to hold live event in July]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149286</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-ea-swerves-e3-to-hold-live-event-in-july"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EA Play Live, the publisher's big annual announcement show, will be held this year on 22nd July. 
That's a month later than 2021's digital-only E3 event, which is dated for 12th to 15th June. 
EA has not been a major part of E3 for years, instead opting to hold its own EA Play events elsewhere. E3 is traditionally held at the Los Angeles Convention Centre, while in recent years EA has housed its own show at the same time a few miles away up in Hollywood. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming a robot to teach itself how to move]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764044</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764044"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T16:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flexible, open-ended learning software works but finds the real world difficult.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTC’s newest headsets signal end of Vive’s 5-year “VR for the home” mission]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763889</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763889"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T16:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vive Focus 3 is a $1,299, enterprise-grade answer to Oculus Quest 2, plus Vive Pro 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon and others ordered to slash diesel pollution from warehouse trucks]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764041</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764041"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T15:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Southern California is being smothered by pollution from e-commerce warehouses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch is getting a calculator app, priced £8]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149270</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-nintendo-switch-is-getting-a-calculator-app-priced-gbp8"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T15:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The application, simply named Calculator, launches on the Nintendo Switch eShop tomorrow,12th May, priced £8.09.
Calculator is a third-party app, not made by Nintendo, and one of the rare few non-gaming applications to make it onto the eShop. Of course, some people do find maths fun - perhaps even a game! I am not one of these people.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galactic Civilizations 4 due out 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149265</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-galactic-civilizations-4-due-out-2022"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Galactic Civilizations 4 is due out on PC in 2022, Stardock has announced.
The space 4X strategy sandbox sequel goes into early access later this spring. The announcement trailer is below:
The player begins with only their home planet and must research new technologies, explore the known galaxy and colonise new worlds while keeping their people at home happy. At the same time, players engage in trade, diplomacy, intrigue and war with alien civilisations.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Security Risk Assessment Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/ai-security-risk-assessment-tool.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/ai-security-risk-assessment-tool.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T14:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft researchers just released an open-source automation tool for security testing AI systems: &#8220;Counterfit.&#8221; Details on their blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fatal Tesla Model S crash unlikely to involve Autopilot, according to NTSB]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764018</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764018"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Was the person found in the back of the car trying to manually release the door?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse-engineered GTA code restored after developer files DMCA counterclaim]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149208</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-reverse-engineered-gta-code-restored-after-developer-files-dmca-counterclaim"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T12:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse-engineered GTA code was restored after its developer filed a DMCA counterclaim on GitHub.
TorrentFreak reports GitHub restored a fork of the fan-made re3 project after its creator filed a Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA) takedown counter-claim.
As Eurogamer reported in February, the Grand Theft Auto 3 and Vice City reverse-engineering fan project known as re3 was hit by a DMCA filed by Rockstar parent company Take-Two that claimed copyright infringement.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite's new PVE survival mode Daybreak looks set to launch soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149187</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-fortnites-new-pve-survival-mode-looks-set-to-launch-soon"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite looks ready to launch its sandbox survival mode, Daybreak, according to files added in today's new 16.40 patch. 
We've seen glimpses of Daybreak before, in leaked files from previous patches and also, intriguingly, via internal documentation released as part of the ongoing Apple v Epic trial, dated from last year. This suggested it has been in the works for quite some time, and was set to arrive a lot sooner.
"You wake up alone and unarmed along the coast of an island, with no memory of how you arr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baby Chris, Lady X and Dante lead the early days of Resident Evil Village modding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149186</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-baby-chris-lady-x-and-dante-lead-the-early-days-of-resident-evil-village-modding"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's early days in the burgeoning demand for Resident Evil Village mods, but already the community has come up with some... interesting tweaks.
THERE MAY BE RESIDENT EVIL VILLAGE SPOILERS AHEAD.
Mini Me Chris is one of the more eye-catching mods, simply because of how nightmarish it is. Modder JTeghius Kittius said: "This was a dumb joke that popped into my head so I had to do this."
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Unbannable" Apex Legends cheater faces potential legal action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149185</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-unbannable-apex-legends-cheater-faces-potential-legal-action"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Respawn recently reassured players that it was exploring "every avenue" to take down Apex Legends cheaters - legal action being one of them - and it seems one high-profile cheater is already facing something worse than the ban hammer. Prolific cheater Tufi, who some in the Apex Legends community have described as a "God" and "unbannable" cheater, is apparently facing some form of legal action from Respawn - although details remain light on exactly how far this has progressed. 
Earlier this week Apex Legends…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new book, Amazon Unbound, reveals Jeff Bezos’ envy of SpaceX]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763718</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763718"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bezos tried to hire Gwynne Shotwell to run Blue Origin in 2016.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warhammer 40,000: Battlesector now out in July]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149172</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-warhammer-40-000-battlesector-now-out-in-july"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warhammer 40,000: Battlesector comes out 15th July on PC, PlayStation and Xbox priced £30.99, publisher Slitherine has announced.
The PC version of the Blood Angels versus Tyranids turn-based strategy game was due out in May, with the console versions to follow in the summer. But Slitherine is now going for a joined-up launch across all platforms in July.
Battlesector is developed by Black Lab Games, maker of the well-received Battlestar Galactica Deadlock. It's described as "battle-scale", and based on gam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic v Apple trial debates appropriateness of Fortnite's naked banana man Peely]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149171</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-epic-v-apple-trial-debates-the-appropriateness-of-fortnites-naked-banana-man-peely"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was inevitable: the appropriateness of Fortnite's bizarre banana man Peely has now been discussed in open court.
Last night, in the ongoing Apple v Epic trial, Peely came under scrutiny for being a naked piece of fruit with arms and legs.
In remarks transcribed from the courtroom by Verge reporter Adi Robertson, a lawyer for Apple brought up Peely in court and made a deal of showing the character wearing clothes (his Chapter 2 Season 2 Bond-esque Agent Peely tuxedo).
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance 2 re-release "on the table"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149155</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-baldurs-gate-dark-alliance-2-re-release-on-the-table"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T09:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A PC port of Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance is coming later this year, Black Isle Studios has confirmed.
The cult classic console RPG re-released last week on PlayStation and Xbox consoles (the Nintendo Switch version is still M.I.A.). The console launch trailer is below:
"The PC port of BG:DA is in the works and coming later this year," Black Isle tweeted.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil Village ships over 3m copies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149144</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-resident-evil-village-ships-over-3m-copies"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capcom has shipped over 3m copies of Resident Evil Village, the company has announced.
The horror game went on sale on Friday, 7th May, and has launched strong. (Digital Foundry's Resident Evil Village tech breakdown is in the video below:)
In the UK, Village is already the second-highest UK boxed debut this year, beaten only by Super Mario 3D World + Bowser's Fury, and has set franchise records for concurrent players on Steam.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDA authorizes Pfizer’s COVID-19 vaccine for 12- to 15-year-olds]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763967</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763967"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T23:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CDC's advisory committee will meet Wednesday to vote on recommending use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev turns The Room 4: Old Sins' creepy old dollhouse into a gorgeous Lego build]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149114</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-fireproof-dev-turns-the-room-4-old-sins-creepy-old-dollhouse-into-gorgeous-lego-build"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lego is (as a year in lockdown with a whole lot to time to assemble plastic bricks has taught me) cool, and developer Fireproof Games' gorgeously atmospheric The Room puzzle series is, among many other good things, cool too. So it should come as absolutely no surprise to anyone that combining the two results in a very cool thing indeed.
The architect of this particular very cool thing is Fireproof Games' own graphic and motion designer Roger Schembri who, under the name Lego CustardKid, has previously submi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple invests $45 million more in Gorilla Glass-maker Corning]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763824</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763824"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:19:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investment follows millions more that produced the iPhone 12's ceramic shield.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware Shuts Down US Pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/ransomware-shuts-down-us-pipeline.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/ransomware-shuts-down-us-pipeline.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T19:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a major story: a probably Russian cybercrime group called DarkSide shut down the Colonial Pipeline in a ransomware attack. The pipeline supplies much of the East Coast. This is the new and improved ransomware attack: the hackers stole nearly 100 gig of data, and are threatening to publish it. The White House has declared a state of emergency and has created a task force to deal with the problem, but it&#8217;s unclear what they can do. This is bad; our supply chains are so tightly coupled that this …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon “seized and destroyed” 2 million counterfeit products in 2020]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763878</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763878"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T19:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Counterfeit products sent to Amazon warehouses are destroyed to prevent resale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the battle of the alien symbiotes in Venom: Let There Be Carnage trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763740</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763740"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T18:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I've been thinking about you, Eddie, because you and I are the same."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By eating them, hyenas gathered 9 Neanderthal skeletons in one cave]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763816</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763816"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T18:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Neanderthals appear to have met a very bad end.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiona N. Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security researcher successfully jailbreaks an Apple AirTag]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763811</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763811"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T17:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Successful jailbreak increases existing AirTag security and privacy concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google: We put YouTube TV in the main YouTube app. What now, Roku?]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763745</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763745"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T17:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google sidesteps the YouTube TV ban, threatens to send free devices to customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First (brief) look at Rambo in Call of Duty: Warzone and Black Ops Cold War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149098</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-first-brief-look-at-rambo-in-call-of-duty-warzone-and-black-ops-cold-war"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Activision has offered a glimpse at Rambo in Call of Duty: Warzone and Black Ops Cold War.
The official Call of Duty Twitter account released a short clip showing Rambo preparing to unleash a fire arrow from his trademark bow at an unfortunate victim, alongside the tagline: "Become war."
Rambo arrives on 20th May as part of the mid-season update for Season 3 - no doubt as a costly soldier skin.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AstraZeneca’s troubled vaccine not renewed in EU; Pfizer gets big, new deal]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763808</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763808"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T17:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meanwhile, China’s Sinopharm vaccine—79% efficacy, easy to store—authorized by WHO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers who shut down pipeline: We don’t want to cause “problems for society”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763760</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763760"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T16:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The attack paralyzed a pipeline that moves 2.5 million barrels per day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Private-equity firm revives zombie fossil-fuel power plant to mine bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763789</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763789"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T16:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Power plant was left for dead until the cryptocurrency boom came along.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ford picks a name for its electric pickup truck: The F-150 Lightning]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763748</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763748"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T16:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SVT F-150 Lightning was a factory hot rod pickup in the 1990s.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony says PS5 could be difficult to find into 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763751</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763751"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T15:26:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Healthy demand, semiconductor shortage combine to keep the system hard to find.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s our first look at 2023’s electric Porsche Macan SUV]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763731</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763731"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T14:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Macan will share an electric platform with Audi's next A6 and Q6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Movie director says Capcom copied his monster for Resident Evil Village boss fight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149044</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-movie-director-says-capcom-copied-his-propellerhead-monster-for-resident-evil-village-boss-fight"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T13:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A movie director has accused Capcom of copying one of his monsters for a Resident Evil Village boss fight.
Dutch director Richard Raaphorst said the Sturm boss found in the recently-released Resident Evil Village is a "one-to-one" copy of a monster he created for his 2013 found footage horror film Frankenstein's Army.
Capcom failed to comment by press time.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A SpaceX booster now trails only 4 space shuttles in flight experience]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763707</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763707"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T12:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This particular first stage is approaching historic status.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Valheim mod lets you build some really big boats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149025</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-this-valheim-mod-lets-you-build-your-own-boat"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever felt like going on a big cruise ship around the mythical world of Valheim? Thanks to the power of modding, now you can, so get ready for some very large vessels.
ValheimRAFT is a mod by Sarcen that allows players to construct their own ships rather than simply use the pre-made ones available in vanilla Valheim. (If the name didn't give it away, it's inspired by the game Raft, a survival game in which you construct a boat from bits of debris.) I had a quick tinker with it and made a basic ghost…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Unclassified NSA Document on Cryptography in the 1970s]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/newly-unclassified-nsa-document-on-cryptography-in-the-1970s.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/newly-unclassified-nsa-document-on-cryptography-in-the-1970s.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a newly unclassified NSA history of its reaction to academic cryptography in the 1970s: &#8220;New Comes Out of the Closet: The Debate over Public Cryptography in the Inman Era,&#8221; Cryptographic Quarterly, Spring 1996, author still classified.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Automotive OS review: Under the hood with Google’s car OS]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1751715</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1751715"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AAOS nails the car platform fundamentals, but it needs more apps and features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft will now brand all its own games as "Ubisoft Originals"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149009</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-ubisoft-will-now-brand-all-its-own-games-as-ubisoft-originals"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T10:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assassin's Creed and Far Cry publisher Ubisoft will now brand all of its games made by internal studios as "Ubisoft Originals". 
The name first cropped up last week, when Ubisoft announced Tom Clancy's The Division: Heartland, a new free-to-play spin-off due later this year or early next.
When asked whether this label meant anything more than fancy new branding, a Ubisoft spokesperson told Eurogamer today that, "Moving forward 'The Ubisoft Original' mention is attached to all of Ubisoft's games created in-h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony expects it will continue to struggle to meet PS5 demand into 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149006</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-sony-expects-it-will-continue-to-struggle-to-meet-ps5-demand-into-2022"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T10:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The constrained supply of the PlayStation 5 will continue into 2022, Sony has warned.
The company's CFO, Hiroki Totoki, said Sony will struggle to meet demand even with a supply boost, Bloomberg reported (paywall).
As most know, the PS5 is incredibly hard to buy at the moment, with stock snapped up as soon as it goes on sale. The console has also been the focus of scalpers, who sell on for an inflated price. Retailers have struggled to prevent new consoles from getting into the hands of scalper groups, some…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monster Hunter Rise and Resident Evil 3 fuel another record year for Capcom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148978</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-monster-hunter-rise-and-resident-evil-3-fuel-another-record-year-for-capcom"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T09:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capcom has seen record profits for the fourth year in a row.
Revenue for the financial year ending 31st March 2021 was 95.3bn yen (£622m), up 16.8 percent from the previous year, with profit of 34.6bn yen (£226m), up 51.6 percent from the previous fiscal year)
Capcom pointed to the success of Monster Hunter Rise and the Resident Evil 3 remake, as well as sales growth for high margin back catalogue titles including Monster Hunter World: Iceborne and the Resident Evil 2 remake. Capcom said the PlayStation 5 a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[90's Kid Space Program]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2461/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2461/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Registration for Final Fantasy 7 battle royale, The First Soldier, is now open]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148951</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-09-registration-for-final-fantasy-7-battle-royale-the-first-soldier-is-now-open"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T13:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Registration to participate in the closed beta for Square Enix's upcoming battle royale, Final Fantasy 7 The First Soldier, is now open.
Prospective players have from now until 27th May 2021 to register their interest, although right now, the beta is restricted to players with 64-bit, 7.1+ Android phones with at least 3GB of memory available.
As is usually the case with these things, registering does not guarantee you a spot in the closed beta, but the sign-up page hints that it wants "tons of players" to g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumour suggests two new colourful DualSense controllers could go on sale "very soon"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148950</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-09-rumour-suggests-two-new-colourful-dualsense-controllers-could-go-on-sale-very-soon"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T13:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new rumour purports two new DualSense controllers could be coming to market "very soon".
According to AreaJugones - a Spanish-language site that has previously correctly leaked a PlayStation Plus freebie lineup ahead of confirmation from PlayStation - the new colour schemes deviate from the current white and black scheme to include shades of red and grey. 
Without photographic evidence, it's not possible to know precisely how the colours will be used, or what parts of the controller will be more colourful…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Careful, Wattson fans - her fence in Apex Legends is useless right now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148945</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-09-careful-wattson-fans-her-fence-in-apex-legends-is-useless-right-now"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T12:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Respawn has seemingly nerfed Wattson's electrified fence in Apex Legends.
As spotted and shared by Twitterer LilakeyLK, it looks as though the latest season has not only introduced a new Legend and competitive mode Arenas, but it's also made a tweak to one of Wattson's key defences... with an emphasis on "fence".
Previously, running into Wattson's fence would slow down an opposing player, but now it looks as though the slowdown and corresponding stun has been removed, essentially making the fence useless (t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New book Press Reset investigates the high human cost of game development]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763446</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763446"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T12:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beloved game-industry journo aims his lens at the little people making big video games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remnant: From the Ashes gets a free next-gen upgrade later this week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148944</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-09-remnant-from-the-ashes-gets-a-free-next-gen-upgrade-later-this-week"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remnant: From the Ashes will shortly receive a free next-gen update to "enhance both frame rate and resolution".
According to developer Gunfire Games, on 13th May players will "receive a free major upgrade patch that will add the option to run the game at 4K resolution at 30fps the PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X, or 1080p resolution at 60fps on both the PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S".
That's not all, either. On the same day, the game will also be added to the PC version of Xbox Game Pass - up until now…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Activision severs links with Call of Duty Ghost voice actor following misogynistic comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148943</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-09-activision-severs-links-with-call-of-duty-ghost-voice-actor-following-misogynistic-comments"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T11:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Activision has cut ties with Call of Duty: Modern Warfare's Ghost voice actor Jeff Leach following the dissemination of a video that compiles his misogynist comments.
The montage - which was shared online by streamers hitting back at Leach's derogatory statements - is described as containing "serious personalised intrusive sexism" and shows Leach using sexually explicit and aggressive language as well as personal insults. 
"In 2021, misogyny has no place," states a caption on the video. "Yet female gamers r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Amy Klobuchar just wrote 600 pages on antitrust]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763506</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763506"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T10:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Monopolies tend to have a lot of control, not just over consumers, but also over politics."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Die Hard's John McClane teased for Call of Duty: Warzone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148912</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-die-hards-john-mcclane-teased-for-call-of-duty-warzone"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T20:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 1980s action movie heroes are coming en masse to Warzone. After this week's tease that Rambo will be added to the battle royale, Activision has indicated Die Hard's John McClane is on his way, too.
Activision even created a website for a fictional air conditioning repair company called Nakatomi Duct Cleaning, offering its services in Verdansk.
The website says "A NAKATOMI CORP DIVISION MASTERING A/C DUCT CLEANING SINCE 1988", but the current Warzone map is set in 1984. Nah... I'm applying too much logic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capcom made a huge chalk lycan on a hill in Somerset to promote Resident Evil Village]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148911</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-capcom-made-a-huge-chalk-artwork-of-a-lycan-on-a-hill-in-somerset-to-promote-resident-evil-village"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T19:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, if you pottered along to the Mendip Hill near Cheddar, Somerset, you'd probably have caught a glimpse of something a bit off: a huge chalk artwork of a lycan.
Local press reported the strange image on Monday, 3rd May after it popped up overnight - and seemingly had no idea what it was about or who made it.
Its true nature was revealed when Resident Evil Village came out on Friday - it was a Capcom PR stunt. And a pretty cool one, I'll admit.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modder's Nier: Automata HD texture pack finally complete after four years of development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148910</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-modders-nier-automata-hd-texture-pack-finally-complete-after-four-years-of-development"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T18:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A modder has released their final Nier: Automata HD texture pack after four years of development.
GPUnity's texture pack mod began life soon after Nier: Automata launched on PC in March 2017. They've continued to work on the mod since then, and now, four years later, released the final version.
Nier: Automata's PC version is infamous for a raft of technical issues that were fixed by modders, including a constant stutter tick due to the game running at around 59 frames per second (this is something explored …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: The role-playing game’s afoot in charming dark comedy Murder Bury Win]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1759895</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1759895"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T18:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not an instant classic like  Clue,  but it's fun, very solid indie fare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sega: No plans for Lost Judgment on PC "at this time"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148909</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-sega-no-plans-for-lost-judgment-on-pc-at-this-time"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Sega announced Lost Judgment for PlayStation 5, PlayStation 4, Xbox Series X and S, and Xbox One - but there was no word of a PC version.
It seemed an odd omission - Tojo Dojo noticed the Yakuza spin-off sequel was briefly listed as coming to PC on the official countdown website that was home to the Lost Judgment announcement. Even after mention of PC was removed from the website, fans spotted mention of the Steam logo in the Lost Judgment website source code.
Unfortunately, it appears Lost Judgm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivian’s electric truck features include air compressor and AC outlets]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763611</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763611"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T17:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's got storage compartments galore, plus an extending truck bed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple brass discussed disclosing 128-million iPhone hack, then decided not to]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763592</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763592"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T16:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emails entered into Epic Games lawsuit show execs contradicting Apple talking points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance re-release on Nintendo Switch delayed at the last minute]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148906</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-baldurs-gate-dark-alliance-re-release-on-nintendo-switch-delayed-at-the-last-minute"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T15:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance's re-release on Nintendo Switch was delayed at the last minute.
The re-release of the much-loved 20 year-old action RPG went ahead as planned yesterday on Xbox One, where it costs a pricey £29.99, and PlayStation 4, where for some reason it costs a fiver cheaper at £24.99.
But even though the official Black Isle Studios Twitter page said yesterday that the Switch version would arrive in a couple of hours, the game failed to materialise on the Nintendo eShop.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Titanfall 2 Gauntlet world record broken twice in two weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148905</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-titanfall-2-gauntlet-world-record-broken-twice-in-a-week"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T15:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Titanfall 2 enjoying an Apex Legends-powered resurgence, so is its superb Gauntlet.
Respawn's wall-hopping assault course tasks players with completing one lap as quickly as possible - and nearly five years after Titanfall 2 came out, speedrunners are breaking world records again.
In October 2019, speedrunner Cash Mayo set an incredible time of 11.7 seconds, shaving a fraction off Mayo's previous world record of 11.9 seconds:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["The Yakuza series has been transformed into a turn-based RPG," says dev]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148879</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-the-yakuza-series-has-been-transformed-into-a-turn-based-rpg-says-dev"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T11:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking to IGN, Yakuza creator Toshihiro Nagoshi and producer Kazuki Hosokawa confirmed the plan for the two series:
"The Yakuza series has been transformed into a turn-based RPG. On the other hand, over the years, Ryu ga Gotoku Studio has accumulated resources and know-how of making flashy and exhilarating action games that are effortless to enjoy. We decided that we should let our signature action gameplay live on through Lost Judgment."
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil Village is off to a flyer on Steam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148875</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-resident-evil-village-is-off-to-a-flyer-on-steam"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil Village is off to a flyer on Steam.
It saw 101,726 peak concurrents on launch day, 7th May.
That makes Capcom's latest comfortably the biggest PC launch for any Resident Evil game. According to SteamCharts, Resident Evil 7 managed an all-time peak of 18,211 concurrents, Resident Evil 6 peaked with 11,836, and the most recent release, the Resident Evil 3 remake, hit 32,635. Only the Resident Evil 2 remake, which saw a concurrents peak of 74,024, comes close.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raven is trying to raise Call of Duty: Warzone's skill ceiling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148870</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-call-of-duty-warzone-developer-says-its-battle-royale-is-close-to-a-balance-homeostasis"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T10:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Warzone developer Raven has said it is close to a "balance homeostasis", where most weapon options are "at the very least viable" - leaving it to focus on raising the skill ceiling of the game.
The developer shared its balance change philosophy as part of the patch notes for a Warzone update that went live this week.
Raven spoke openly about the difficulty it faces making sweeping changes to the Warzone meta, as popular guns are inevitably affected.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It began as an AI-fueled dungeon game. Then it got much darker]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763513</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763513"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T10:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI algorithm created disturbing stories, including sex scenes involving children.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sniper Ghost Warrior Contracts 2 gets PS5 delay due to "unforeseen technical issues"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148855</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-sniper-ghost-warrior-contracts-2-gets-ps5-delay-due-to-unforeseen-technical-issues"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T21:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CI Games has announced a delay for the PlayStation 5 version of its upcoming long-distance shooter Sniper Ghost Warrior Contracts 2, resulting from "unforeseen technical issues".
Sniper Ghost Warrior Contracts 2 - which features a "dramatic single-player campaign set in modern day Middle East" - was originally due on PlayStation 5 on 4th June, arriving alongside versions for PS4, Xbox One, Xbox X/S and PC. However, despite the PS5 edition's delay to a currently unspecified future point, other platforms will…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 “Sun Valley” will do away with Windows 95 era icons]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763533</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763533"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T21:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The results are more subtle than you might expect from a 25+ year visual update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: COVID Relief Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/friday-squid-blogging-covid-relief-funds.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/friday-squid-blogging-covid-relief-funds.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T21:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A town in Japan built a giant squid statue with its COVID relief grant.
One local told the Chunichi Shimbun newspaper that while the statue may be effective in the long run, the money could have been used for &#8220;urgent support,&#8221; such as for medical staff and long-term care facilities.
But a spokesperson for the town told Fuji News Network that the statue would be a tourist attraction and part of a long term strategy to help promote Noto&#8217;s famous flying squid.

I am impressed by the town&#821…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony faces lawsuit over alleged “monopoly pricing” of PlayStation downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763530</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763530"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T20:19:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proposed class action says Sony's moves have increased prices for PlayStation games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Returnal reinstating pre-rollback fixes in new patch tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148850</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-returnal-reinstating-pre-rollback-fixes-in-new-patch-tomorrow"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T20:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Housemarque is releasing a new patch for PlayStation 5-exclusive roguelite Returnal tomorrow, 8th May, which will, among other things, reinstate all pre-rollback fixes that briefly went live earlier this week.
On Wednesday, Housemarque was forced to pull Returnal's 1.3.3 patch after players began reporting it was corrupting save games. The developer later released version 1.3.4, which rolled back to Returnal's most recent stable build - a move that enabled some affected players to resume their pro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[96% of US users opt out of app tracking in iOS 14.5, analytics find]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763464</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763464"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the first data on user behavior exceeds advertisers' worst fears.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ajit Pai promised cheaper Internet—real prices rose 19 percent instead]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763472</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763472"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Home-Internet prices rose four times faster than inflation in Trump era.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skullgirls 2nd Encore's next DLC fighter Umbrella has a ravenous sentient brolly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148849</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-skullgirls-2nd-encores-next-dlc-fighter-umbrella-has-a-ravenous-sentient-brolly"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Hidden Variable has unveiled the latest DLC character to join the roster of acclaimed fighters Skullgirls 2nd Encore and the free-to-play Skullgirls Mobile: the sou'westered, be-wellied Umbrella and her sentient brolly chum, Hungern.
Umbrella, the second DLC character to arrive as part of Skullgirls 2nd Encore's season pass (following on from March's Annie), is described as a small, slow character with limited movement that's able to take some "big swings" thanks Hungern.
Indeed, while the perpetu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Autopilot director contradicts Musk’s self-driving timeline]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763422</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763422"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk described full autonomy as "basically a solved problem" in 2016.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy B. Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acclaimed post-apocalyptic city builder Frostpunk is heading to mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148841</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-acclaimed-post-apocalyptic-city-builder-frostpunk-is-heading-to-mobile"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer 11 Bit Studios' superb post-apocalyptic city builder Frostpunk is coming to iOS and Android devices "later this year".
Frostpunk initially launched on PC in 2018 before making its way to Xbox and PlayStation the following year. It's a fascinating, frequently gruelling, and wonderfully atmospheric experience, delivering a captivating blend of brutal survival sim, city builder, and rich narrative as players attempt to survive - through the slow expansion their settlement, and with plenty of tough mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google wants people to use 2FA, so it’s just going to turn it on for them]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763423</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763423"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-tech-savvy users always use the defaults, and the default will soon be 2FA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook and Big Pharma exploited disease “awareness” for personalized marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763427</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763427"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visiting medical sites, patient support groups, and more feed the algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did our ancestors kill all the island megafauna?]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763424</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763424"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T15:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Study adds data to a long-running argument.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Contributors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDPR in talks to use The Witcher 3 mods in official next-gen version]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148822</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-the-witcher-3s-next-gen-version-might-use-fan-made-mods"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T14:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ray-tracing, faster load times and more. But rather unexpectedly, it seems some of these improvements are coming from the community, as CDPR has confirmed that it is in talks with those who made mods for the 2015 game. 
Kotaku spotted that mod creator Halk Hogan, responsible for The Witcher 3 HD Reworked project, had announced he'd received an "official message from CDPR about cooperation", and that "it's very likely HDRP will be included in the official next generation update". CDPR then confirmed to Kotak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is an Edge Location in AWS? A Simple Explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8740</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/what-is-an-edge-location-in-aws-a-simple-explanation/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS edge locations are designed to deliver services with as less latency as possible. Learn more about edge locations, use cases, and where they might make sense for your organization.
The post What is an Edge Location in AWS? A Simple Explanation appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost Judgment leaks on PlayStation Store ahead of official reveal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148717</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-lost-judgment-leaks-on-playstation-store-ahead-of-official-reveal"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Sega has officially announced Lost Judgment, the Judgment sequel due out globally 24th September 2021 on PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, Xbox Series X and S.
Developer Ryu Ga Gotoku Studio said in addition to Kamurocho, fans will be able to adventure to the scenic port city of Yokohama. One of the most important new locations is a high school, with a "highly detailed" interior. The trailer is below:
The developers have leaned heavily on the fast-paced action portion of the original game. The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valheim modders are fleshing out the game's unused biomes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148799</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-valheim-modders-are-fleshing-out-the-games-unused-biomes"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you've finished all the biomes and bosses currently available in Valheim - what now? Well, you could wait for the next official update from Iron Gate: but the next biome is quite a few updates away, so you may be waiting a while to explore the Mistlands in all their glory. 
Alternatively, you can just install a bunch of mods. Here's a video of me exploring a rejuvenated Ashlands, and running away performing a tactical retreat when I realised that the enemies are actually quite difficult. Thank goodness I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching Cybersecurity to Children]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/teaching-cybersecurity-to-children.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/teaching-cybersecurity-to-children.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T13:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new draft of an Australian educational curriculum proposes teaching children as young as five cybersecurity:
The proposed curriculum aims to teach five-year-old children &#8212; an age at which Australian kids first attend school &#8212; not to share information such as date of birth or full names with strangers, and that they should consult parents or guardians before entering personal information online.
Six-and-seven-year-olds will be taught how to use usernames and passwords, and the pitfalls of click…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM creates the world’s first 2 nm chip]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763407</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763407"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T11:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM's new 2 nm process offers transistor density similar to TSMC's next-gen 3 nm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unsolved mysteries of the Warhammer 40k universe with loremaster Dan Abnett]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762186</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762186"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T11:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best-selling author goes deep—like, real deep—on wild and crazy Warhammer questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Hutchinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why hasn’t Waymo expanded its driverless service? Here’s my theory]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762459</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762459"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suburban ride-hailing is a lousy business to be in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy B. Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vaccinated]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2460/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2460/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What cats’ love of boxes and squares can tell us about their visual perception]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762974</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762974"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T21:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Vision has evolved to answer questions having to do with boundaries and contours."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9,000 fliers may have had reused swabs jammed up their noses in Indonesia]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763266</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763266"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T20:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five workers were arrested for washing and reusing cotton swabs for testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Story of Colossus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/the-story-of-colossus.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/the-story-of-colossus.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nice video of a talk by Chris Shore on the history of Colossus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Spectre-Like Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/new-spectre-like-attacks.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/new-spectre-like-attacks.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T15:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There&#8217;s new research that demonstrates security vulnerabilities in all of the AMD and Intel chips with micro-op caches, including the ones that were specifically engineered to be resistant to the Spectre/Meltdown attacks of three years ago.
Details:
The new line of attacks exploits the micro-op cache: an on-chip structure that speeds up computing by storing simple commands and allowing the processor to fetch them quickly and early in the speculative execution process, as the team explains in a writeup…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Portals Are an Anti-Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8725</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/developer-portals-are-an-anti-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer portals can be used to enforce standardization and to enable multi-cloud use cases. But they also have some serious issues and should be avoided in most cases. 
The post Developer Portals Are an Anti-Pattern appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 2020]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2459/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2459/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Remotely Hacked from a Drone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/tesla-remotely-hacked-from-a-drone.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/tesla-remotely-hacked-from-a-drone.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:41:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an impressive hack:
Security researchers Ralf-Philipp Weinmann of Kunnamon, Inc. and Benedikt Schmotzle of Comsecuris GmbH have found remote zero-click security vulnerabilities in an open-source software component (ConnMan) used in Tesla automobiles that allowed them to compromise parked cars and control their infotainment systems over WiFi. It would be possible for an attacker to unlock the doors and trunk, change seat positions, both steering and acceleration modes &#8212; in short, pretty much wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying the Person Behind Bitcoin Fog]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/identifying-the-person-behind-bitcoin-fog.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/identifying-the-person-behind-bitcoin-fog.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T14:36:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The person behind the Bitcoin Fog was identified and arrested. Bitcoin Fog was an anonymization service: for a fee, it mixed a bunch of people&#8217;s bitcoins up so that it was hard to figure out where any individual coins came from. It ran for ten years.
Identifying the person behind Bitcoin Fog serves as an illustrative example of how hard it is to be anonymous online in the face of a competent police investigation:
Most remarkable, however, is the IRS&#8217;s account of tracking down Sterlingov using th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bubble Wrap]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2458/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2458/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: On Squid Coloration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/friday-squid-blogging-on-squid-coloration.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/friday-squid-blogging-on-squid-coloration.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T21:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nice excerpt from Martin Wallin&#8217;s book Squid.
As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.
Read my blog posting guidelines here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DynamoDB vs. MongoDB: A Comparison and How to Choose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8713</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/dynamodb-vs-mongodb-a-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T14:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A real world comparison of two wildly successful modern replacements for traditional database systems.
The post DynamoDB vs. MongoDB: A Comparison and How to Choose appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Scanlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serious MacOS Vulnerability Patched]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/serous-macos-vulnerability-patched.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/serous-macos-vulnerability-patched.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T12:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple just patched a MacOS vulnerability that bypassed malware checks.
The flaw is akin to a front entrance that&#8217;s barred and bolted effectively, but with a cat door at the bottom that you can easily toss a bomb through. Apple mistakenly assumed that applications will always have certain specific attributes. Owens discovered that if he made an application that was really just a script—code that tells another program what do rather than doing it itself—and didn&#8217;t include a standard application me…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After the Pandemic]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2457/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2457/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying People Through Lack of Cell Phone Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/identifying-people-through-lack-of-cell-phone-use.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/identifying-people-through-lack-of-cell-phone-use.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T11:07:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this entertaining story of French serial criminal Rédoine Faïd and his jailbreaking ways, there&#8217;s this bit about cell phone surveillance:
After Faïd&#8217;s helicopter breakout, 3,000 police officers took part in the manhunt. According to the 2019 documentary La Traque de Rédoine Faïd, detective units scoured records of cell phones used during his escape, isolating a handful of numbers active at the time that went silent shortly thereafter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sun Also Crashes: Keeping Current]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8701</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/the-sun-also-crashes-keeping-current/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you let the tech you’re skilled in become the cornerstone of your identity, you limit future career possibilities. Here’s what to do instead
The post The Sun Also Crashes: Keeping Current appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confidence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/confidence/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/confidence/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Amazon Athena? An Introduction and Walkthrough]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8676</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/what-is-amazon-athena-an-introduction-and-walkthrough/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Amazon Athena right for your organization? Learn about the pros and cons of the serverless query service to see if it makes sense for your use case.
The post What is Amazon Athena? An Introduction and Walkthrough appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect Fit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/perfect-fit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/perfect-fit/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.21: Metrics Stability hits GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/23/kubernetes-release-1.21-metrics-stability-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/23/kubernetes-release-1.21-metrics-stability-ga/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Han Kang (Google), Elana Hashman (Red Hat)
Kubernetes 1.21 marks the graduation of the metrics stability framework and along with it, the first officially supported stable metrics. Not only do stable metrics come with supportability guarantees, the metrics stability framework brings escape hatches that you can use if you encounter problematic metrics.
See the list of stable Kubernetes metrics here
What are stable metrics and why do we need them?
A stable metric is one which, from a consumption poin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Evolving Kubernetes networking with the Gateway API]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/22/evolving-kubernetes-networking-with-the-gateway-api/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/22/evolving-kubernetes-networking-with-the-gateway-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Mark Church (Google), Harry Bagdi (Kong), Daneyon Hanson (Red Hat), Nick Young (VMware), Manuel Zapf (Traefik Labs)
The Ingress resource is one of the many Kubernetes success stories. It created a diverse ecosystem of Ingress controllers which were used across hundreds of thousands of clusters in a standardized and consistent way. This standardization helped users adopt Kubernetes. However, five years after the creation of Ingress, there are signs of fragmentation into different but strikingly simi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[S3’s Durability Guarantees Aren’t What You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8662</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/s3s-durability-guarantees-arent-what-you-think/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[S3 has insanely generous data durability guarantees. Even so, read the fine print, and you’ll realize that S3 doesn’t remove the need for backups.
The post S3&#8217;s Durability Guarantees Aren&#8217;t What You Think appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Graceful Node Shutdown Goes Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/21/graceful-node-shutdown-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/21/graceful-node-shutdown-beta/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: David Porter (Google), Mrunal Patel (Red Hat), and Tim Bannister (The Scale Factory)
Graceful node shutdown, beta in 1.21, enables kubelet to gracefully evict pods during a node shutdown.
Kubernetes is a distributed system and as such we need to be prepared for inevitable failures — nodes will fail, containers might crash or be restarted, and - ideally - your workloads will be able to withstand these catastrophic events.
One of the common classes of issues are workload failures on node shutdown or …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Annotating Kubernetes Services for Humans]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/20/annotating-k8s-for-humans/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/20/annotating-k8s-for-humans/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Richard Li, Ambassador Labs
Have you ever been asked to troubleshoot a failing Kubernetes service and struggled to find basic information about the service such as the source repository and owner?
One of the problems as Kubernetes applications grow is the proliferation of services. As the number of services grows, developers start to specialize working with specific services. When it comes to troubleshooting, however, developers need to be able to find the source, understand the service and dependen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Defining Network Policy Conformance for Container Network Interface (CNI) providers]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/20/defining-networkpolicy-conformance-cni-providers/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/20/defining-networkpolicy-conformance-cni-providers/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Matt Fenwick (Synopsys), Jay Vyas (VMWare), Ricardo Katz, Amim Knabben (Loadsmart), Douglas Schilling Landgraf (Red Hat), Christopher Tomkins (Tigera)
Special thanks to Tim Hockin and Bowie Du (Google), Dan Winship and Antonio Ojea (Red Hat),
Casey Davenport and Shaun Crampton (Tigera), and Abhishek Raut and Antonin Bas (VMware) for
being supportive of this work, and working with us to resolve issues in different Container Network Interfaces (CNIs) over time.
A brief conversation around &quot;node …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing Indexed Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/19/introducing-indexed-jobs/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/19/introducing-indexed-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aldo Culquicondor (Google)
Once you have containerized a non-parallel Job,
it is quite easy to get it up and running on Kubernetes without modifications to
the binary. In most cases, when running parallel distributed Jobs, you had
to set a separate system to partition the work among the workers. For
example, you could set up a task queue to assign one work item to each
Pod or multiple items
to each Pod until the queue is emptied.
The Kubernetes 1.21 release introduces a new field to control Job comp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Volume Health Monitoring Alpha Update]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/16/volume-health-monitoring-alpha-update/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/16/volume-health-monitoring-alpha-update/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Xing Yang (VMware)
The CSI Volume Health Monitoring feature, originally introduced in 1.19 has undergone a large update for the 1.21 release.
Why add Volume Health Monitoring to Kubernetes?
Without Volume Health Monitoring, Kubernetes has no knowledge of the state of the underlying volumes of a storage system after a PVC is provisioned and used by a Pod. Many things could happen to the underlying storage system after a volume is provisioned in Kubernetes. For example, the volume could be deleted by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/meeting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/meeting/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development satire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Three Tenancy Models For Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/15/three-tenancy-models-for-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/15/three-tenancy-models-for-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Ryan Bezdicek (Medtronic), Jim Bugwadia (Nirmata), Tasha Drew (VMware), Fei Guo (Alibaba), Adrian Ludwin (Google)
Kubernetes clusters are typically used by several teams in an organization. In other cases, Kubernetes may be used to deliver applications to end users requiring segmentation and isolation of resources across users from different organizations. Secure sharing of Kubernetes control plane and worker node resources allows maximizing productivity and saving costs in both cases.
The Kubernet…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning is a Marvelously Executed Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8634</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/machine-learning-is-a-marvelously-executed-scam/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning is a Marvelously Executed Scam I&#8217;ve joked periodically that machine learning (or &#8220;ML&#8221;) adherents claim to be able to sort through vast quantities of data and find absolutely anything except a viable business model. I&#8217;d like to revisit that with a clarification: They also apparently can&#8217;t tell a story around what they do [&#8230;]
The post Machine Learning is a Marvelously Executed Scam appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Local Storage: Storage Capacity Tracking, Distributed Provisioning and Generic Ephemeral Volumes hit Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/14/local-storage-features-go-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/14/local-storage-features-go-beta/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Patrick Ohly (Intel)
The &quot;generic ephemeral
volumes&quot;
and &quot;storage capacity
tracking&quot;
features in Kubernetes are getting promoted to beta in Kubernetes
1.21. Together with the distributed provisioning
support
in the CSI external-provisioner, development and deployment of
Container Storage Interface (CSI) drivers which manage storage locally
on a node become a lot easier.
This blog post explains how such drivers worked before and how these
features can be used to make drivers simp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine 3.10.9, 3.11.11 and 3.12.7 released]]></title>
        <id>https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.10.9-3.11.11-3.12.7-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.10.9-3.11.11-3.12.7-released.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine Linux]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alpine Linux News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine 3.13.5 released]]></title>
        <id>https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.13.5-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.13.5-released.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine Linux]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alpine Linux News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>