<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-21T00:46:24.464Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.7.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What mimes interacting with invisible objects says about visual perception]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766305</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766305"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T23:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mimes "make us feel like we’re aware of an object just by seeming to interact with it."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snap debuts true AR glasses that show the potential (and limitations) of AR]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766403</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766403"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Limited availability, battery life, and FOV make for a curiosity, not a product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google announces its first-ever physical retail store]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766390</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766390"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's New York City Campus will be home to its first retail store, at 15th and 9th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need for annual COVID shots may hinge on how many get vaccinated now, Fauci says]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766436</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766436"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T21:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In new interviews, Fauci discusses the future of COVID-19 vaccinations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is (finally) killing off Internet Explorer entirely]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766388</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766388"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T18:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internet Explorer lives on in Edge IE Mode, LTSC Windows 10, and Windows Server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mandatory opt-out, data breach notification part of new privacy bill]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766347</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766347"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T16:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Senators reintroduce bill as scrutiny of social media ramps up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Returnal's latest patch once again aiming to make more Deceased Scouts appear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150656</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-20-returnals-latest-patch-once-again-aiming-to-make-more-deceased-scouts-appear"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T16:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Housemarque has released a new patch for its PlayStation-5-exclusive sci-fi roguelite Returnal, this one aiming to increase the number of Deceased Scouts appearing during player run-throughs, among other tweaks and bug fixes.
Deceased Scouts, in the very possible scenario you've yet to see one, are supposed show up while playing Returnal with an online connection, and represent other players who've died while attempting to best the horrors present on the planet Atropos. The idea is that players ca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome’s RSS-powered “Follow” button is like a rebooted Google Reader]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766325</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766325"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T16:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For now, it's an Android "experiment" that might get "a broader rollout in Chrome."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We drove the Audi RS e-tron GT for an hour; here’s what we learned]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766309</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766309"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T16:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ars got to spend some time with a preproduction car in Virginia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frontier knowingly sold Internet speeds it can’t deliver, FTC lawsuit says]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766326</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766326"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T15:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontier capped actual DSL speeds to levels below its advertised rates, FTC says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GTA 5 speedrunner beats game without taking damage - and in only 9 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150642</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-20-gta-5-speedrunner-beats-game-without-taking-damage-and-in-only-9-hours"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T15:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for a look at some truly impressive gaming skills, as a speedrunner has managed to beat the whole of GTA 5 without taking any damage: and he did it all in nine hours. 
The feat was achieved by UnNameD, who uploaded a three-part video of the run to YouTube on Sunday. According to the description this was UnNameD's 48th attempt at completing the run, in which he had "1HP, no Trevor ability, no armours, 0 deaths". UnNameD used the One Hit KO mod to complete the run, which kills the player immediately if t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starfield release date reportedly late 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150647</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-20-starfield-release-date-reportedly-late-2022"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T15:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starfield launches late 2022, according to Bloomberg's Jason Schreier.
Schreier tweeted to say Bethesda plans to tease this release date at E3 next month.
Bethesda announced Starfield at E3 2018, calling the game its "next generation" first-person sci-fi RPG.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pfizer’s COVID vaccine can stay in normal fridge for up to a month, FDA says]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766329</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766329"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T15:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Change extends fridge storage from 5 days to a month—significantly aiding logistics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like Ni No Kuni 2 is coming to Nintendo Switch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2147809</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-04-30-looks-like-ni-no-kuni-2-is-coming-to-nintendo-switch"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE 20/5/21: Bandai Namco has now officially confirmed Ni No Kuni 2: Revenant Kingdom for Nintendo Switch, and given it a release date of 17th September.
As detailed in the earlier ratings board leak, below, this will be the Prince's Edition version of the game with both of its major DLCs included: The Lair of the Lost Lord and The Tale of a Timeless Tome. You'll also get a collection of items, including a "Proper Tidy" ring themed around the game's fairy helper.
Here's a look at all that in action:
Read…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bizarro Banking Trojan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/bizarro-banking-trojan.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/bizarro-banking-trojan.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:13:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bizarro is a new banking trojan that is stealing financial information and crypto wallets.
…the program can be delivered in a couple of ways­ — either via malicious links contained within spam emails, or through a trojanized app. Using these sneaky methods, trojan operators will implant the malware onto a target device, where it will install a sophisticated backdoor that “contains more than 100 commands and allows the attackers to steal online banking account credentials,” the researchers write.
The backdoo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valheim sells 6.8m copies, expected to shift another 1m by July]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150564</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-20-valheim-sells-6-8m-copies-expected-to-shift-another-1m-by-july"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been a while since we checked in on Valheim's sales figures: the game exploded out of nowhere in February, managing to shift a staggering 4m copies in only three weeks and reaching the 5m milestone in March. Well, we now have an update, as publisher Embracer Group has released its full year financial report. And yep, it looks like Valheim really helped boost those numbers. 
According to the report, Valheim has now sold over 6.8m copies. Embracer Group doesn't think the success will stop there, however,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PES 2021 won't get updated national team squads until Euro 2020 hits the knockout stage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150565</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-20-pes-2021-wont-get-updated-national-team-squads-until-euro-2020-hits-the-knockout-stage"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Konami has confirmed PES 2021 won't get updated national team squads until Euro 2020 hits the knockout stage.
Data pack 7.0, due out next month towards the end of June to coincide with the tournament's advance into the knockout stage, adds updated national team squads based on the final 26 chosen players for each team, and increases squad sizes from 23 players to 26.
Ideally this update would best go live before the tournament kicks off on 11th June, but that hasn't been possible "due to time constraints an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What PlayStation’s “monopoly” lawsuits get wrong about digital game sales]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766234</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766234"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T10:45:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding download options from traditional retailers doesn't seem to affect prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DC announces Injustice animated movie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150557</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-20-dc-announces-injustice-animated-movie"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T10:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DC has announced an Injustice animated movie.
Confirmation comes as part of a list of bonus features for the upcoming animated movie Batman: The Long Halloween, Part Two. The bonus in question is "a sneak peek at the next DC animated movie - an advanced look at Injustice".
That's all we know for now. Injustice is of course a series of DC-flavoured fighting games from Mortal Kombat developer NetherRealm. Injustice: Gods Among Us came out in 2013, before a sequel, Injustice 2, came out in May 2017.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EA opening new studio led by former Shadow of Mordor exec]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150545</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-20-ea-opens-new-studio-led-by-former-shadow-of-mordor-exec"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T10:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following its acquisition of British developer Codemasters, it looks like EA is once again expanding its portfolio of developers - as the company is launching a new studio led by former Monolith Productions VP Kevin Stephens. 
The studio doesn't yet have a name, but we do know it will be based in the Seattle area and will work on an open-world action-adventure game (via GamesIndustry.biz). During his time at Monolith Stephens oversaw projects such as Middle-earth: Shadow of Mordor and Middle-earth: Shadow o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Silver founds new Free Radical Design to work on TimeSplitters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150535</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-20-deep-silver-has-founded-a-new-free-radical-design-to-work-on-timesplitters"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T09:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TimeSplitters will return, courtesy of a fresh studio named Free Radical Design.
This Free Radical Design will be a new developer owned by publisher Deep Silver, with several key figures from the original developer.
In a statement published on Twitter this morning, Deep Silver said the company would be "headed up" by TimeSplitters co-creators Steve Ellis and David Doak, who were part of the core team from the original Free Radical Design's heyday. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If you want Rambo and John McClane in Call of Duty: Warzone and Black Ops Cold War, expect to spend £33.58 worth of COD Points]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150537</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-20-if-you-want-rambo-and-john-mcclane-in-call-of-duty-warzone-and-black-ops-cold-war-expect-to-spend-gbp33-58-worth-of-cod-points"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T09:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rambo and John McClane are now in Call of Duty: Warzone and Black Ops Cold War and, as expected, they cost 2400 COD Points - each.
Both '80s action movie heroes come in a bundle of their own that includes other gubbins to sweeten the deal, such as weapon skins, finisher moves, watches, charms, emblems, calling cards and consumables.
But the fact remains it's impossible to buy the Rambo and John McClane outside of these bundles. There is no option to unlock the skins through gameplay in either the free-to-pl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Warzone substantially reduces Stopping Power spawn rates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150522</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-20-call-of-duty-warzone-substantially-reduces-stopping-power-spawn-rates"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raven has made a significant change to Call of Duty: Warzone with its mid-season three update: Stopping Power field upgrade spawn rates have been reduced substantially across all modes.
It's a change the Warzone community has called on Raven to make for some time. This field upgrade lets you reload your gun with stopping power rounds that deal extra damage. In a game already lethal enough, Stopping Power was used to laser enemies to death in the blink of an eye.
Explaining the decision to make Stopping Powe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This is Ford’s first electric pickup truck, the F-150 Lightning]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766120</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766120"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T01:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The standard-range electric F-150 will start at just under $40,000 before tax credits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android 12 at Google I/O: Hints of the redesign in the beta, lots of news]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766029</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766029"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T00:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O features a big Android info dump, but not much working code right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Before ruining millions of vaccines, Emergent failed inspections, raked in cash]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766272</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766272"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T22:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tens of millions of J&J and AstraZeneca doses are still in limbo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: The Nevers makes abrupt turn in disorienting midseason finale]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765374</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765374"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T22:15:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We briefly wondered if HBO Max was accidentally airing an entirely different series]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple rolls out a slew of new accessibility features to iPhone, Watch, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766111</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766111"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T21:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New services include sign-language tech support and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 vulnerabilities under attack give hackers full control of Android devices]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766173</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766173"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T20:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google updates a 2-week-old security bulletin to say some vulnerabilities were 0-days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semiconductor shortages continue to worsen, causing record order delays]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766153</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766153"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T20:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automakers are expecting $110 billion in lost sales this year due to shortages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T overcharged Washington, DC, for 5 years, must pay $1.5 million, AG says]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766102</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766102"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T18:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DC announces $1.5M settlement after alleging AT&T "knowingly" violated contract.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HBO Max with ads: $10/mo starting in June, and guess what it won’t include]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766096</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766096"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T18:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Similar to Hulu's price options; other stream-with-ads options are much less.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Square Enix calls Outriders its "next big franchise" as it reaches 3.5m unique players]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150484</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-19-square-enix-calls-outriders-its-next-big-franchise-as-it-reaches-3-5m-unique-players"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T17:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer People Can Fly's co-op-focussed looter-shooter Outriders received a bit of a mixed critical reception at launch, but publisher Square Enix seems pretty happy with the public response, saying the game is "poised to be the company's next big franchise" after 3.5m unique players flocked to the experience in its first month.
Things didn't exactly start off smoothly for Outriders when it launched on PlayStation, Xbox, and PC at the start of April, of course, with server woes leaving many players unable…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This is Kia’s next electric car: The 300-mile EV6]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766083</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766083"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T17:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is the first Kia to use the brand's new 800-volt platform for electric cars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supermassive's third Dark Pictures Anthology horror House of Ashes gets new teaser trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150471</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-19-third-dark-pictures-anthology-horror-outing-house-of-ashes-gets-new-teaser-trailer"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T16:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're two games into developer Supermassive's Dark Pictures Anthology horror series, with a third - titled House of Ashes - on the not-too-distant horizon. Supermassive says it'll be revealing more on this latest instalment next week, but first, there's a new teaser trailer.
House of Ashes, as befits the Dark Pictures anthology format, offers up a new standalone story with its own particular take on fear. Gone is the nautical horror of the series' first outing, Man of Medan, and the time-hopping witch-y ter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Want improved fast travel in Skyward Sword HD? Buy this $25 Amiibo!]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766030</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766030"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Other Switch games also hide some key gameplay features behind figurines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone has bid more than $2 million for the first New Shepard seat]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766028</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766028"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T15:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bidding will culminate in a live auction on June 12.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bubble bursts overnight, dragging down stocks]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766031</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1766031"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T15:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After stunning run-up over the past year, cryptocurrencies are tanking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASCAR and F1 are coming to Rocket League Season 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2143023</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-03-28-nascar-and-f1-are-coming-to-rocket-league-season-3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T15:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE 19/5/21: Rocket League has now detailed its Formula 1 Fan Pack, to launch on 20th May. It includes an F1 2021 car with unique decal, ten further F1 team decals plus Pirelli wheels - and you can see a glimpse of it in action below:
ORIGINAL STORY 28/3/21: Rocket League's "high octane" Season 3 will drop, for free, on 7th April, 2021.
"Players, start your engines! Rocket League Season 3 is fueled up and ready to roll on April 7!" developer Psyonix teases in the description of a new video on YouTube. "G…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not-E3 event Summer Game Fest details live show, extensive publisher line-up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150444</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-19-not-e3-event-summer-game-fest-details-live-show-extensive-publisher-line-up"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation, EA and Xbox will take part in Geoff Keighley's definitely-not-E3 Summer Game Fest event, which will broadcast an announcements show on Thursday 10th June at 6pm UK time.
Mark your calendars for the usual flurry of world premieres, as well as a musical performance by Weezer.
While absolutely not part of the official E3 (which will exist digitally this year via a web portal/app) Summer Game Fest will take place at roughly the same time.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New CEO Onboarding at AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8819</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/new-ceo-onboarding-at-aws/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Selipsky is returning to AWS as its new CEO. I fill him in on some of the things he missed while he was gone. 
The post New CEO Onboarding at AWS appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite's NBA tie-in boasts a basketball back bling you can play with]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150424</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-19-fortnites-nba-collaboration-lets-you-play-basketball-with-someones-back-bling"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite has hosted football clubs, American football clubs and - most recently - Neymar Jr. Now, it's the turn of basketball, and the NBA.
A collection of NBA outfits join Fortnite this week on Friday's shop reset (that's 1am on Saturday here in the UK). As with previous sports skins, each outfit will let you customise it with licensed logos for all of the league's teams.
Perhaps more fun, though, is the Mini Hoop Back Bling item - which looks like it'll let you take a basketball shot when standing with so…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Several Cyberpunk 2077 lawsuits have been rolled into one]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150422</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-19-cyberpunk-2077-lawsuits"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T13:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The launch of Cyberpunk 2077 back in December 2020 was, by most accounts, a bit of a car crash. The game's poor performance on base consoles led to the game being pulled from the PlayStation Store, and was followed by a significant slump in CD Projekt's stock price. 
This led to a bunch of angry investors, many of whom filed class action lawsuits against CD Projekt for allegedly misleading them over the state of the game. So many, in fact, that several lawsuits have now been rolled into one big lawsuit by a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2021 iPad Pro review: More of the same—but way, way faster thanks to M1]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765495</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765495"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T13:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the Marvel movie sequel of Apple products: The same formula but bigger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Falconeer lands on PlayStation, Switch in August]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150415</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-19-the-falconeer-lands-on-playstation-switch-in-august"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It'll launch on those platforms in a new Warrior Edition, which includes all previous updates and add-ons, plus a new expansion: Edge of the World.
Edge of the World is described as a "significant" update to the game, with new quests, map locations, story and items. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First look at Die Hard's John McClane in Call of Duty: Warzone and Black Ops Cold War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150409</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-19-first-look-at-die-hards-john-mcclane-in-call-of-duty-warzone-and-black-ops-cold-war"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T12:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Die Hard's John McClane hits Call of Duty: Warzone and Black Ops Cold War tomorrow, but we can see his in-game model now.
Once you've downloaded Black Ops Cold War's latest update, which prepares the game for the mid-season three refresh, you can see McClane as a "coming soon" operator.
I'm not sure what I was expecting! Call of Duty's McClane looks a lot like McClane from the first Die Hard film, which is what you want, really.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Censorship and Surveillance in China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/apple-censorship-and-surveillance-in-china.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/apple-censorship-and-surveillance-in-china.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good investigative reporting on how Apple is participating in and assisting with Chinese censorship and surveillance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch Online limps past 100 game milestone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150381</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-19-nintendo-switch-online-limps-past-100-game-milestone"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo has announced five more retro games for its Switch Online catalogue, bringing the service's overall total of NES and SNES classics to 104. 
But while Nintendo noted it had passed the 100 game milestone, Nintendo fans are less impressed with the games on offer. 
May's list of additions includes SNES games Caveman Ninja (also known as Joe & Mac), Magical Drop 2, Super Baseball Simulator 1.000 and Spanky's Quest, plus Ninja JaJaMaru-kun for NES. Here's a look at all of those in action:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Games Done Quick 2021 reveals full schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150363</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-19-summer-games-done-quick-2021-reveals-full-schedule"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T10:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watching speedrunners strut their stuff in Summer Games Done Quick always makes for entertaining viewing, and this year's event looks like another banger. There's GeoGuessr runs, blindfolded Super Mario 64, and even a Destiny 2 Deep Stone Crypt raid. And as usual, it's all for a good cause. 
Summer Games Done Quick 2021 is scheduled to take place between 4th-11th July, with a packed-out timetable and a real mix of games. There's Dragon Age: Inquisition, Pikmin 3 Deluxe, Nintendogs, Outer Wilds, Dishonored, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix's new Resident Evil: Infinite Darkness trailer has vomiting zombies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150353</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-19-netflixs-new-resident-evil-infinite-darkness-trailer-has-vomiting-zombies"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T09:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil: Infinite Darkness, the new CGI series from Netflix, has today received a new trailer and an 8th July release date. 
Our best look yet at the Leon S. Kennedy-starring show, this two-minute montage has vomiting zombies, zombie rats and a hulking big thing which may be the series' big bad. 
Let's take a look:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War update adds sniper flinch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150356</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-19-big-call-of-duty-black-ops-cold-war-update-adds-sniper-flinch"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T09:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Treyarch has added sniper flinch to Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War as part of the game's latest big update.
Black Ops Cold War Multiplayer fans have called for some form of sniper flinch ever since the game came out last year.
Flinch is the disruption caused to your aim when you're hit by enemy fire. Sniper rifles are seen by some as overpowered in Black Ops Cold War because of their distinct lack of flinch.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zelda: Skyward Sword's Loftwing amiibo lets you skip a frustrating piece of game design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150347</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-19-zelda-skyward-swords-loftwing-amiibo-lets-you-skip-a-frustrating-piece-of-game-design"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T09:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo has revealed a Zelda and Loftwing amiibo figurine which launches alongside its Skyward Sword HD remaster on 16th July.
Tapping the amiibo to your Switch lets you zip between the game's airborne overworld and Hyrule's surface, wherever you are - a handy feature not available in the original game. See this in action in the trailer below:
The fact Nintendo has added this ability will undoubtedly save time when playing Skyward Sword HD. You no longer have to visit specific points to swap between the sk…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dimensional Chess]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2465/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2465/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching to OFTC]]></title>
        <id>https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Switching-to-OFTC.html</id>
        <link href="https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Switching-to-OFTC.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine Linux]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alpine Linux News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shake-up reported at the CDC; two high-profile officials depart]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765994</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765994"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T23:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent hiccups reportedly led to tensions within the agency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20 percent of Switch sales now going to households that already had a Switch]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765955</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765955"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T23:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miyamoto wants a Switch "not just [for] every family, but [for] every single person."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rare quasicrystal found in trinitite formed during 1945 Trinity Test]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765764</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765764"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T21:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Research suggests other quasicrystals might form in lighting strikes, meteor impacts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google, Samsung, and Fitbit team up to save Wear OS]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765728</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765728"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T20:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung is bringing the hardware, Google is bringing the software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verizon forces users onto pricier plans to get $50-per-month gov’t subsidy]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765823</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765823"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T20:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might have to change Internet plans to get the FCC's $50 low-income subsidy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indigenous forest gardens remain productive and diverse for over a century]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765746</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765746"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T20:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gardens persist for 150 years after those who planted them were removed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Contributors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change is erasing humanity’s oldest art]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765735</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765735"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T19:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change is speeding up the process of erosion, according to a recent study.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiona N. Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s best tech deals: Roku media streamers, Apple iPad Air, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765506</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765506"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T19:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealmaster also has deals on Xbox Game Pass Ultimate, SSDs, and LG OLED TVs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida water plant compromise came hours after worker visited malicious site]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765767</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765767"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T19:31:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers find watering-hole attack targeting water utilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All fossil fuel exploration needs to end this year, IEA says]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765722</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765722"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T19:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renewable spending needs to double to $4 trillion per year by 2030.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google shows off Android 12’s huge UI overhaul]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765725</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765725"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T18:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google confirms Android 12's color-changing UI, all-new design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel’s Optane H20 is the latest attempt at “hybrid” laptop storage]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765707</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765707"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T18:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[H20 benchmarks well, but real-world performance and price remain to be seen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compromised credentials? Google can now change website passwords for you]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765557</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765557"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T18:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Duplex will soon navigate the "change password" interface of websites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia will add anti-mining flags to the rest of its RTX 3000 GPU series]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765697</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765697"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T17:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Company says it learned from RTX 3060 fiasco, but is "LHR" just antivirus for GPUs?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything coming to Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War with Season Three Reloaded]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150282</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-everything-coming-to-call-of-duty-black-ops-cold-war-with-season-three-reloaded"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of this week's Season Three Reloaded update, Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War is getting a raft of new content.
As well as Rambo and John McClane as brand new operators, and the baseball bat melee weapon and AMP63 pistol, Treyarch's shooter gets two new Multiplayer maps, the new main quest for Zombies' Outbreak mode, and Rambo and Die Hard twists on classic game modes.
The headline here is the arrival of Standoff, a 6v6 map first introduced in Black Ops 2. This is a medium-sized map with a three-lan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers show neutralizing antibodies correlate with COVID protection]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765622</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765622"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T17:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antibodies produced by vaccines and infections declined at roughly similar rates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Warzone gets Nakatomi Plaza, survival camps and a CIA Outpost this week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150277</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-call-of-duty-warzone-gets-nakatomi-plaza-survival-camps-and-a-cia-outpost-this-week"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Activision has confirmed some new points of interest coming to Call of Duty: Warzone's map this week as part of the Season Three Reloaded update and the '80s action movie hero event.
From 20th May, Nakatomi Plaza from Die Hard will appear in Downtown for a limited time. This is the tallest single structure seen in Warzone, and includes five floors of space Die Hard fans will find familiar.
Nakatomi Plaza replaces the Broadcast Tower and surrounding blocks in Downtown's southern district. It houses multiple …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple planning MacBook Pro with 16-core GPU, Mac Pro with 128 GPU cores]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765693</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765693"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg's sources spill core counts and more on the next wave of Macs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War and Warzone trailer shows off Rambo in action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150270</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-call-of-duty-black-ops-cold-war-and-warzone-trailer-shows-off-rambo-in-action"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Activision has released a new trailer for Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War and Warzone that shows off Rambo in action.
The video, below, reveals how Rambo looks in Activision's mega-shooter. We see the '80s action hero leap out of a chopper at the start of a Warzone game, parachute into the action, and use his iconic bow and arrow. There's a lot of shouting while firing guns, as you'd expect.
There's a lot relating to Die Hard here, too. There's a brief shot of what looks like Nakatomi Plaza in Warzone:
Rea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saints Row: The Third Remastered gets free PS5 and Xbox Series upgrade next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150264</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-saints-row-the-third-remastered-gets-free-playstation-5-and-xbox-series-upgrade-next-week"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saints Row: The Third Remastered is getting some improvements on PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series next week, with a free upgrade that will bring these console versions to the same standard as the "PC edition at high settings". 
Arriving on 25th May, the PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S upgrade will allow the game's engine to "run at a much higher performance, bringing improvements to lighting, texture resolution, and other visual effects thanks to the powerful hardware." The press release from Deep Silver exp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hallelujah! Divinity: Original Sin 2 arrives today on iPad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150246</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-hallelujah-divinity-original-sin-2-arrives-today-on-ipad"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Divinity: Original Sin 2 has been released on iPad and iPad Pro.
This is apparently a proper, full fat port. There are no surprise new microtransactions or anything like that. It's the full game, Gift Bag DLCs included, as you remember it on PC or consoles. And it costs £23.99 (check regional pricing).
It's been developed over two years by Larian and Russian partner Elveris. DOS2 iPad has touch controls, obviously, but also supports mouse and keyboard as well as game pads, such as the PS5 pad.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another media acquisition? This one would involve Amazon, MGM, and ~$9B]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765675</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765675"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T15:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does this at least mean we can watch No Time to Die at home soon?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Mattise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance finally launches on Nintendo Switch this week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150255</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-baldurs-gate-dark-alliance-finally-launches-on-nintendo-switch-this-week"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance finally launches on Nintendo Switch on 20th May, Black Isle has announced.
The re-release of the 20-year-old console action role-playing game was scheduled to hit the eShop on 7th May alongside PlayStation and Xbox, but suffered a delay at the last minute.
Black Isle subsequently tweeted to apologise for the situation.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding a Russian Keyboard to Protect against Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/adding-a-russian-keyboard-to-protect-against-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/adding-a-russian-keyboard-to-protect-against-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T15:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of Russian malware — the malware that targeted the Colonial Pipeline, for example — won’t install on computers with a Cyrillic keyboard installed. Brian Krebs wonders if this could be a useful defense:
In Russia, for example, authorities there generally will not initiate a cybercrime investigation against one of their own unless a company or individual within the country’s borders files an official complaint as a victim. Ensuring that no affiliates can produce victims in their own countries is the eas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EA wants Codemasters to retain identity like Respawn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150228</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-ea-wants-codemasters-to-retain-identity-like-respawn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year Electronic Arts swooped in to buy British developer Codemasters for hefty $1.2bn (£851m), and we're now starting to hear further details about what the publisher plans to do with its new acquisition. In an interview with MCV, EA CEO Andrew Wilson explained that EA wants to give Codemasters the Respawn treatment: in other words, allowing Codemasters to retain its identity without too much outside interference. 
"Similar to Respawn, our orientation isn't to come in and take over Codemasters; our ori…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rockstar outlines summer updates for GTA Online and Red Dead Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150225</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-rockstar-outlines-summer-updates-for-gta-online-and-red-dead-online"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T13:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rockstar has outlined summer updates for GTA Online and Red Dead Online.
Let's start with GTA Online. Rockstar was light on detail in its blog post:
"In Los Santos, car culture is back on the streets in a big way, with new opportunities for fans of performance and customisation upgrades to get together with like-minded gearheads to test and show off their rides free from interference from authorities and other troublemakers. The renewed interest is bringing a new underground car meet into the area, along wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox Game Pass adds Slime Rancher on PC next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150221</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-xbox-game-pass-adds-slime-rancher-on-pc-next-week"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T13:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slime Rancher on PC plus SnowRunner for console, cloud and PC headline the next two weeks of Xbox Game Pass additions. 
SnowRunner arrives for all Xbox Game Pass platforms today - coincidentally the day it confirmed a £20.99 Year 2 Pass for even more post-launch content.
PopCap puzzler Peggle 2 and third-person shooter Plants vs Zombies: Battle for Neighborville meanwhile both arrive on Thursday, 20th May for cloud devices via EA Play.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grand Theft Auto 5 hits PS5 and Xbox Series X and S this November]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150216</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-grand-theft-auto-5-hits-ps5-and-xbox-series-x-and-s-this-november"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T13:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grand Theft Auto 5 hits PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X and S on 11th November, Rockstar has announced.
Currently, the game is playable on current-gen consoles via backwards compatibility.
The standalone version of GTA Online will be available to players on both platforms. But, as previously announced, the standalone version of GTA Online will be available for free exclusively to PS5 players during the first three months, ending in February 2022. This means that if you want GTA Online on Xbox Series X and S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything we know about the plug-in hybrid McLaren Artura]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765657</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765657"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T12:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a new carbon-fiber monocoque and a 120-degree V6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demeo is the best multiplayer, virtual-reality D&D clone ever made]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763983</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763983"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T11:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issues aside, it already feels like sharing a real-life dice-and-minis table with friends.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Effect Legendary Edition's first mods let you adjust FOV, have ME1 gay romance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150171</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-mass-effect-legendary-editions-first-mods-let-you-adjust-fov-have-me1-gay-romance"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T11:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Effect Legendary Edition has only been released a few days, but already there are dozens of mods to customise its experience. 
Numerous options available via NexusMods tweak the trilogy's lighting, colour palette and field of view - such as the Better Camera (Higher FOV) mod by JadeBarker.
An early attempt at unlocking gay romance in Mass Effect 1 has also already appeared. Same Sex Mod for Default Shepard lets male Shepard romance Kaiden and female Shepard romance Ashley. But this will only work with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SnowRunner is getting a second year of post-launch support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150167</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-snowrunner-is-getting-a-second-year-of-post-launch-support"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T10:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wonderful SnowRunner has today launched on Steam, Xbox Game Pass and Nintendo Switch alongside Season 4: New Frontiers - and we've got confirmation of a second year of post-launch support.
SnowRunner, which Christian Donlan described as a "beautiful game about getting nowhere slowly", launched last year on the Epic Games Store, PlayStation 4 and Xbox One.
New Frontiers, meanwhile, is set in Amur Oblast, Russia, and provides 16 square kilometers of Russian wilderness to navigate for the rehabilitation of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Effect Legendary Edition hasn't fixed this infinite Paragon/Renegade point glitch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150140</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-mass-effect-legendary-edition-hasnt-fixed-this-infinite-paragon-renegade-point-glitch"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As resurfaced by Kotaku, this exploit is found on the planet of Noveria - so if you want to take advantage of having a full goodie-two-shoes reputation gauge, head there as quickly as you can. 
Having a beefy Paragon or Renegade points bar is important throughout Mass Effect, as it'll allow you to resolve certain situations through dialogue and without things automatically playing out as a bloodbath.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black & White 2 modder releases 4K texture pack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150136</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-black-and-white-2-modder-releases-4k-texture-pack"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Black & White 2 modder has released a 4K texture pack for the game.
Modder merendas235 uploaded the 6GB texture pack to NexusMods on 16th May (thanks, DSOGaming).
The video below is a comparison of Black & White 2 running with and without the texture pack.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Murdered teen footballer now in FIFA 21 - 15 years after his death]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150119</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-18-murdered-teen-footballer-now-in-fifa-21-15-years-after-his-death"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T08:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A teen footballer who was murdered in 2006 is now in FIFA 21.
Kiyan Prince was a 15-year-old playing for Queens Park Rangers when his life was tragically cut short in 2006 when he was stabbed while trying to break up a fight in school.
Now, 15 years later, EA has added Prince to the QPR squad in FIFA 21. He appears in the game as a 30-year-old.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Library]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/new-library/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/new-library/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden pledges to share 20 million COVID-19 vaccine doses with the world]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765579</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765579"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T22:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 20 million will be in addition to 60 million AstraZeneca doses already pledged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s M1 is a fast CPU—but M1 Macs feel even faster due to QoS]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765494</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765494"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T20:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Howard Oakley did an excellent deep dive on M1 scheduling and performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Music subscribers will get lossless and spatial audio for free next month]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765499</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765499"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T19:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New features will launch with iOS 14.6, macOS 11.4 in June.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocket Lab reviewing data after its second Electron failure in a year]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765439</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765439"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T18:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["We deeply regret the loss of BlackSky's payload."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDC defends its abrupt reversal on masks after backlash from experts]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765479</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765479"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T17:22:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts question timing as CDC director says public pressure wasn’t a factor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T to spin off WarnerMedia, basically admitting giant merger was a mistake]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765461</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765461"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WarnerMedia and Discovery to merge, and standalone AT&T will focus on broadband.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget multiple cameras—Sharp phone has one giant 1-inch camera sensor]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765409</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765409"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the biggest smartphone camera sensor ever—or at least tied.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[City pays $350,000 after suing “hackers” for opening Dropbox link it sent them]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765448</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765448"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Employee mistakenly sent the link when replying to a records request.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unreal developer Epic Games sues smart glasses maker Nreal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150067</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-17-unreal-developer-epic-games-sues-smart-glasses-maker-nreal"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese augmented reality headset company Nreal is being sued by Epic Games, developer of Fortnite and Unreal Engine.
If you hadn't guessed already, the squabble is over the name Nreal, which Epic Games argues is deliberately similar to its own Unreal (thanks, The Verge). 
The two companies have been warring over the name for years, though this latest legal challenge from Epic appears to have been sparked by an Nreal boast it had "big news" - seemingly, that its Nreal smartglasses were being prepped for US …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not enough to trust science on vaccines—others have to as well]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765440</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765440"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Personal trust and societal consensus have an additive effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Roblox’s definition of “games” is key to the Epic vs. Apple case]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765432</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765432"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T15:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The line between "game" and "experience" has major implications for iOS App Review.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mario Golf: Super Rush has a mode where you race across courses on foot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150057</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-17-mario-golf-super-rush-has-a-mode-where-you-race-across-courses-on-foot"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T15:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo has shown off an extended look at several new modes coming to Mario Golf: Super Rush, as well as the game's full character roster. 
Speed Golf is a fresh mode where players race each other on foot across the golf course in-between taking shots. (If only karts existed in Mario's world!)
While dashing, players can use items to regain stamina and special attacks to thwack the ball/other players out of the way. (Seriously, why isn't Mario Golf Kart a thing?)
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chivalry 2 crossplay open beta kicks off next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150055</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-17-chivalry-2-crossplay-open-beta-kicks-off-next-week"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chivalry 2 crossplay open beta kicks off next week, developer Torn Banner Studios has announced.
The multiplayer first-person slasher inspired by medieval movie battles launches its new open beta on 27th May. It ends on 1st June.
The open beta is a free download on PC via the Epic Games Store, PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 5, and on Xbox One, Xbox Series X and S.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From apes to birds, there are 65 animal species that “laugh”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765400</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765400"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T13:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laughter is spread widely across mammals and occurs in birds, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Walsall council criticised for enormous "Super Mario" plant pots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150032</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-17-walsall-council-criticised-for-enormous-super-mario-plant-pots"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T13:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walsall council has been slammed for splashing taxpayer pounds on the oversized planters, which have been arranged throughout the town centre. 
Birmingham Mail reported that the spending has come at a time its local authority is being asked to cut £29m from its budget - and these plant pots don't look Cheep Cheep.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assassin's Creed fans translate all of Valhalla's Vinland dialogue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150018</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-17-assassins-creed-fans-translate-all-of-valhallas-vinland-dialogue"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T13:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assassin's Creed fansite Access the Animus has worked with Montreal's Kanien'kehá:ka Onkwawén:na Raotitióhkwa Language and Cultural Center to translate all of the unsubtitled dialogue in Valhalla's Vinland arc.
The video below reveals what is being said in all of the conversations going on around Eivor in this part of the game, which she (and you) are deliberately left unable to understand.
As well as dialogue, it includes translations of item descriptions and more. There's also a fascinating explanation of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samurai Shodown hits Steam 14th June with a new DLC character]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150020</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-17-samurai-shodown-hits-steam-14th-june-with-a-new-dlc-character"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T13:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samurai Shodown hits Steam 14th June with a new DLC character, SNK has announced.
The fighting game arrives on Steam a year after it launched on PC via the Epic Games Store.
On the same day, new DLC character Shiro Tokisada Amakusa comes out.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A brief look at electric vehicles from the dawn of the automobile age]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765381</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765381"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T13:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electric vehicles were well represented during the early decades of the car.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Microsoft Flight Simulator modder is building a tour guide to the entire world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2150013</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-17-a-microsoft-flight-simulator-modder-is-building-a-tour-guide-to-the-entire-world"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An ambitious modder is building an audio tour of the entire virtual world - inside Microsoft Flight Simulator.
Bushtalk Radio is a community-driven project that adds audio descriptions to over 8000 points of interest in the sim. These audio descriptions are played automatically as you arrive at one of the supported POIs.
Some of the most-visited POIs with accompanying audio tours include a raft of UK landmarks, such as The O2, Tower Bridge, Hyde Park, The Shard and Big Ben.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Effect Legendary Edition off to good start on Steam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149996</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-17-mass-effect-legendary-edition-off-to-good-start-on-steam"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Its current peak concurrent total of 59,650 (via Steam Charts and BenjiSales) is the highest for any Mass Effect or indeed BioWare game on Steam. 
The average user review rating is "Very Positive", though there are a number of complaints over the game's lack of an FOV slider outside of photo mode, and its insistence on launching Origin to launch the Legendary Edition launcher, to then launch a specific game.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is 85% of US Critical Infrastructure in Private Hands?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/is-85-of-us-critical-infrastructure-in-private-hands.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/is-85-of-us-critical-infrastructure-in-private-hands.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most US critical infrastructure is run by private corporations. This has major security implications, because it’s putting a random power company in — say — Ohio — up against the Russian cybercommand, which isn’t a fair fight.
When this problem is discussed, people regularly quote the statistic that 85% of US critical infrastructure is in private hands. It’s a handy number, and matches our intuition. Still, I have never been able to find a factual basis, or anyone who knows where the number comes from. Paul…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Effect Legendary Edition changed a character's race, fixing a decade-old bug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149975</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-17-mass-effect-legendary-edition-changed-a-characters-race-fixing-a-decade-old-bug"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T10:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BioWare has changed a Mass Effect character's race from human to turian - fixing a long-standing issue many (correctly) assumed was a bug.
THERE MAY BE MASS EFFECT 1 SPOILERS AHEAD.
Elanos Haliat, a human-hating pirate and previous leader of the Terminus Systems, appears in Mass Effect 1 on the world of Agebinium. Shepard encounters him when investigating a mysterious nuclear probe which needs to be defused.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Muller's Ratchet]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2464/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2464/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neutrons unlock the secrets of Antonie van Leeuwenhoek’s microscopes]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765022</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765022"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T21:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[His most powerful microscope holds a lens likely made with Robert Hooke's 1678 recipe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fans hit back at plans to introduce premium QoL and XP boosts in New World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149911</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-16-fans-hit-back-at-plans-to-introduce-premium-qol-and-xp-boosts-in-new-world"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T15:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Players have hit back at plans to introduce a premium currency shop in Amazon's upcoming MMORPG, New World.
The leak - which comes via the game's current alpha-test and was shared on Reddit - alleges that New World is introducing in-game purchases for "special cosmetic items for players and their in-game homes" and "may sell quality-of-life items or boosts that will help players improve their time spent levelling up their character and trade skill experience".
In response, the official Twitter account for t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Fantasy 14 vinyl boxset can be pre-ordered now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149907</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-16-final-fantasy-14-vinyl-boxset-can-be-pre-ordered-now"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T14:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A vinyl collection of music taken from Final Fantasy 14 will release on 31st August 2021.
The bundle - which includes tracks across A Realm Reborn, Heavenwards, Stormblood and Shadowbringers - is available to pre-order now for £87 / $100, although custom duties and shipping costs are not included.  
Each LP jacket features "gorgeous illustrations" by Kuroimori and the "vinyl cutting was done in Los Angeles by mastering virtuoso, Bernie Grundman". Purchases of the vinyl boxset will also receive a MP3 downloa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O 2021 preview: Google resurrects Wear OS and Android tablets?]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764606</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764606"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T13:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google I/O schedule promises to resurrect some long-dead form factors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google wants you to know Stadia is still "alive and well"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149903</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-16-google-wants-you-to-know-stadia-is-still-alive-and-well"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T11:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite a recent flurry of exits and changes at the top, Google is keen for us to know that Stadia is "alive and well" and "focused on delivering value for [its] partners and on behalf of [its] players".
"We're well on our way to over 100 new games launching on Stadia in 2021, and we're continuing to make Stadia a great place to play games on devices you already own," Stadia developer marketing lead, Nate Ahearn, told our sister site GamesIndustry.biz.
"I'd tell any non-believers to take notice of how we're…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's the working title of the next Tomb Raider movie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149899</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-16-heres-the-working-title-of-the-next-tomb-raider-movie"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T11:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next Tomb Raider movie's working title is Tomb Raider: Obsidian.
Misha Green - who has taken the reins from previous director Ben Wheatley as well as writing the film's story - confirmed the news on Twitter, also letting fans know that the first draft of the script has been finished. 
"Still a long journey to production," Green tweeted excitedly (thanks, GamesRadar+). "Title's not even approved. But first draft finished!!!"
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop FOMO inspires a new wave of crypto pump-and-dumps]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765272</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765272"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T11:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discord groups promise big earnings  by manipulating the crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[500,000 cheaters have been banned from Call of Duty: Warzone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149895</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-16-500-000-cheaters-have-been-banned-from-call-of-duty-warzone"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T10:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over half a million Call of Duty: Warzone accounts have now been banned for cheating. 
After banning a further 30,000 unscrupulous players yesterday, Warzone co-developer Raven Software confirmed that that brings the total of banned accounts to a staggering 500,000. 
Raven didn't elaborate on whether or not this was on a single platform or shared across all of them, nor what the cheaters were actually doing to warrant the ban hammer - but at least it shows that the studio takes cheating seriously, and is ho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leaked The Division Heartland gameplay warns closed test players not to leak the game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149878</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-15-leaked-the-division-heartland-gameplay-warns-closed-test-players-not-to-leak-the-game"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T20:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 20 minutes of The Division Heartland gameplay has leaked online, as well as a video from Ubisoft that warns closed test players not to leak the game.
Heartland is a standalone free-to-play game due out for PC, PlayStation and Xbox at some point this or next year. It's in development at Ghost Recon studio Red Storm Entertainment.
It appears the gameplay, which is currently live on Vimeo, has emerged from an ongoing invite-only test that is under strict NDA.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Dogs: Legion's upcoming 4.5 update adds 60fps performance mode on PS5 and Xbox Series X]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149873</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-15-watch-dogs-legions-upcoming-4-5-update-adds-60fps-performance-mode-on-ps5-and-xbox-series-x"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T15:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Dogs: Legion's upcoming 4.5 patch adds a 60fps performance mode on PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X, Ubisoft has announced.
Title update 4.0 went live last week, and in a blog post, Ubisoft revealed some new features coming with the 4.5 update.
The headline addition is the 60fps performance mode on PS5 and Xbox Series X. Ubisoft said this is "one of the biggest requests from our next-gen console players".
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hades PS4 rating spotted]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149871</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-15-hades-ps4-rating-spotted"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T14:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hades looks set for release on PlayStation 4.
The eagle-eyed watchers at ResetEra spotted a PS4 listing for Hades on the website of Korea's Game Rating and Administration Committee.
Supergiant's superb roguelite brawler was available first on PC in early access form in December 2018, before launching proper in September on PC and Nintendo Switch.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The chip shortage is driving up tech prices–starting with TVs]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765280</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765280"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T11:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some high-end televisions already cost 30% more than they did last summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Bangeman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Effect Legendary Edition changes Tali's controversial cabin photo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149851</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-15-mass-effect-legendary-edition-changes-talis-controversial-cabin-photo"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T10:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Effect Legendary Edition changes one of the longest-standing issues with the franchise: Tali's face.
THERE MAY BE MASS EFFECT SPOILERS AHEAD.
Original party member Tali'Zorah is a quarian whose face has been one of the most popular online discussion topics about Mass Effect. Throughout the series, her face is concealed due to her having to wear a suit that protects her from disease.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colonial Pipeline paid a $5 million ransom—and kept a vicious cycle turning]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765276</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765276"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T10:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stopping payments would go a long way to stopping ransomware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treyarch reveals what's next for Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War Zombies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149846</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-15-treyarch-reveals-whats-next-for-call-of-duty-black-ops-cold-war-zombies"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T09:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Treyarch has detailed what's coming to Zombies mode in Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War.
Outbreak gets its first main quest with the launch of the mid-season three refresh, at 6pm UK time on Thursday 20th May - the same time Rambo and Die Hard's Die Hard's John McClane hit Black Ops Cold War and Warzone.
In a blog post, Treyarch said that from there, the studio plans to release a "record amount" of quest-driven Zombies content ahead of the next chapters of the Dark Aether story.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's three minutes of unedited Biomutant gameplay on five platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149842</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-15-heres-three-minutes-of-unedited-biomutant-gameplay-on-five-platforms"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T09:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THQ Nordic has released just over three minutes of unedited Biomutant gameplay on five different platforms.
In each video we see a slight variation on the same objective, with the player character sprinting across the lush open world towards a fight with a guerilla miniboss and its minions. The martial arts style combat system looks like a lot of fun, and I particularly liked how the guerilla can grab the player, launch them into the air then bat them away - nice, smooth animations.
The PC gameplay is in th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Fantasy 14 expansion Endwalker out in November]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149839</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-15-final-fantasy-14-expansion-endwalker-out-in-november"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T08:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Final Fantasy 14 expansion Endwalker launches 23rd November 2021, Square Enix has announced.
Square Enix also announced a new job to be introduced with Endwalker: the reaper. This is a scythe-wielding melee DPS job who summons avatars while fighting in close-quarter combat.
A first look at the reaper in action is in the video below:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pipeline attacker Darkside suddenly goes dark—here’s what we know]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765287</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765287"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T21:25:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The closure may mean the group is ceasing or altering ops—or pulling an exit scam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: Far Side Squid Comic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/friday-squid-blogging-far-side-squid-comic.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/friday-squid-blogging-far-side-squid-comic.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T21:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A classic.
As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.
Read my blog posting guidelines here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers force two mice to hang out and induce FOMO in a third]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765264</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765264"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synchronized activity between brains seems to be the key to socializing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Contributors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elite Dangerous: Odyssey players will be put in separate galaxy to base game friends]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149832</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-14-elite-dangerous-odyssey-owners-will-play-in-separate-galaxy-to-base-game-friends"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T19:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elite Dangerous players wanting to make use of the new features found in the space sim's on-foot-focussed Odyssey expansion will be required to play in an expansion-exclusive version of the galaxy when it comes to PC on 19th May, separating them from their base game friends.
Odyssey, of course, delivers a considerable shake-up to Elite Dangerous' classic cockpit-focussed formula, enabling Commanders to stretch their legs and step out of their ships in order to stroll about space stations, settlements, and p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Despite big Marvel and Star Wars shows, Disney+ falls short of targets]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765225</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765225"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T18:47:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The limits to recent explosive streaming platform growth might be in sight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ISPs claim broadband prices aren’t too high—Biden admin isn’t buying it]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765202</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765202"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T18:38:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Biden still plans "bold action" to lower Internet prices despite heavy lobbying.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious health incidents rise to 130, US officials confirm]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765210</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765210"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T18:17:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most recent reports have come in the past two weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TSMC is considering a 3 nm foundry in Arizona]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765205</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765205"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T17:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The already planned 5 nm Arizona plant may be joined by a second, 3 nm plant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Speaking Engagements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/upcoming-speaking-engagements-8.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/upcoming-speaking-engagements-8.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T17:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a current list of where and when I am scheduled to speak:
I’m keynoting the (all-virtual) RSA Conference 2021, May 17-20, 2021.
I’m keynoting the 5th International Symposium on Cyber Security Cryptology and Machine Learning (via Zoom), July 8-9, 2021.
I’ll be speaking at an Informa event on September 14, 2021. Details to come.
The list is maintained on this page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mount Vesuvius victims died just moments away from rescue]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765087</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765087"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T16:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A skeleton unearthed at the site may belong to a high-ranking naval officer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiona N. Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple US agencies probing world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765146</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765146"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T16:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IRS, DOJ, and CFTC are looking at potential criminal violations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel 6 leak shows off distinctive new design]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765109</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765109"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T16:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Besides the all-new Google "Whitechapel" SoC, it's reportedly getting a new design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Epic v. Apple namecheck, Itch.io runs one-day-only dev-friendly promo]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765110</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765110"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T16:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Similar to "Bandcamp Fridays"—comes after Itch.io was disparaged in Epic v. Apple.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EA's "dodgebrawl" game Knockout City getting 10-day free trial at launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149819</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-14-eas-competitive-dodgebrawl-game-knockout-city-getting-10-day-free-trial-at-launch"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T16:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knockout City, the EA-published competitive "dodgebrawl" game from Velan Studios, will have a 10-day free trial on all platforms when it launches next Friday, 21st May.
The gist of Knockout City is that, in time-honoured dodgeball style, two teams of players (either 3v3 or 4v4) battle it out for supremacy by lobbing balls at each other. It's an easy to understand premise with a vibrantly approachable visual sheen, putting it on a collision course with  countless other offerings in the busy field of live-ser…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland’s health care system taken down after ransomware attack]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765173</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765173"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T16:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doctors left unable to access patient records after "very sophisticated" attack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Bangeman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China is about to attempt a highly ambitious landing on Mars]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765111</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765111"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T16:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a lot of intrigue surrounding the mission. Will the lander survive?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Call of Duty: Warzone exploit has been fixed, this time for unbreakable gas masks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149800</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-14-another-call-of-duty-warzone-exploit-has-been-fixed-this-time-for-unbreakable-gas-masks"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another day, another game-breaking glitch in Call of Duty: Warzone. It wasn't quite the infamous stim glitch, but the end result was similar, as this time players found an exploit that allowed them to create unbreakable gas masks. Thankfully, this particular method has now been patched out by Raven. 
In your average game of Warzone, masks are supposed to degrade when you sit outside the ring, eventually breaking so that you start taking damage from the gas (and die). Some players figured out a way to glitch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is an ECU? An EC2 Compute Unit, Simply Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8803</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/what-is-an-ecu-an-ec2-compute-unit-simply-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An EC2 Compute Unit (ECU) was Amazon’s first attempt to compare the CPU performance of different EC2 instance types. Find out what an ECU measured, why it was created, and why it was replaced.
The post What is an ECU? An EC2 Compute Unit, Simply Explained appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite fan survey reveals dozens of potential skins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149784</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-14-fortnite-fan-survey-reveals-dozens-of-potential-skins"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T13:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artwork revealing dozens of potential Fortnite characters has been posted online. 
Fortnite fans do not typically get to see the battle royale's eye-catching characters until they're added to the game's files - and even then, some are encrypted so they're a complete surprise until they go on sale. 
However, a new player survey has spilled onto the internet via LeakySussed - and among questions about the game itself there are dozens of unrevealed characters for fans to offer feedback on.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I am alone." Skyrim player tries to kill everyone in the game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149743</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-14-skyrim-player-kills-everyone-in-the-game-then-declares-i-am-alone"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T13:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Skyrim player has tried to kill everyone in the game.
"It is finished," redditor jaeinskyrim declared (thanks, PCGamesN). "2201 people/NPCs, plus over 2400 more various creatures. All gone. I am alone in Skyrim."
It was a monumental task. Bethesda's open-world fantasy adventure is huge and packed with NPCs - people, animals, creatures, undead, daedra, automatons... they all fell by the wayside amid jaeinskyrim's murderous rampage. They enlisted the help of a long list of mods, including Kill 'em All and D…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Destiny 2 players say its transmog system is worse than feared]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149754</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-14-destiny-2-players-say-its-transmog-system-is-worse-than-feared"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T12:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Destiny 2's new transmog system to change the appearance of items has come under further fire from fans, following its general release. 
In the run up to its long-awaited launch, players despaired at the announcement of its grind-heavy mechanics. Now it's actually out in the wild, the criticism has continued. 
Chief among the complaints is the fact that Synthstrand, the base tier of three transmog currencies, appears to be time-gated. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware Is Getting Ugly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/ransomware-is-getting-ugly.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/ransomware-is-getting-ugly.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T11:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern ransomware has two dimensions: pay to get your data back, and pay not to have your data dumped on the Internet. The DC police are the victims of this ransomware, and the criminals have just posted personnel records &#8212; &#8220;including the results of psychological assessments and polygraph tests; driver&#8217;s license images; fingerprints; social security numbers; dates of birth; and residential, financial, and marriage histories&#8221; &#8212; for two dozen police officers.
The negotiations don…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disco Elysium no longer in Australian Classification Board sin bin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149738</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-14-disco-elysium-no-longer-in-australian-classification-board-sin-bin"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T11:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Australian Classification Board has garnered a reputation for being pretty tight about the games it approves: its refusal to give DayZ the green light over weed resulted in the game being changed worldwide, and Disco Elysium similarly found itself in the firing line earlier this year. Back in March, the board announced that Disco Elysium: The Final Cut was too offensive to go on sale, citing its depiction of drug use, crime and violence as just some of the reasons for the ban. 
Well, the board has now r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocket Report: Starship orbital flight details, Ariane 5 may delay Webb launch]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765014</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1765014"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T11:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Also, Boeing's Starliner spacecraft gets a new launch date.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Very experimental" Resident Evil Village third-person mod features a headless Ethan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149729</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-14-very-experimental-resident-evil-village-third-person-mod-features-a-headless-ethan"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A modder is working on getting a third-person perspective up and running within the normally first-person Resident Evil Village.
Modder FluffyQuack is working on a third-person mod for Capcom's horror game, and has published footage of it working.
THERE MAY BE RESIDENT EVIL VILLAGE SPOILERS AHEAD.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Mass Effect Legendary Edition, the trilogy's best ending is still available if you only play ME3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149724</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-14-in-mass-effect-legendary-edition-the-trilogys-best-ending-is-still-available-if-you-only-play-me3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Effect Legendary Edition features BioWare's full trilogy in its most accessible form yet - but it also lets you pick and choose to play individual games. 
Perhaps you just want to play Mass Effect 3? Or maybe you want to start with ME2, as the series fleshes out its roster of characters, and skip ME1's Mako?
Well, all of this - as it always did - plays into the trilogy's big finale. Avoiding spoilers, it's worth remembering that whatever Shepard's own individual choices might be, these choices are also…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blizzard lowers price of a cloned World of Warcraft Classic character following backlash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149721</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-14-blizzard-lowers-the-price-of-a-cloned-world-of-warcraft-classic-character-following-backlash"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blizzard has lowered the price of a cloned World of Warcraft Classic character following a backlash from players.
The company was set to charge $35 per character for an optional cloning service, which would let players keep playing the original World of Warcraft Classic content and The Burning Crusade content with the same character.
The $35 (around £25) price was roundly criticised by the World of Warcraft community as being too expensive - and Blizzard came under fire accordingly.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberpunk parkour game Ghostrunner is getting a sequel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149720</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-14-cyberpunk-parkour-game-ghostrunner-is-getting-a-sequel"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T09:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready for some more cyberpunk? No, not that one, I'm talking about cyberpunk action-parkour game Ghostrunner, which is now getting a sequel. 
Publisher 505 Games and lead developer One More Level have announced that Ghostrunner 2 is currently in development, and will release on PC, PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S. As of yet there's no release date for the sequel, so we may be waiting a while to slide around its neon-lit streets. 
In the short term there's still plenty to come for the original game…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Katy Perry debuts Pokémon pop song Electric]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149713</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-14-katy-perry-has-released-her-pokemon-pop-song"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pokémon continues its 25th anniversary celebrations today with the release of Katy Perry's new single Electric.
In the video, Katy Perry and her Pikachu reminisce about growing up - and we see flashbacks to when she was younger and Pikachu was just a Pichu. Pokémon evolve, and so do people too! I think that's the message here. 
It's no Pokérap, but you can watch it anyway below:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dungeons & Dragons Dark Alliance launches straight into Xbox Game Pass]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149698</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-14-dungeons-and-dragons-dark-alliance-launches-straight-into-xbox-game-pass"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T09:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dungeons &amp; Dragons Dark Alliance launches straight into Xbox Game Pass.
Dark Alliance will be available on Xbox One, Xbox Series X and S, Windows 10 PC, and phones and tablets via Xbox Cloud Gaming with Xbox Game Pass on 22nd June, developer Tuque Games announced.
The game is also available then on PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 5, and supports PC and console crossplay at launch.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astrophotography]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2463/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2463/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Using Finalizers to Control Deletion]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/05/14/using-finalizers-to-control-deletion/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/05/14/using-finalizers-to-control-deletion/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Aaron Alpar (Kasten)
Deleting objects in Kubernetes can be challenging. You may think you’ve deleted something, only to find it still persists. While issuing a kubectl delete command and hoping for the best might work for day-to-day operations, understanding how Kubernetes delete commands operate will help you understand why some objects linger after deletion.
In this post, I’ll look at:
What properties of a resource govern deletion
How finalizers and owner references impact object deletion
How the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo’s new “Go” brand of travel gear kicks off with a wireless-charging mouse]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764990</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764990"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T22:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Also announced: a 20,000 mAh portable charger for users' various devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fall Guys' latest mid-season update out now bringing two new stages and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149649</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-13-fall-guys-latest-mid-season-update-out-now-adds-two-new-stages"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T20:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fall Guys' 80s-themed fourth season has reached its mid-point, meaning, as is now tradition, the arrival of a brand-new content update designed to freshen up the second half of the season with a variety of new gameplay twists and additions.
As detailed over on the Fall Guys subreddit, Season 4.5, which is out now on PC and PlayStation 4, introduces two brand-new rounds - Slimescraper and Button Bashers - as well as a total of 55 variations across 12 rounds. Slimescraper is described as spiritual successor t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New users can get 3 months of Xbox Game Pass Ultimate for $1 today]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764814</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764814"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T19:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealmaster also has deals on iPhone cases, Garmin watches, and robot vacuums.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New analysis confirms hypothesis for source of mysterious auroral “dunes”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763383</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763383"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T19:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ongoing collaboration between physicists and amateur stargazers yields new insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla owner who “drives” from back seat got arrested, then did it again]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764902</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764902"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T18:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Man jailed for leaving driver seat empty says he feels safer in back seat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation Play at Home continues next week with free in-game currency and virtual items]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149642</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-13-playstation-play-at-home-continues-next-week-with-free-in-game-currency-and-virtual-items"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T18:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although last month's generous PlayStation Play at Home game giveaway has run its course (with the exception of Horizon Zero Dawn, which remains free until tomorrow, 14th May), Sony isn't quite done yet. Players will soon be able to claim free in-game currency and virtual items for a selection of popular titles, including Call of Duty: Warzone and Rocket League.
Starting next Monday, 17th May, at 4am BST/8pm PDT, nine titles (both free-to-play and full-price) will be offering special currency and item bundl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vaccinated people can now go maskless in most indoor locations [Updated]]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764922</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764922"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T18:32:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With vaccines generally available and highly effective, the US shifts its advice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox Party Chat gets text-to-speech and speech-to-text as accessibility push continues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149638</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-13-xbox-party-chat-gets-text-to-speech-and-speech-to-text-as-accessibility-push-continues"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T17:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Continuing its welcome push for accessibility and inclusivity on Xbox, Microsoft has introduced a number of new features to its Xbox Party Chat system.
The new accessibility features - which will initially be available, starting today, to those signed up to the Xbox Insiders programme - specifically bring speech-to-text transcription and text-to-speech synthesis to Microsoft's system-wide Xbox Party Chat.
The former coverts all words spoken by members of a party chat into adjustable text, overlaid on gamepl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Surface Duo fire sale puts device at 50% off]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764822</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764822"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T16:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's weird dual-screen Android phone hits the bargain bin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft puts Windows 10X variant on the back burner]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764827</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764827"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T16:20:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It looks like Microsoft is abandoning its plans for the tablet-focused distro.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk: Bitcoin is bad for climate (and you can’t buy Teslas with it anymore)]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764840</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764840"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T16:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla CEO flip-flops, says that environmental concerns drove the decision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pokémon cards pulled from Target and Walmart due to safety concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149618</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-13-pokemon-cards-pulled-from-target-and-walmart-due-to-safety-concerns"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The high demand for Pokémon trading cards seems to be causing all sorts of mischief - again. Two major US stores are pulling their Pokémon cards, citing customer safety concerns as the reason. 
After images of shop notices were posted on social media, Target confirmed to Bleeding Cool that it has decided to temporarily suspend the sale of MLB, NFL, NBA and Pokémon trading cards out of "an abundance of caution". The cards will be pulled from all stores on 14th May, but will continue to be sold online. 
As fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden signs executive order to strengthen US cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764836</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764836"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T15:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Move comes after high-profile hacks, including attack on crucial fuel pipeline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Financial Times</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congress fires warning shot at NASA after SpaceX Moon lander award]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764485</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764485"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T14:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["This bill, in the main, is not supposed to be about space."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New US Executive Order on Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/new-us-executive-order-on-cybersecurity.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/new-us-executive-order-on-cybersecurity.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T14:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden signed an executive order to improve government cybersecurity, setting new security standards for software sold to the federal government.
For the first time, the United States will require all software purchased by the federal government to meet, within six months, a series of new cybersecurity standards. Although the companies would have to &#8220;self-certify,&#8221; violators would be removed from federal procurement lists, which could kill their chances of selling their products on the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation 5's DualSense controller gets black and red versions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149594</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-13-playstation-5s-dualsense-controller-gets-black-and-red-versions"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T13:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rejoice, goths and people who just like their gaming peripherals to look sleek: a black version of the PlayStation 5's DualSense controller has been announced, and will be available for purchase from next month. And for the flamboyant among you, there's also a bold red. 
Announced via the PlayStation blog, the two new colours are themed around space and are officially called "midnight black and cosmic red". The black apparently comes in "two subtly different shades of black with light grey detailing", and y…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's how E3's virtual event will work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149577</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-13-e3-2021-will-use-an-online-portal-and-app"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month we heard that, rather unsurprisingly, this year's E3 will be an online-only event due to the ongoing Covid-19 pandemic. We now have an idea of how that's going to work in practice, as the ESA has announced an online portal and app for E3 2021. 
In a press release, the ESA described the online portal and app as "a key hub for the duration of the show". It will feature hosted events, virtual booths, online forums, video conferencing, and even profile and avatar creation. The exhibitor booths will h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real robotaxi service gets a step closer in San Francisco (Updated)]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764798</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764798"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T12:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Waymo and Cruise have both applied for permits to deploy a commercial service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Effect Legendary Edition: Tests, thoughts, and a 10 am EDT Twitch stream]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764076</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764076"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T12:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you can't make the morning Twitch stream, we still have tons of impressions to share.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony working on 25 games for PlayStation 5, half of which are new IP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149551</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-13-sony-working-on-25-games-for-playstation-5-half-of-which-are-new-ip"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, it sure sounds like PlayStation Studios has been beavering away creating first-party games for the PlayStation 5, as an interview has revealed Sony currently has 25 PS5 titles in the works - half of which are new IP. 
Speaking to Wired, Guerilla confounder Hermen Hulst shared the numbers and said "there's an incredible amount of variety originating from different regions" in the pipeline, with a mixture of "big, small, different games". 
There are, of course, several first-party games we already know …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steam’s “price parity rule” isn’t wreaking havoc on game prices]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764632</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764632"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T10:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Game publishers aren't "passing on the savings" from "cheaper" online storefronts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colonial Pipeline resumes operations after ransomware prompted closure]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764758</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764758"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T00:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Closure prompted panic buying, price hikes, and other disruptions in East Coast states.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlpineConf 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://alpinelinux.org/posts/AlpineConf-2021.html</id>
        <link href="https://alpinelinux.org/posts/AlpineConf-2021.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine Linux]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alpine Linux News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vizio TV buyers are becoming the product Vizio sells, not just its customers]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764690</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764690"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T22:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vizio's ads, streaming, and data business grew 133 percent year-over-year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDC advisory committee recommends COVID vaccine for 12- to 15-year-olds]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764646</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764646"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T20:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formal approval of the Pfizer/BioNTech by the CDC expected within 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s 2nd-gen Echo Show offers better cameras, CPUs, and speakers]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764517</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764517"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T20:12:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Echo Show 8 features a 13mp wide-angle camera, 8-core CPU, and digital pan/zoom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better than holograms: 3D-animated starships can be viewed from any angle]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763689</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763689"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T19:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike holograms, the optical trap display produces images viewable from all angles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blizzard showing off Overwatch 2 PvP in two-hour livestream next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149489</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-blizzard-showing-off-overwatch-2-pvp-in-two-hour-livestream-next-week"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T18:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its announcement back at BlizzCon 2019, Overwatch 2's pre-release marketing has predominantly focussed on its new bits - which is to say its story campaign and co-op modes. PvP's still a major part of the package, of course, and Blizzard will finally be giving Overwatch 2's competitive multiplayer an airing more of an airing next week.
That's according to Overwatch game director Aaron Keller, making his Developer Update video debut following Jeff Kaplan's departure from Blizzard last month.
"We've bee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi and the US government bury the hatchet, settle investment ban]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764488</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764488"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T17:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's DOD called Xiaomi a "Communist Chinese military company" in mid-January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neural implant lets paralyzed person type by imagining writing]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764531</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764531"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T17:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A paralyzed individual hit 90 characters per minute, 99% accuracy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$50 monthly broadband discounts available starting today via 825 ISPs]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764525</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764525"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T16:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FCC's emergency pandemic fund is open, with 825 home and mobile ISPs participating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snap cuts off Yolo, LMK anonymous messaging apps after lawsuit over teen’s death]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764515</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764515"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T16:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawsuit alleges messaging apps were “dangerous and defective.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scarlet Nexus console demos arrive later this month, starting with Xbox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149466</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-scarlet-nexus-console-demos-arrive-later-this-month-starting-with-xbox"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're still trying to wrap your head around what "brain punk" is, then not to worry, as action-RPG Scarlet Nexus is getting some demos this month ahead of its release on 25th June. Hopefully that will help clear some things up. 
Bandai Namco has announced the demo will first land on Xbox Series X/S and Xbox One on 21st May, with PlayStation 4 and PS5 following on 28th May. There's no news on whether the demo is coming to PC, so we'll have to wait and see if it comes to the platform. 
Scarlet Nexus is se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valve’s Gabe Newell hints at vague console plans coming “this year”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764492</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764492"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indefinite tease comes during Q&#038;A with New Zealand students.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best smartwatches for every type of user]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764083</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764083"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We looked at smartwatches from every stripe, shape, and price point to find the best ones for your needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Gaskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[J&J vaccine supply has run out; Emergent says it’s working on improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764475</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764475"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T14:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vaccine production at Emergent's facility is still halted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Is Someone Else’s Job Zero]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8791</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/security-is-someone-elses-job-zero/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you attend an AWS talk about security, bump into an AWS security person in a business meeting, or are in line behind an AWS employee at a Starbucks, you&#8217;ll invariably hear the phrase &#8220;Security is Job Zero.&#8221; What does this actually mean? Cynically, I might suggest that they came up with a list of [&#8230;]
The post Security Is Someone Else’s Job Zero appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europa Universalis 4 director apologises for "long trail of low quality releases"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149443</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-europa-universalis-4-director-apologises-for-long-trail-of-low-quality-releases"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent Leviathan expansion for Europa Universalis 4 has managed to earn itself an unflattering spot amongst the lowest-ranked products on Steam, with a positive review rating of only seven percent from 3955 reviews. Players said the DLC was seriously buggy and suffered from a host of problems, and sure enough, the game's bug report megathreads quickly filled up with complaints. Paradox Tinto studio manager and game director Johan Andersson has now issued an apology for the state of the expansion and sev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox Series X/S adds OG Xbox dashboard theme]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149432</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-xbox-series-x-s-adds-og-xbox-dashboard-theme"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released a new dynamic theme for Xbox Series X/S which brings to life the retro, Matrix-inspired aesthetic of the OG Xbox. 
The animated background, named "The Original", is more akin to the loading animation you got when first turning on that chunky console rather than its actual dashboard, but the look will likely still feel familiar. 
Here's The Verge's Tom Warren with a preview - though it should now be rolling out to all Xbox Series X/S owners:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Book Sale: Beyond Fear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/book-sale-beyond-fear.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/book-sale-beyond-fear.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have 80 copies of my 2000 book Beyond Fear available at the very cheap price of $5 plus shipping. Note that there is a 20% chance that your book will have a &#8220;BT Counterpane&#8221; sticker on the front cover.
Order your signed copy here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft says it won't abandon paid AAA games for free-to-play]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149402</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-ubisoft-says-it-wont-abandon-paid-aaa-games-for-free-to-play"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T11:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking with investors, Ubisoft financial boss Frederick Duguet said the company's focus on releasing three to four big budget games per year was no longer "a proper indication of our value creation dynamics". Or, in normal speak, Ubisoft wanted its profits to grow by making even more money from other things.
On Twitter, Ubisoft's Sean Lama clarified this did not mean free-to-play games would replace AAA games. Instead, it meant Ubisoft now saw free-to-play as "an additional way to experience some of these…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Console Purchase Pilot looks like a new way to avoid Xbox Series scalping]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149389</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-microsoft-offers-new-way-to-avoid-xbox-series-scalping-through-insider-program"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T11:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since the new generation of consoles released at the end of last year, both the PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series consoles have suffered from stock shortages - and as a result of that, increased levels of scalping. The problem grew so severe that even British politicans began to pay attention. And with console shortages set to continue for the foreseeable future, it seems Microsoft is trialling a new way for customers to acquire a console - without everything being ruined by scalper bots. 
The new program,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volvo and Daimler bet on hydrogen truck boom this decade]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764362</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764362"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T10:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swedish and German groups expect fuel to challenge diesel in long-distance freight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Financial Times</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Destiny 2 cross-play accidentally switched on early]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149379</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-destiny-2-cross-play-accidentally-switched-on-early"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T10:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bungie has acknowledged the fact you can currently play with people from platforms other than your own in Destiny 2 - all a little earlier than planned. 
Reports of Destiny 2 crossplay being possible emerged last night, and were picked up by Destiny community manager Cozmo. 
Describing it as an unintended "sneak peek", Bungie said that crossplay was officially still in development, and would be disabled again in the coming days. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends update nerfs Spitfire and Bocek Bow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149363</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-apex-legends-update-nerfs-spitfire-and-bocek-bow"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T10:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends' Legacy update has now been live for over a week - after a somewhat wobbly start - and Respawn has already rolled out some balance changes for two weapons. The Spitfire and newly-added Bocek Bow, both considered overpowered by the player community, have been adjusted to make them a little less lethal. 
As explained on the Legacy patch notes page, the Spitfire's bullet damage has been reduced from 19 to 18, while gold and purple magazines will now hold 50 bullets instead of 55. The Bocek seems t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Battlefield 6 is designed for PS5 and Xbox Series X, but will also run on last-gen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149361</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-12-battlefield-6-is-designed-for-new-consoles-but-will-also-run-on-last-gen"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EA has discussed how Battlefield 6 will benefit from its development focus having been on current-gen consoles - PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S - even though it will also launch on last-gen hardware - PS4 and Xbox One.
The fact Battlefield 6 will not be exclusive to current-gen consoles seems somewhat obvious, in the grand scheme of things - with scalpers and low stock still prevalent and a huge, active install base for PS4 and Xbox One. But EA only made it official for the first time last night, in an e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA Award]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2462/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2462/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aston Martin’s new boss tells us about the future of the company]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764324</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764324"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T23:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former AMG CEO Tobias Moers is now in charge of the British carmaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Famed Arthurian tale comes to silver screen in The Green Knight trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764204</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764204"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T22:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Honor. That is why a knight does what he does."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rare fungal infections that destroy eyeballs and kill are on the rise in India]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764334</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764334"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T21:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People with diabetes are particularly vulnerable to the aggressive fungus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware crooks post cops’ psych evaluations after talks with DC police stall]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764296</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764296"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T21:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Babuk demands $4 million, Metropolitan Police Department offers $100,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia’s RTX 3050 brings ray tracing and DLSS to $800 laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764225</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764225"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T20:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Performance-boosting DLSS on entry-level laptops could be a big deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LucasArts' 16-bit classic Zombies Ate My Neighbors heading to PC and consoles in June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149315</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-lucasarts-16-bit-classic-zombies-ate-my-neighbors-heading-to-pc-and-consoles-in-june"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T20:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LucasArts' fondly remembered 16-bit classic Zombies At My Neighbours is getting a long-awaited re-release on Xbox, PlayStation, Switch, and PC on 29th June.
Zombies Ate My Neighbors, which originally launched on SNES and Sega Mega Drive back in 1993, follows the adventures of Zeke and Julie (who can be played solo or co-operatively) as they attempt to save their neighbours from a host of B-movie monsters - zombies, werewolves, vampires, giant ants, aliens, and so on - on a journey that stretches from suburb…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Github reverses takedown of reverse-engineered GTA source code]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764252</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764252"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T19:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identical fork is restored after DMCA counterclaim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel claims its new Tiger Lake-H CPUs for laptops beat AMD’s Ryzen 5000]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764054</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764054"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T19:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flagship Core i9-11980HK allegedly beats Ryzen 9 5900HX by 11 to 26 percent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our fave gentleman thief is back for revenge in trailer for Lupin part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764063</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764063"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Viewers frustrated by part 1's maddening cliffhanger won't have much longer to wait.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTC expanding PC VR headset line-up with Vive Pro 2 this June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149310</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-htc-expanding-pc-vr-headset-line-up-with-vive-pro-2-this-june"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTC has unveiled the latest addition to its PC VR headset line-up in the form of the Vive Pro 2, which arrives on 4th June with pre-orders open now.
As its name implies, HTC's Vive Pro 2 is the direct successor to the high-end PC VR headset it released in 2018. It'll up the ante with a 5K resolution display (2448x2448 pixels per eye), a 120-degree field of view, and a 120Hz panel. By way of contrast, the original Vive Pro featured a 2880x1600 resolution, a 110-degree field of view, and a 90Hz refresh rate.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baltimore chief prosecutor asks FCC to stop negative news coverage about her]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764100</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764100"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First Amendment prevents FCC from punishing news station for its "tone."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s MagSafe wireless charger is on sale for a new low price today]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763926</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763926"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealmaster also has wireless headphones, Switch gear, and gaming monitors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After many delays, Massachusetts’ Vineyard Wind is finally approved]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764130</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764130"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new project will be over 20 times larger than anything built in the US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel and Nvidia announce new 11th-gen laptop CPUs and RTX GPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149289</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2021-05-11-new-intel-laptop-cpus-and-nvidia-gpus-announced"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bad news: your gaming laptop is officially last-gen. That's the word from Intel and Nvidia, who teamed up today to announce new mobile processors and graphics cards. Intel is debuting their Comet Lake H CPUs, bringing their 10nm process to high-performance 45W processors ideal for gaming or content creation, while Nvidia announced two new mobile graphics cards, the RTX 3050 and 3050 Ti. Here's what you need to know.
Let's cover Nvidia's announcements first, as the company is doing something a bit unusual he…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: The Samsung/AMD Exynos SoC will be out for laptops this year]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764029</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764029"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:48:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exynos with an AMD GPU is coming for laptops, but maybe not phones?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft's beleaguered pirate game Skull & Bones now won't arrive before 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149305</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-ubisofts-beleaguered-pirate-game-skull-and-bones-now-wont-arrive-before-2022"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft has confirmed its long-announced and much-postponed shared-world swashbuckler Skull &amp; Bones is now expected to release in the 2022-2023 financial year.
Originally revealed back at E3 2017, Skull &amp; Bones - which is being developed by Ubisoft Singapore - was initially due to release on Xbox, PS4, and PC sometime the following year. However, it's now been subject to two official delays, once in 2018 and another in 2019.
As part of the latter announcement, Ubisoft told fans, "We're going to batt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stargate: Timekeepers is an RTS coming to PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149252</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-stargate-timekeepers-is-an-rts-coming-to-pc"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember Stargate? 27 years after the much-loved sci-fi film came out, a new Stargate game has been announced.
Stargate: Timekeepers is a real-time strategy game set for PC and in development at Creative Forge Games, the Polish studio behind Phantom Doctrine and Hard West. It's published by Slitherine.
The teaser video below does not include gameplay, but we do get to see a Stargate. It's all very '90s.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EA swerves E3 to hold live event in July]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149286</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-ea-swerves-e3-to-hold-live-event-in-july"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EA Play Live, the publisher's big annual announcement show, will be held this year on 22nd July. 
That's a month later than 2021's digital-only E3 event, which is dated for 12th to 15th June. 
EA has not been a major part of E3 for years, instead opting to hold its own EA Play events elsewhere. E3 is traditionally held at the Los Angeles Convention Centre, while in recent years EA has housed its own show at the same time a few miles away up in Hollywood. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming a robot to teach itself how to move]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764044</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764044"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T16:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flexible, open-ended learning software works but finds the real world difficult.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTC’s newest headsets signal end of Vive’s 5-year “VR for the home” mission]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763889</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763889"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T16:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vive Focus 3 is a $1,299, enterprise-grade answer to Oculus Quest 2, plus Vive Pro 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon and others ordered to slash diesel pollution from warehouse trucks]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764041</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764041"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T15:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Southern California is being smothered by pollution from e-commerce warehouses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch is getting a calculator app, priced £8]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149270</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-nintendo-switch-is-getting-a-calculator-app-priced-gbp8"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T15:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The application, simply named Calculator, launches on the Nintendo Switch eShop tomorrow,12th May, priced £8.09.
Calculator is a third-party app, not made by Nintendo, and one of the rare few non-gaming applications to make it onto the eShop. Of course, some people do find maths fun - perhaps even a game! I am not one of these people.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galactic Civilizations 4 due out 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149265</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-galactic-civilizations-4-due-out-2022"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Galactic Civilizations 4 is due out on PC in 2022, Stardock has announced.
The space 4X strategy sandbox sequel goes into early access later this spring. The announcement trailer is below:
The player begins with only their home planet and must research new technologies, explore the known galaxy and colonise new worlds while keeping their people at home happy. At the same time, players engage in trade, diplomacy, intrigue and war with alien civilisations.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Security Risk Assessment Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/ai-security-risk-assessment-tool.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/ai-security-risk-assessment-tool.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T14:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft researchers just released an open-source automation tool for security testing AI systems: &#8220;Counterfit.&#8221; Details on their blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fatal Tesla Model S crash unlikely to involve Autopilot, according to NTSB]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764018</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1764018"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Was the person found in the back of the car trying to manually release the door?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse-engineered GTA code restored after developer files DMCA counterclaim]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149208</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-reverse-engineered-gta-code-restored-after-developer-files-dmca-counterclaim"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T12:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse-engineered GTA code was restored after its developer filed a DMCA counterclaim on GitHub.
TorrentFreak reports GitHub restored a fork of the fan-made re3 project after its creator filed a Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA) takedown counter-claim.
As Eurogamer reported in February, the Grand Theft Auto 3 and Vice City reverse-engineering fan project known as re3 was hit by a DMCA filed by Rockstar parent company Take-Two that claimed copyright infringement.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite's new PVE survival mode Daybreak looks set to launch soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149187</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-fortnites-new-pve-survival-mode-looks-set-to-launch-soon"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortnite looks ready to launch its sandbox survival mode, Daybreak, according to files added in today's new 16.40 patch. 
We've seen glimpses of Daybreak before, in leaked files from previous patches and also, intriguingly, via internal documentation released as part of the ongoing Apple v Epic trial, dated from last year. This suggested it has been in the works for quite some time, and was set to arrive a lot sooner.
"You wake up alone and unarmed along the coast of an island, with no memory of how you arr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baby Chris, Lady X and Dante lead the early days of Resident Evil Village modding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149186</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-baby-chris-lady-x-and-dante-lead-the-early-days-of-resident-evil-village-modding"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's early days in the burgeoning demand for Resident Evil Village mods, but already the community has come up with some... interesting tweaks.
THERE MAY BE RESIDENT EVIL VILLAGE SPOILERS AHEAD.
Mini Me Chris is one of the more eye-catching mods, simply because of how nightmarish it is. Modder JTeghius Kittius said: "This was a dumb joke that popped into my head so I had to do this."
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Unbannable" Apex Legends cheater faces potential legal action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149185</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-unbannable-apex-legends-cheater-faces-potential-legal-action"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Respawn recently reassured players that it was exploring "every avenue" to take down Apex Legends cheaters - legal action being one of them - and it seems one high-profile cheater is already facing something worse than the ban hammer. Prolific cheater Tufi, who some in the Apex Legends community have described as a "God" and "unbannable" cheater, is apparently facing some form of legal action from Respawn - although details remain light on exactly how far this has progressed. 
Earlier this week Apex Legends…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new book, Amazon Unbound, reveals Jeff Bezos’ envy of SpaceX]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763718</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763718"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bezos tried to hire Gwynne Shotwell to run Blue Origin in 2016.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warhammer 40,000: Battlesector now out in July]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149172</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-warhammer-40-000-battlesector-now-out-in-july"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warhammer 40,000: Battlesector comes out 15th July on PC, PlayStation and Xbox priced £30.99, publisher Slitherine has announced.
The PC version of the Blood Angels versus Tyranids turn-based strategy game was due out in May, with the console versions to follow in the summer. But Slitherine is now going for a joined-up launch across all platforms in July.
Battlesector is developed by Black Lab Games, maker of the well-received Battlestar Galactica Deadlock. It's described as "battle-scale", and based on gam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic v Apple trial debates appropriateness of Fortnite's naked banana man Peely]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149171</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-epic-v-apple-trial-debates-the-appropriateness-of-fortnites-naked-banana-man-peely"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was inevitable: the appropriateness of Fortnite's bizarre banana man Peely has now been discussed in open court.
Last night, in the ongoing Apple v Epic trial, Peely came under scrutiny for being a naked piece of fruit with arms and legs.
In remarks transcribed from the courtroom by Verge reporter Adi Robertson, a lawyer for Apple brought up Peely in court and made a deal of showing the character wearing clothes (his Chapter 2 Season 2 Bond-esque Agent Peely tuxedo).
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance 2 re-release "on the table"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149155</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-baldurs-gate-dark-alliance-2-re-release-on-the-table"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T09:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A PC port of Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance is coming later this year, Black Isle Studios has confirmed.
The cult classic console RPG re-released last week on PlayStation and Xbox consoles (the Nintendo Switch version is still M.I.A.). The console launch trailer is below:
"The PC port of BG:DA is in the works and coming later this year," Black Isle tweeted.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil Village ships over 3m copies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149144</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-11-resident-evil-village-ships-over-3m-copies"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capcom has shipped over 3m copies of Resident Evil Village, the company has announced.
The horror game went on sale on Friday, 7th May, and has launched strong. (Digital Foundry's Resident Evil Village tech breakdown is in the video below:)
In the UK, Village is already the second-highest UK boxed debut this year, beaten only by Super Mario 3D World + Bowser's Fury, and has set franchise records for concurrent players on Steam.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDA authorizes Pfizer’s COVID-19 vaccine for 12- to 15-year-olds]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763967</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763967"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T23:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CDC's advisory committee will meet Wednesday to vote on recommending use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev turns The Room 4: Old Sins' creepy old dollhouse into a gorgeous Lego build]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149114</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-fireproof-dev-turns-the-room-4-old-sins-creepy-old-dollhouse-into-gorgeous-lego-build"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lego is (as a year in lockdown with a whole lot to time to assemble plastic bricks has taught me) cool, and developer Fireproof Games' gorgeously atmospheric The Room puzzle series is, among many other good things, cool too. So it should come as absolutely no surprise to anyone that combining the two results in a very cool thing indeed.
The architect of this particular very cool thing is Fireproof Games' own graphic and motion designer Roger Schembri who, under the name Lego CustardKid, has previously submi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple invests $45 million more in Gorilla Glass-maker Corning]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763824</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763824"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:19:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investment follows millions more that produced the iPhone 12's ceramic shield.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware Shuts Down US Pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/ransomware-shuts-down-us-pipeline.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/ransomware-shuts-down-us-pipeline.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T19:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a major story: a probably Russian cybercrime group called DarkSide shut down the Colonial Pipeline in a ransomware attack. The pipeline supplies much of the East Coast. This is the new and improved ransomware attack: the hackers stole nearly 100 gig of data, and are threatening to publish it. The White House has declared a state of emergency and has created a task force to deal with the problem, but it&#8217;s unclear what they can do. This is bad; our supply chains are so tightly coupled that this …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon “seized and destroyed” 2 million counterfeit products in 2020]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763878</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763878"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T19:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Counterfeit products sent to Amazon warehouses are destroyed to prevent resale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the battle of the alien symbiotes in Venom: Let There Be Carnage trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763740</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763740"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T18:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I've been thinking about you, Eddie, because you and I are the same."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By eating them, hyenas gathered 9 Neanderthal skeletons in one cave]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763816</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763816"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T18:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Neanderthals appear to have met a very bad end.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiona N. Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security researcher successfully jailbreaks an Apple AirTag]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763811</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763811"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T17:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Successful jailbreak increases existing AirTag security and privacy concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google: We put YouTube TV in the main YouTube app. What now, Roku?]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763745</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763745"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T17:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google sidesteps the YouTube TV ban, threatens to send free devices to customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First (brief) look at Rambo in Call of Duty: Warzone and Black Ops Cold War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149098</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-first-brief-look-at-rambo-in-call-of-duty-warzone-and-black-ops-cold-war"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Activision has offered a glimpse at Rambo in Call of Duty: Warzone and Black Ops Cold War.
The official Call of Duty Twitter account released a short clip showing Rambo preparing to unleash a fire arrow from his trademark bow at an unfortunate victim, alongside the tagline: "Become war."
Rambo arrives on 20th May as part of the mid-season update for Season 3 - no doubt as a costly soldier skin.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AstraZeneca’s troubled vaccine not renewed in EU; Pfizer gets big, new deal]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763808</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763808"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T17:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meanwhile, China’s Sinopharm vaccine—79% efficacy, easy to store—authorized by WHO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers who shut down pipeline: We don’t want to cause “problems for society”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763760</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763760"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T16:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The attack paralyzed a pipeline that moves 2.5 million barrels per day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Private-equity firm revives zombie fossil-fuel power plant to mine bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763789</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763789"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T16:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Power plant was left for dead until the cryptocurrency boom came along.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ford picks a name for its electric pickup truck: The F-150 Lightning]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763748</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763748"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T16:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SVT F-150 Lightning was a factory hot rod pickup in the 1990s.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony says PS5 could be difficult to find into 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763751</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763751"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T15:26:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Healthy demand, semiconductor shortage combine to keep the system hard to find.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s our first look at 2023’s electric Porsche Macan SUV]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763731</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763731"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T14:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Macan will share an electric platform with Audi's next A6 and Q6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Movie director says Capcom copied his monster for Resident Evil Village boss fight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149044</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-movie-director-says-capcom-copied-his-propellerhead-monster-for-resident-evil-village-boss-fight"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T13:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A movie director has accused Capcom of copying one of his monsters for a Resident Evil Village boss fight.
Dutch director Richard Raaphorst said the Sturm boss found in the recently-released Resident Evil Village is a "one-to-one" copy of a monster he created for his 2013 found footage horror film Frankenstein's Army.
Capcom failed to comment by press time.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A SpaceX booster now trails only 4 space shuttles in flight experience]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763707</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763707"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T12:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This particular first stage is approaching historic status.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Valheim mod lets you build some really big boats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149025</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-this-valheim-mod-lets-you-build-your-own-boat"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever felt like going on a big cruise ship around the mythical world of Valheim? Thanks to the power of modding, now you can, so get ready for some very large vessels.
ValheimRAFT is a mod by Sarcen that allows players to construct their own ships rather than simply use the pre-made ones available in vanilla Valheim. (If the name didn't give it away, it's inspired by the game Raft, a survival game in which you construct a boat from bits of debris.) I had a quick tinker with it and made a basic ghost…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Unclassified NSA Document on Cryptography in the 1970s]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/newly-unclassified-nsa-document-on-cryptography-in-the-1970s.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/newly-unclassified-nsa-document-on-cryptography-in-the-1970s.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a newly unclassified NSA history of its reaction to academic cryptography in the 1970s: &#8220;New Comes Out of the Closet: The Debate over Public Cryptography in the Inman Era,&#8221; Cryptographic Quarterly, Spring 1996, author still classified.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Automotive OS review: Under the hood with Google’s car OS]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1751715</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1751715"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AAOS nails the car platform fundamentals, but it needs more apps and features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft will now brand all its own games as "Ubisoft Originals"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149009</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-ubisoft-will-now-brand-all-its-own-games-as-ubisoft-originals"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T10:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assassin's Creed and Far Cry publisher Ubisoft will now brand all of its games made by internal studios as "Ubisoft Originals". 
The name first cropped up last week, when Ubisoft announced Tom Clancy's The Division: Heartland, a new free-to-play spin-off due later this year or early next.
When asked whether this label meant anything more than fancy new branding, a Ubisoft spokesperson told Eurogamer today that, "Moving forward 'The Ubisoft Original' mention is attached to all of Ubisoft's games created in-h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony expects it will continue to struggle to meet PS5 demand into 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2149006</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-sony-expects-it-will-continue-to-struggle-to-meet-ps5-demand-into-2022"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T10:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The constrained supply of the PlayStation 5 will continue into 2022, Sony has warned.
The company's CFO, Hiroki Totoki, said Sony will struggle to meet demand even with a supply boost, Bloomberg reported (paywall).
As most know, the PS5 is incredibly hard to buy at the moment, with stock snapped up as soon as it goes on sale. The console has also been the focus of scalpers, who sell on for an inflated price. Retailers have struggled to prevent new consoles from getting into the hands of scalper groups, some…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monster Hunter Rise and Resident Evil 3 fuel another record year for Capcom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148978</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-10-monster-hunter-rise-and-resident-evil-3-fuel-another-record-year-for-capcom"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T09:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capcom has seen record profits for the fourth year in a row.
Revenue for the financial year ending 31st March 2021 was 95.3bn yen (£622m), up 16.8 percent from the previous year, with profit of 34.6bn yen (£226m), up 51.6 percent from the previous fiscal year)
Capcom pointed to the success of Monster Hunter Rise and the Resident Evil 3 remake, as well as sales growth for high margin back catalogue titles including Monster Hunter World: Iceborne and the Resident Evil 2 remake. Capcom said the PlayStation 5 a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[90's Kid Space Program]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2461/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2461/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Registration for Final Fantasy 7 battle royale, The First Soldier, is now open]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148951</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-09-registration-for-final-fantasy-7-battle-royale-the-first-soldier-is-now-open"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T13:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Registration to participate in the closed beta for Square Enix's upcoming battle royale, Final Fantasy 7 The First Soldier, is now open.
Prospective players have from now until 27th May 2021 to register their interest, although right now, the beta is restricted to players with 64-bit, 7.1+ Android phones with at least 3GB of memory available.
As is usually the case with these things, registering does not guarantee you a spot in the closed beta, but the sign-up page hints that it wants "tons of players" to g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumour suggests two new colourful DualSense controllers could go on sale "very soon"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148950</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-09-rumour-suggests-two-new-colourful-dualsense-controllers-could-go-on-sale-very-soon"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T13:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new rumour purports two new DualSense controllers could be coming to market "very soon".
According to AreaJugones - a Spanish-language site that has previously correctly leaked a PlayStation Plus freebie lineup ahead of confirmation from PlayStation - the new colour schemes deviate from the current white and black scheme to include shades of red and grey. 
Without photographic evidence, it's not possible to know precisely how the colours will be used, or what parts of the controller will be more colourful…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Careful, Wattson fans - her fence in Apex Legends is useless right now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148945</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-09-careful-wattson-fans-her-fence-in-apex-legends-is-useless-right-now"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T12:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Respawn has seemingly nerfed Wattson's electrified fence in Apex Legends.
As spotted and shared by Twitterer LilakeyLK, it looks as though the latest season has not only introduced a new Legend and competitive mode Arenas, but it's also made a tweak to one of Wattson's key defences... with an emphasis on "fence".
Previously, running into Wattson's fence would slow down an opposing player, but now it looks as though the slowdown and corresponding stun has been removed, essentially making the fence useless (t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New book Press Reset investigates the high human cost of game development]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763446</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763446"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T12:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beloved game-industry journo aims his lens at the little people making big video games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remnant: From the Ashes gets a free next-gen upgrade later this week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148944</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-09-remnant-from-the-ashes-gets-a-free-next-gen-upgrade-later-this-week"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remnant: From the Ashes will shortly receive a free next-gen update to "enhance both frame rate and resolution".
According to developer Gunfire Games, on 13th May players will "receive a free major upgrade patch that will add the option to run the game at 4K resolution at 30fps the PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X, or 1080p resolution at 60fps on both the PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S".
That's not all, either. On the same day, the game will also be added to the PC version of Xbox Game Pass - up until now…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Activision severs links with Call of Duty Ghost voice actor following misogynistic comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148943</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-09-activision-severs-links-with-call-of-duty-ghost-voice-actor-following-misogynistic-comments"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T11:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Activision has cut ties with Call of Duty: Modern Warfare's Ghost voice actor Jeff Leach following the dissemination of a video that compiles his misogynist comments.
The montage - which was shared online by streamers hitting back at Leach's derogatory statements - is described as containing "serious personalised intrusive sexism" and shows Leach using sexually explicit and aggressive language as well as personal insults. 
"In 2021, misogyny has no place," states a caption on the video. "Yet female gamers r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Amy Klobuchar just wrote 600 pages on antitrust]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763506</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763506"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T10:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Monopolies tend to have a lot of control, not just over consumers, but also over politics."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Die Hard's John McClane teased for Call of Duty: Warzone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148912</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-die-hards-john-mcclane-teased-for-call-of-duty-warzone"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T20:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 1980s action movie heroes are coming en masse to Warzone. After this week's tease that Rambo will be added to the battle royale, Activision has indicated Die Hard's John McClane is on his way, too.
Activision even created a website for a fictional air conditioning repair company called Nakatomi Duct Cleaning, offering its services in Verdansk.
The website says "A NAKATOMI CORP DIVISION MASTERING A/C DUCT CLEANING SINCE 1988", but the current Warzone map is set in 1984. Nah... I'm applying too much logic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capcom made a huge chalk lycan on a hill in Somerset to promote Resident Evil Village]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148911</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-capcom-made-a-huge-chalk-artwork-of-a-lycan-on-a-hill-in-somerset-to-promote-resident-evil-village"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T19:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, if you pottered along to the Mendip Hill near Cheddar, Somerset, you'd probably have caught a glimpse of something a bit off: a huge chalk artwork of a lycan.
Local press reported the strange image on Monday, 3rd May after it popped up overnight - and seemingly had no idea what it was about or who made it.
Its true nature was revealed when Resident Evil Village came out on Friday - it was a Capcom PR stunt. And a pretty cool one, I'll admit.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modder's Nier: Automata HD texture pack finally complete after four years of development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148910</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-modders-nier-automata-hd-texture-pack-finally-complete-after-four-years-of-development"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T18:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A modder has released their final Nier: Automata HD texture pack after four years of development.
GPUnity's texture pack mod began life soon after Nier: Automata launched on PC in March 2017. They've continued to work on the mod since then, and now, four years later, released the final version.
Nier: Automata's PC version is infamous for a raft of technical issues that were fixed by modders, including a constant stutter tick due to the game running at around 59 frames per second (this is something explored …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: The role-playing game’s afoot in charming dark comedy Murder Bury Win]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1759895</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1759895"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T18:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not an instant classic like  Clue,  but it's fun, very solid indie fare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sega: No plans for Lost Judgment on PC "at this time"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148909</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-sega-no-plans-for-lost-judgment-on-pc-at-this-time"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Sega announced Lost Judgment for PlayStation 5, PlayStation 4, Xbox Series X and S, and Xbox One - but there was no word of a PC version.
It seemed an odd omission - Tojo Dojo noticed the Yakuza spin-off sequel was briefly listed as coming to PC on the official countdown website that was home to the Lost Judgment announcement. Even after mention of PC was removed from the website, fans spotted mention of the Steam logo in the Lost Judgment website source code.
Unfortunately, it appears Lost Judgm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivian’s electric truck features include air compressor and AC outlets]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763611</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763611"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T17:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's got storage compartments galore, plus an extending truck bed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple brass discussed disclosing 128-million iPhone hack, then decided not to]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763592</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763592"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T16:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emails entered into Epic Games lawsuit show execs contradicting Apple talking points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Goodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance re-release on Nintendo Switch delayed at the last minute]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148906</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-baldurs-gate-dark-alliance-re-release-on-nintendo-switch-delayed-at-the-last-minute"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T15:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance's re-release on Nintendo Switch was delayed at the last minute.
The re-release of the much-loved 20 year-old action RPG went ahead as planned yesterday on Xbox One, where it costs a pricey £29.99, and PlayStation 4, where for some reason it costs a fiver cheaper at £24.99.
But even though the official Black Isle Studios Twitter page said yesterday that the Switch version would arrive in a couple of hours, the game failed to materialise on the Nintendo eShop.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Titanfall 2 Gauntlet world record broken twice in two weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148905</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-titanfall-2-gauntlet-world-record-broken-twice-in-a-week"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T15:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Titanfall 2 enjoying an Apex Legends-powered resurgence, so is its superb Gauntlet.
Respawn's wall-hopping assault course tasks players with completing one lap as quickly as possible - and nearly five years after Titanfall 2 came out, speedrunners are breaking world records again.
In October 2019, speedrunner Cash Mayo set an incredible time of 11.7 seconds, shaving a fraction off Mayo's previous world record of 11.9 seconds:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["The Yakuza series has been transformed into a turn-based RPG," says dev]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148879</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-the-yakuza-series-has-been-transformed-into-a-turn-based-rpg-says-dev"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T11:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking to IGN, Yakuza creator Toshihiro Nagoshi and producer Kazuki Hosokawa confirmed the plan for the two series:
"The Yakuza series has been transformed into a turn-based RPG. On the other hand, over the years, Ryu ga Gotoku Studio has accumulated resources and know-how of making flashy and exhilarating action games that are effortless to enjoy. We decided that we should let our signature action gameplay live on through Lost Judgment."
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil Village is off to a flyer on Steam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148875</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-resident-evil-village-is-off-to-a-flyer-on-steam"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil Village is off to a flyer on Steam.
It saw 101,726 peak concurrents on launch day, 7th May.
That makes Capcom's latest comfortably the biggest PC launch for any Resident Evil game. According to SteamCharts, Resident Evil 7 managed an all-time peak of 18,211 concurrents, Resident Evil 6 peaked with 11,836, and the most recent release, the Resident Evil 3 remake, hit 32,635. Only the Resident Evil 2 remake, which saw a concurrents peak of 74,024, comes close.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raven is trying to raise Call of Duty: Warzone's skill ceiling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148870</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-08-call-of-duty-warzone-developer-says-its-battle-royale-is-close-to-a-balance-homeostasis"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T10:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Warzone developer Raven has said it is close to a "balance homeostasis", where most weapon options are "at the very least viable" - leaving it to focus on raising the skill ceiling of the game.
The developer shared its balance change philosophy as part of the patch notes for a Warzone update that went live this week.
Raven spoke openly about the difficulty it faces making sweeping changes to the Warzone meta, as popular guns are inevitably affected.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It began as an AI-fueled dungeon game. Then it got much darker]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763513</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763513"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T10:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI algorithm created disturbing stories, including sex scenes involving children.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sniper Ghost Warrior Contracts 2 gets PS5 delay due to "unforeseen technical issues"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148855</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-sniper-ghost-warrior-contracts-2-gets-ps5-delay-due-to-unforeseen-technical-issues"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T21:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CI Games has announced a delay for the PlayStation 5 version of its upcoming long-distance shooter Sniper Ghost Warrior Contracts 2, resulting from "unforeseen technical issues".
Sniper Ghost Warrior Contracts 2 - which features a "dramatic single-player campaign set in modern day Middle East" - was originally due on PlayStation 5 on 4th June, arriving alongside versions for PS4, Xbox One, Xbox X/S and PC. However, despite the PS5 edition's delay to a currently unspecified future point, other platforms will…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 “Sun Valley” will do away with Windows 95 era icons]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763533</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763533"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T21:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The results are more subtle than you might expect from a 25+ year visual update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: COVID Relief Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/friday-squid-blogging-covid-relief-funds.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/friday-squid-blogging-covid-relief-funds.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T21:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A town in Japan built a giant squid statue with its COVID relief grant.
One local told the Chunichi Shimbun newspaper that while the statue may be effective in the long run, the money could have been used for &#8220;urgent support,&#8221; such as for medical staff and long-term care facilities.
But a spokesperson for the town told Fuji News Network that the statue would be a tourist attraction and part of a long term strategy to help promote Noto&#8217;s famous flying squid.

I am impressed by the town&#821…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony faces lawsuit over alleged “monopoly pricing” of PlayStation downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763530</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763530"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T20:19:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proposed class action says Sony's moves have increased prices for PlayStation games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Orland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Returnal reinstating pre-rollback fixes in new patch tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148850</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-returnal-reinstating-pre-rollback-fixes-in-new-patch-tomorrow"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T20:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Housemarque is releasing a new patch for PlayStation 5-exclusive roguelite Returnal tomorrow, 8th May, which will, among other things, reinstate all pre-rollback fixes that briefly went live earlier this week.
On Wednesday, Housemarque was forced to pull Returnal's 1.3.3 patch after players began reporting it was corrupting save games. The developer later released version 1.3.4, which rolled back to Returnal's most recent stable build - a move that enabled some affected players to resume their pro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[96% of US users opt out of app tracking in iOS 14.5, analytics find]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763464</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763464"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the first data on user behavior exceeds advertisers' worst fears.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ajit Pai promised cheaper Internet—real prices rose 19 percent instead]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763472</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763472"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Home-Internet prices rose four times faster than inflation in Trump era.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skullgirls 2nd Encore's next DLC fighter Umbrella has a ravenous sentient brolly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148849</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-skullgirls-2nd-encores-next-dlc-fighter-umbrella-has-a-ravenous-sentient-brolly"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Hidden Variable has unveiled the latest DLC character to join the roster of acclaimed fighters Skullgirls 2nd Encore and the free-to-play Skullgirls Mobile: the sou'westered, be-wellied Umbrella and her sentient brolly chum, Hungern.
Umbrella, the second DLC character to arrive as part of Skullgirls 2nd Encore's season pass (following on from March's Annie), is described as a small, slow character with limited movement that's able to take some "big swings" thanks Hungern.
Indeed, while the perpetu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Autopilot director contradicts Musk’s self-driving timeline]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763422</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763422"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk described full autonomy as "basically a solved problem" in 2016.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy B. Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acclaimed post-apocalyptic city builder Frostpunk is heading to mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148841</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-acclaimed-post-apocalyptic-city-builder-frostpunk-is-heading-to-mobile"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer 11 Bit Studios' superb post-apocalyptic city builder Frostpunk is coming to iOS and Android devices "later this year".
Frostpunk initially launched on PC in 2018 before making its way to Xbox and PlayStation the following year. It's a fascinating, frequently gruelling, and wonderfully atmospheric experience, delivering a captivating blend of brutal survival sim, city builder, and rich narrative as players attempt to survive - through the slow expansion their settlement, and with plenty of tough mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google wants people to use 2FA, so it’s just going to turn it on for them]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763423</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763423"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-tech-savvy users always use the defaults, and the default will soon be 2FA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook and Big Pharma exploited disease “awareness” for personalized marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763427</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763427"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visiting medical sites, patient support groups, and more feed the algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did our ancestors kill all the island megafauna?]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763424</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763424"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T15:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Study adds data to a long-running argument.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ars Contributors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDPR in talks to use The Witcher 3 mods in official next-gen version]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148822</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-the-witcher-3s-next-gen-version-might-use-fan-made-mods"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T14:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ray-tracing, faster load times and more. But rather unexpectedly, it seems some of these improvements are coming from the community, as CDPR has confirmed that it is in talks with those who made mods for the 2015 game. 
Kotaku spotted that mod creator Halk Hogan, responsible for The Witcher 3 HD Reworked project, had announced he'd received an "official message from CDPR about cooperation", and that "it's very likely HDRP will be included in the official next generation update". CDPR then confirmed to Kotak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is an Edge Location in AWS? A Simple Explanation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8740</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/what-is-an-edge-location-in-aws-a-simple-explanation/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS edge locations are designed to deliver services with as less latency as possible. Learn more about edge locations, use cases, and where they might make sense for your organization.
The post What is an Edge Location in AWS? A Simple Explanation appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost Judgment leaks on PlayStation Store ahead of official reveal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148717</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-lost-judgment-leaks-on-playstation-store-ahead-of-official-reveal"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Sega has officially announced Lost Judgment, the Judgment sequel due out globally 24th September 2021 on PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, Xbox Series X and S.
Developer Ryu Ga Gotoku Studio said in addition to Kamurocho, fans will be able to adventure to the scenic port city of Yokohama. One of the most important new locations is a high school, with a "highly detailed" interior. The trailer is below:
The developers have leaned heavily on the fast-paced action portion of the original game. The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valheim modders are fleshing out the game's unused biomes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2148799</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-05-07-valheim-modders-are-fleshing-out-the-games-unused-biomes"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you've finished all the biomes and bosses currently available in Valheim - what now? Well, you could wait for the next official update from Iron Gate: but the next biome is quite a few updates away, so you may be waiting a while to explore the Mistlands in all their glory. 
Alternatively, you can just install a bunch of mods. Here's a video of me exploring a rejuvenated Ashlands, and running away performing a tactical retreat when I realised that the enemies are actually quite difficult. Thank goodness I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eurogamer.net | News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching Cybersecurity to Children]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/teaching-cybersecurity-to-children.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/teaching-cybersecurity-to-children.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T13:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new draft of an Australian educational curriculum proposes teaching children as young as five cybersecurity:
The proposed curriculum aims to teach five-year-old children &#8212; an age at which Australian kids first attend school &#8212; not to share information such as date of birth or full names with strangers, and that they should consult parents or guardians before entering personal information online.
Six-and-seven-year-olds will be taught how to use usernames and passwords, and the pitfalls of click…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM creates the world’s first 2 nm chip]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763407</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763407"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T11:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM's new 2 nm process offers transistor density similar to TSMC's next-gen 3 nm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unsolved mysteries of the Warhammer 40k universe with loremaster Dan Abnett]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762186</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762186"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T11:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best-selling author goes deep—like, real deep—on wild and crazy Warhammer questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Hutchinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why hasn’t Waymo expanded its driverless service? Here’s my theory]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762459</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762459"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suburban ride-hailing is a lousy business to be in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy B. Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vaccinated]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2460/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2460/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What cats’ love of boxes and squares can tell us about their visual perception]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762974</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1762974"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T21:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Vision has evolved to answer questions having to do with boundaries and contours."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9,000 fliers may have had reused swabs jammed up their noses in Indonesia]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763266</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1763266"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T20:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five workers were arrested for washing and reusing cotton swabs for testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Story of Colossus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/the-story-of-colossus.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/the-story-of-colossus.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nice video of a talk by Chris Shore on the history of Colossus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Spectre-Like Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/new-spectre-like-attacks.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/new-spectre-like-attacks.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T15:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There&#8217;s new research that demonstrates security vulnerabilities in all of the AMD and Intel chips with micro-op caches, including the ones that were specifically engineered to be resistant to the Spectre/Meltdown attacks of three years ago.
Details:
The new line of attacks exploits the micro-op cache: an on-chip structure that speeds up computing by storing simple commands and allowing the processor to fetch them quickly and early in the speculative execution process, as the team explains in a writeup…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Portals Are an Anti-Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8725</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/developer-portals-are-an-anti-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer portals can be used to enforce standardization and to enable multi-cloud use cases. But they also have some serious issues and should be avoided in most cases. 
The post Developer Portals Are an Anti-Pattern appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 2020]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2459/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2459/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Remotely Hacked from a Drone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/tesla-remotely-hacked-from-a-drone.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/tesla-remotely-hacked-from-a-drone.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:41:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an impressive hack:
Security researchers Ralf-Philipp Weinmann of Kunnamon, Inc. and Benedikt Schmotzle of Comsecuris GmbH have found remote zero-click security vulnerabilities in an open-source software component (ConnMan) used in Tesla automobiles that allowed them to compromise parked cars and control their infotainment systems over WiFi. It would be possible for an attacker to unlock the doors and trunk, change seat positions, both steering and acceleration modes &#8212; in short, pretty much wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying the Person Behind Bitcoin Fog]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/identifying-the-person-behind-bitcoin-fog.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/05/identifying-the-person-behind-bitcoin-fog.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T14:36:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The person behind the Bitcoin Fog was identified and arrested. Bitcoin Fog was an anonymization service: for a fee, it mixed a bunch of people&#8217;s bitcoins up so that it was hard to figure out where any individual coins came from. It ran for ten years.
Identifying the person behind Bitcoin Fog serves as an illustrative example of how hard it is to be anonymous online in the face of a competent police investigation:
Most remarkable, however, is the IRS&#8217;s account of tracking down Sterlingov using th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bubble Wrap]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2458/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2458/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: On Squid Coloration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/friday-squid-blogging-on-squid-coloration.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/friday-squid-blogging-on-squid-coloration.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T21:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nice excerpt from Martin Wallin&#8217;s book Squid.
As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.
Read my blog posting guidelines here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DynamoDB vs. MongoDB: A Comparison and How to Choose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8713</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/dynamodb-vs-mongodb-a-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T14:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A real world comparison of two wildly successful modern replacements for traditional database systems.
The post DynamoDB vs. MongoDB: A Comparison and How to Choose appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Scanlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serious MacOS Vulnerability Patched]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/serous-macos-vulnerability-patched.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/serous-macos-vulnerability-patched.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T12:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple just patched a MacOS vulnerability that bypassed malware checks.
The flaw is akin to a front entrance that&#8217;s barred and bolted effectively, but with a cat door at the bottom that you can easily toss a bomb through. Apple mistakenly assumed that applications will always have certain specific attributes. Owens discovered that if he made an application that was really just a script—code that tells another program what do rather than doing it itself—and didn&#8217;t include a standard application me…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After the Pandemic]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2457/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2457/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying People Through Lack of Cell Phone Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/identifying-people-through-lack-of-cell-phone-use.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/04/identifying-people-through-lack-of-cell-phone-use.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T11:07:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this entertaining story of French serial criminal Rédoine Faïd and his jailbreaking ways, there&#8217;s this bit about cell phone surveillance:
After Faïd&#8217;s helicopter breakout, 3,000 police officers took part in the manhunt. According to the 2019 documentary La Traque de Rédoine Faïd, detective units scoured records of cell phones used during his escape, isolating a handful of numbers active at the time that went silent shortly thereafter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sun Also Crashes: Keeping Current]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8701</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/the-sun-also-crashes-keeping-current/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you let the tech you’re skilled in become the cornerstone of your identity, you limit future career possibilities. Here’s what to do instead
The post The Sun Also Crashes: Keeping Current appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confidence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/confidence/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/confidence/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Amazon Athena? An Introduction and Walkthrough]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8676</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/what-is-amazon-athena-an-introduction-and-walkthrough/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Amazon Athena right for your organization? Learn about the pros and cons of the serverless query service to see if it makes sense for your use case.
The post What is Amazon Athena? An Introduction and Walkthrough appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect Fit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/perfect-fit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/perfect-fit/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.21: Metrics Stability hits GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/23/kubernetes-release-1.21-metrics-stability-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/23/kubernetes-release-1.21-metrics-stability-ga/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Han Kang (Google), Elana Hashman (Red Hat)
Kubernetes 1.21 marks the graduation of the metrics stability framework and along with it, the first officially supported stable metrics. Not only do stable metrics come with supportability guarantees, the metrics stability framework brings escape hatches that you can use if you encounter problematic metrics.
See the list of stable Kubernetes metrics here
What are stable metrics and why do we need them?
A stable metric is one which, from a consumption poin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Evolving Kubernetes networking with the Gateway API]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/22/evolving-kubernetes-networking-with-the-gateway-api/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/04/22/evolving-kubernetes-networking-with-the-gateway-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Mark Church (Google), Harry Bagdi (Kong), Daneyon Hanson (Red Hat), Nick Young (VMware), Manuel Zapf (Traefik Labs)
The Ingress resource is one of the many Kubernetes success stories. It created a diverse ecosystem of Ingress controllers which were used across hundreds of thousands of clusters in a standardized and consistent way. This standardization helped users adopt Kubernetes. However, five years after the creation of Ingress, there are signs of fragmentation into different but strikingly simi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[S3’s Durability Guarantees Aren’t What You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=8662</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/s3s-durability-guarantees-arent-what-you-think/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[S3 has insanely generous data durability guarantees. Even so, read the fine print, and you’ll realize that S3 doesn’t remove the need for backups.
The post S3&#8217;s Durability Guarantees Aren&#8217;t What You Think appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>