<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-10-08T06:26:35.153Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing ClusterClass and Managed Topologies in Cluster API]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/10/08/capi-clusterclass-and-managed-topologies/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/10/08/capi-clusterclass-and-managed-topologies/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Fabrizio Pandini (VMware)
The Cluster API community is happy to announce the implementation of ClusterClass and Managed Topologies, a new feature that will greatly simplify how you can provision, upgrade, and operate multiple Kubernetes clusters in a declarative way.
A little bit of context…
Before getting into the details, let's take a step back and look at the history of Cluster API.
The Cluster API project started three years ago, and the first releases focused on extensibility and implementing a declarative API that allows a seamless experience across infrastructure providers. This was a success with many cloud providers: AWS, Azure, Digital Ocean, GCP, Metal3, vSphere and still counting.
With extensibility addressed, the focus shifted to features, like automatic control plane …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil reboot trailer looks like a welcome return to gaming roots]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1802183</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1802183"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T23:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Director Johannes Roberts wanted to evoke dark tone and scary aspects of the games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends' Halloween-themed Monsters Within event starts next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2171053</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-apex-legends-halloween-themed-monsters-within-event-starts-next-week"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T22:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends is getting in on the spooky action October inevitably brings with its special Halloween-themed Monsters Within limited-time event, starting next Tuesday, 12th October.
Monsters Within's most notable addition is Encore, a brand-new map for Arenas mode that whisks players off to Boreas, the home planet of recently introduced playable character Seer. This wide-open map is flanked by two high-ground power positions - the VIP Lounge and the Performance Stage - said to require strong environmental awareness, teamwork, and strategy if victory is to be secured.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPadOS 15 mini-review: It’s all about the home screen]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1802043</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1802043"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T22:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As an addendum to our iOS 15 review, we look at what's new on the iPad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blizzard announces Joe Shely as new Diablo 4 game director]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2171052</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-blizzard-announces-joe-shely-as-new-diablo-4-game-director"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T21:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blizzard has announced Joe Shely as the new game director on Diablo 4, following the departure of previous director Luis Barriga amid ongoing legal action by the California Department of Fair Employment and Housing alleging sexual harassment, discrimination, and a "frat boy" work culture at the studio.
Shely is a long-time Blizzard employee with game designer credits on the likes of Diablo 3: Reaper of Souls, and World of Warcraft expansions The Burning Crusade and Wrath of the Lich King, and has been a design lead on Diablo 4 since "the beginning".
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lunar samples returned by Chang’e-5 tell of recent volcanism]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1802125</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1802125"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T19:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Recent" is relative—the samples are roughly two billion years old.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare doesn’t have to cut off copyright-infringing websites, judge rules]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1802094</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1802094"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T18:43:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Judge rules content-delivery service doesn't "contribute" to copyright infringement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eidos Montreal announces move to four-day work week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2171043</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-eidos-montreal-announces-move-to-four-day-work-week"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eidos Montreal, the Square Enix studio behind the likes of Shadow of the Tomb Raider and the upcoming Guardians of the Galaxy game, has announced it's switching to a four-day working week - a move it hopes will "increase the productivity and well-being of our employees."
Announcing the initiative on its on its website, Eidos Montreal explained it would begin closing its Montreal and Sherbrooke studios each Fridays within the next few weeks - shifting its teams from the current 40-hour weekly work schedule to 32 hours "without changing the working conditions currently in place nor the salaries of employees".
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How bushmeat could help us meet the world’s climate goals]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801919</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801919"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T18:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s difficult but possible to meet human and environmental needs with wild meat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s fourth podcasting service will reportedly be “YouTube Podcasts“]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801974</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801974"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T17:19:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube already covers TV, Movies, Music, and Gaming, so sure, Podcasts are next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hands-on with Back 4 Blood’s retail version: Our three-hour stream is now on VOD]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1802034</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1802034"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T16:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you didn't watch and chat live on Twitch, we've preserved our session for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resident Evil movie gets first trailer, December release date in UK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2171032</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-resident-evil-movie-gets-first-trailer-december-release-date-in-uk"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T16:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been curious to know what Sony Pictures' latest stab at a Resident Evil film adaptation looks like, then wonder no more: the studio has offered up a first trailer alongside news that the movie will be getting a theatrical release on 3rd December in the UK.
Resident Evil: Welcome to Racoon City, to give the movie its full title, is directed by 47 Meters Down's Johannes Roberts and marks Sony's second crack at adapting Capcom's beloved survival horror series for the big screen, following on from Paul W. S. Anderson's Milla-Jovovich-starring six-movie take on the video game franchise.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Locke kids are not alright in official trailer for Locke and Key S2]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801801</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801801"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T16:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["This world has so much potential to be reborn. To be ruled."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GM’s next driver-assist system will be hands-free in “95% of situations”]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1802014</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1802014"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T16:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The advanced system will use lidar, cameras, and radar—and debut in a Cadillac.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scandinavian adventure Röki coming to PlayStation and Xbox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2171018</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-scandinavian-adventure-roki-coming-to-playstation-and-xbox"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scandinavian folklore adventure Röki is coming to PlayStation and Xbox consoles.
The game, previously only available on PC and Switch, follows Tove as she saves her family in a fantastical world of mythical creatures.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jabra owner goes after gaming with SteelSeries acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801977</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801977"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T15:48:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jabra parent company GN makes an approximately $1.2 billion deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scharon Harding</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tales of Arise adds new difficulties, weapons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2171010</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-tales-of-arise-adds-new-difficulties-weapons"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The enjoyable Tales of Arise gets a selection of new free and paid content today, including some fresh gameplay difficulties and yet more premium costumes. 
First up, for free, there's the addition of Very Easy and Unknown modes, which will offer new simple/extremely difficult gameplay options. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 bug could reduce Ryzen CPU performance by up to 15%, AMD says]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801973</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801973"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T15:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software fixes for the problems are coming later this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Halo: The Master Chief Collection gets its final season next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2171016</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-halo-the-master-chief-collection-gets-its-final-season-next-week"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T15:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[343 Industries is wrapping up updates for Halo: The Master Chief Collection with its announcement of the game's final season. 
Season eight goes medieval, with feudal armour sets inspired by mythical warriors, Roman warriors and beyond. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishraq Subhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safeway spent $367M to prepare for Theranos tests that never came]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801978</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801978"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T14:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Holmes' charisma sealed the deal, but Theranos never delivered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox 20th anniversary controller announced, unlocks exclusive background]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2171001</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-xbox-20th-anniversary-controller-on-the-way"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T14:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox is releasing special edition hardware to celebrate the 20th anniversary of the console in November.
That includes a £60/$70 controller with an exclusive dynamic background locked behind it, which disappears if you choose another background and disconnect the controller. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky partnering with Microsoft on new Kinect-like camera]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170987</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-sky-partnering-with-microsoft-on-new-kinect-like-camera"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T14:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The spirit of Kinect is being revived by Sky and moulded into the new - yet very familiar-looking - Sky Glass Camera, for release next year.
Sky is even partnering with Microsoft on the device's software, which will let you sync your TV with others to watch films, sport and telly shows in a group while video and text chatting (thanks, The Verge). It's like Snap never left.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Battlefield 2042 fans think it has too many bots, and they're just too OP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170990</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-battlefield-2042-fans-think-it-has-too-many-bots-and-theyre-just-too-op"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T14:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Players have been getting their first taste of Battlefield 2042 with the open beta now in early access. 
One of the game's main features is larger player counts for current-gen consoles and PC, with up to 128 players in a game. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishraq Subhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best video game trailer you'll see this week is about brake pads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170980</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-the-best-video-game-trailer-youll-see-this-week-is-about-brake-pads"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T14:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are game trailers, and then there are Polyphony Digital game trailers - overblown, melodramatic and frequently marvelous, the one that's just dropped to announce a new partnership with Brembo might well be a new favourite. 
It offers a brilliantly moody monochrome look within the factories of Italian brake manufacturer Brembo - a place I'd thought might have been fairly mundane, but the tense Hollywood soundtrack and loving shots of all that machinery have convinced me otherwise. By the time those pads had been bolted onto a GT3 Audi R8 I'll admit I was on the edge of my seat. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[StreamElements launch second Creator Diversity Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170968</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-streamelements-launch-second-creator-diversity-program"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T13:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applications are now open for the StreamElements Creator Diversity Program.
The programme, which began last year, aims to support creators from underrepresented groups on Twitch, YouTube and Facebook Gaming with a 12 month career accelerator.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arkane Lyon studio head leaves after 16 years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170966</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-arkane-lyon-studio-head-leaves-after-16-years"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T13:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Romuald Capron, the head of Arkane Lyon, is stepping down after 16 years at the studio. 
Capron stepped down last week, shortly after the launch of Deathloop, which received high acclaim across the board, and less than a year after the company became part of Microsoft. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishraq Subhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There's a new official Ashes cricket game, after a couple of years without]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170957</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-theres-a-new-official-ashes-cricket-game-after-a-couple-of-years-without"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T13:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cricket 22: The Official Game of The Ashes will launch next month, on 25th November for Steam, PlayStation and Xbox. 
Pre-order customers will get early access to The Nets Challenge, a portion of the game where you can train up ahead of the main release, later in October.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US gov’t will slap contractors with civil lawsuits for hiding breaches]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801922</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801922"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T12:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Civil Cyber-Fraud Initiative mandates data-breach reporting for gov't contractors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xbox Cloud Gaming now runs on Series X hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170930</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-xbox-cloud-gaming-now-runs-on-series-x-hardware"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Xbox Cloud Gaming service is now fully powered by Xbox Series X hardware. 
The company told The Verge it recently completed the upgrade, allowing for higher framerates and lower loading times. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishraq Subhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New database for gaming accessibility launches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170928</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-new-database-for-gaming-accessibility-launches"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T11:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new database for gaming accessibility has been launched, allowing players to make informed choices based on accessibility options.
Discussions around accessibility are becoming more open, with Sony promoting the abundance of features present in the likes of The Last of Us Part 2 and Ratchet & Clank: Rift Apart, and Psychonauts 2 developer Double Fine highlighting assist features.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best part of Windows 11 is a revamped Windows Subsystem for Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801283</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801283"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T10:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WSL is finally easy to install—and offers automatic sound/graphics support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Salter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EA "exploring" idea of dropping FIFA name]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170914</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-ea-exploring-idea-of-dropping-fifa-name"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T10:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Future FIFA games may give up the rights to use the FIFA name, EA has said.
In a blog posted ostensibly to trumpet the "record-breaking launch" of FIFA 22, EA also mentioned it was currently "exploring the idea of renaming" the franchise. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch confirms data exposed in major leak, but "no indication" passwords leaked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170903</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-twitch-confirms-data-exposed-in-major-leak"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a major leak of its source code, Twitch has commented in more detail via a new blog post confirming "some data" had been exposed, although there was "no indication" that login details had leaked.
The post follows an initial comment on Twitter from the Amazon-owned streaming platform, as previously reported.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Randy Pitchford steps down as Gearbox Software president]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170910</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-07-randy-pitchford-steps-down-as-gearbox-software-president"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gearbox Software co-founder Randy Pitchford is stepping down as president of the company. 
Replacing him in the position is former chief technology officer Steve Jones, while Pitchford remains CEO of The Gearbox Entertainment Company (the holding company of Gearbox Software) and president of Gearbox Studios, which will oversee Gearbox's development of film and television shows. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishraq Subhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citing liberty, Idaho Lt. Gov. McGeachin bans vaccine mandates in power grab]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801880</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801880"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T00:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gov. Brad Little will reverse all McGeachin's actions when he gets back to state.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHO recommends malaria vaccine for use in children]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801872</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801872"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T23:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the efficacy is under 50 percent, it should still save numerous lives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One America News founder claimed he started network at AT&T’s request]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801788</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801788"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T21:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T "told us they wanted a conservative network," OAN founder said in court.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nobel awarded for making common, cheap chemicals into catalysts]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801799</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801799"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T20:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Common chemicals can often work better than pricey metal catalysts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Timmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take a peek inside Steam Deck with Valve's latest promotional video]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170856</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-06-take-a-peek-inside-steam-deck-with-valves-latest-video"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T20:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're just a few months away from the first batch of Steam Decks shipping, and, in the run-up to release, Valve has ripped open its handheld gaming PC to give those curious sorts in the audience a quick peek at its decidedly compact innards.
"One of the most frequently asked questions we've received about Steam Deck," Valve's explains over on Steam, "is about the components inside it, and whether they're replaceable or upgradable. The answer is a bit more complicated than just a yes or no, so we've made a video to explain all the details."
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Among the Stars chronicles daring space mission to repair physics experiment]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1800732</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1800732"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T20:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alpha Magnetic Spectrometer studies cosmic rays from its perch on-board the ISS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firmware update brings new Conversation Boost feature to AirPods Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801711</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1801711"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T19:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cheapest AirPods haven't changed much, but Pro and Max got new features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announces official Xbox-inspired Adidas trainer range]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170853</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-06-microsoft-announces-official-xbox-inspired-adidas-trainer-range"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T18:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever loved something so much you wanted to put your feet in it? If you answered yes and the something you love is Xbox, then there's good news: Microsoft has teamed up with Adidas to launch a range of official Xbox shoes.
The foot-focussed collaboration, part of Microsoft's ongoing celebrations to mark 20 years since the launch of the original Xbox, begins with the arrival of the Xbox 20th Forum Tech - a pair of trainers sporting "translucent green details" said to be inspired by the Halo: Combat Evolved special edition Xbox, released back in 2001.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony ending credit card, debit card, and PayPal payments on PlayStation 3 and Vita]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170842</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-06-sony-ending-credit-card-debit-card-and-paypal-payments-on-playstation-3-and-vita"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T16:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony may have given the PlayStation 3 and Vita stores a last minute reprieve earlier this year following a consumer backlash, but its plans to rein in its legacy services continue, with the company now announcing it'll soon be removing the option to pay for items using credit cards, debit cards, and PayPal on its older consoles.
Writing on its Discontinued PlayStation apps, features and services page, Sony says customers will no longer be able to use the aforementioned payment options to either purchase digital content or to add funds to their wallets directly from their PS3 or Vita starting on 27th October.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grounded getting sizzling sandbox biome, first dungeon and more in "biggest update yet"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170172</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-01-grounded-getting-sizzling-sandbox-biome-first-dungeon-and-more-in-biggest-update-yet"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been just under 11 months since Obsidian launched inch-high garden survival adventure Grounded into early access for Xbox and PC, and as its one-year anniversary approaches, the team is readying Hot and Hazy, its "largest update yet", for a 20th October release.
Since Grounded's stellar launch last year - it attracted a million players within two days and 5 million within four months - the team, still relatively small at only 20 people, has continued to expand on its appealingly diminutive premise.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch source code leaked by anonymous hacker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170700</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-06-twitch-source-code-leaked-by-anonymous-hacker"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T15:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE 4.30pm UK: Twitch has finally acknowledged this morning's reports of a security breach and has said it is now investigating further.
"We can confirm a breach has taken place," Twitch said in a message posted to Twitter. "Our teams are working with urgency to understand the extent of this. We will update the community as soon as additional information is available. Thank you for bearing with us."
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animal Crossing Direct scheduled for Brewster's birthday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2170800</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-10-06-animal-crossing-direct-scheduled-for-brewsters-birthday"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T14:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announced during September's Nintendo Direct, the Animal Crossing Direct finally has a time and date.
Fans can tune in at 3pm UK time on 15th October for 20 minutes of information about new content coming to Animal Crossing New Horizons some time in November. Watch on the Nintendo YouTube channel.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Nightingale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Compelling Economics of Cloudflare R2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=11058</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/the-compelling-economics-of-cloudflare-r2/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare announced its own object storage offering last week, snarkily naming it “R2” instead of AWS’ “S3.” Storage is great, but let’s tie it to cloud economics here. We don’t have specifics as to edge case pricing dimensions, but Cloudflare’s blog post goes into some detail about how it works. First, it charges a rate […]
The post The Compelling Economics of Cloudflare R2 appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Syniverse Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/10/synaverse-hack.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/10/synaverse-hack.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T14:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3xpm8/company-that-routes-billions-of-text-messages-quietly-says-it-was-hacked">This</a> is interesting:</p>
<blockquote><p>A company that is a critical part of the global telecommunications infrastructure used by AT&#038;T, T-Mobile, Verizon and several others around the world such as Vodafone and China Mobile, quietly disclosed that hackers were inside its systems for years, impacting more than 200 of its clients and potentially millions of cellphone users worldwide.</p></blockquote>
<p>I&#8217;ve never heard of the company.</p>
<p>No details about the hack. It could be nothing. It could be a national intelligence service looking for information.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Air Travel Packing List]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2525/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2525/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/air_travel_packing_list.png" title="I know the etiquette is controversial, but I think it's rude when the person in front of me reclines their seat into the bell of my trumpet." alt="I know the etiquette is controversial, but I think it's rude when the person in front of me reclines their seat into the bell of my trumpet." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/update/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development satire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: A Closer Look at NSA/CISA Kubernetes Hardening Guidance]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/10/05/nsa-cisa-kubernetes-hardening-guidance/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/10/05/nsa-cisa-kubernetes-hardening-guidance/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Jim Angel (Google), Pushkar Joglekar (VMware), and Savitha
Raghunathan (Red Hat)
Disclaimer
Background
USA's National Security Agency (NSA) and the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure
Security Agency (CISA)
released, "Kubernetes Hardening Guidance"
on August 3rd, 2021. The guidance details threats to Kubernetes environments
and provides secure configuration guidance to minimize risk.
The following sections of this blog correlate to the sections in the NSA/CISA guidance.
Any missing sections are skipped because of limited opportunities to add
anything new to the existing content.
Note: This blog post is not a substitute for reading the guide. Reading the published
guidance is recommended before proceeding as the following content is
complementary.
Introduction and Threat Model
Note th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook Is Down]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/10/facebook-is-down.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/10/facebook-is-down.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T22:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Facebook &#8212; along with Instagram and WhatsApp &#8212; went <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/10/04/technology/facebook-down.html">down globally</a> today. Basically, someone <a href="https://krebsonsecurity.com/2021/10/what-happened-to-facebook-instagram-whatsapp/">deleted</a> their BGP records, which made their DNS <a href="https://twitter.com/GossiTheDog/status/1445065065527394321">fall apart</a>.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8230;at approximately 11:39 a.m. ET today (15:39 UTC), someone at Facebook caused an update to be made to the company&#8217;s Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) records. BGP is a mechanism by which Internet service providers of the world share information about which providers are responsible for routing Internet traffic to which specific groups of Internet addresses.</p>
<p>In simpler terms, sometime this morning Facebook took away the map telling the world&#8217;s computers how to find its various online properties. As a result, when one types Facebook.com into a web browser, the browser has no idea where to find Facebook.com, and so returns an error page...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cheating on Tests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/10/cheating-on-tests.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/10/cheating-on-tests.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T14:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Interesting <a href="https://boingboing.net/2021/10/02/test-takers-busted-for-using-bluetooth-connected-flip-flops-to-cheat.html">story</a> of test-takers in India using Bluetooth-connected flip-flops to communicate with accomplices while taking a test.</p>
<p>What&#8217;s interesting is how this cheating was discovered. It&#8217;s not that someone noticed the communication devices. It&#8217;s that the proctors noticed that cheating test takers were acting <a href="https://www.schneier.com/essays/archives/2004/11/profile_hinky.html">hinky</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comet Visitor]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2524/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2524/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/comet_visitor.png" title="It's a myth that the Great Wall of China is the only human-made structure visible from space--there are LOTS of structures for us to feel self-conscious about!" alt="It's a myth that the Great Wall of China is the only human-made structure visible from space--there are LOTS of structures for us to feel self-conscious about!" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: Squid Game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/10/friday-squid-blogging-squid-game.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/10/friday-squid-blogging-squid-game.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T21:22:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Netflix has a new series called <a href="https://www.denofgeek.com/tv/squid-game-review-netflix/"><em>Squid Game</em></a>, about people competing in a deadly game for money. It has nothing to do with actual squid.</p>
<p>As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.</p>
<p>Read my blog posting guidelines <a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2017/03/commenting_poli.html">here</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Death Due to Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/10/a-death-due-to-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/10/a-death-due-to-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T14:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The <i>Wall Street Journal</i> is <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/ransomware-hackers-hospital-first-alleged-death-11633008116">reporting</a> on a baby&#8217;s death at an Alabama hospital in 2019, which they argue was a direct result of the ransomware attack the hospital was undergoing.</p>
<blockquote><p>Amid the hack, fewer eyes were on the heart monitors &#8212; normally tracked on a large screen at the nurses&#8217; station, in addition to inside the delivery room. Attending obstetrician Katelyn Parnell texted the nurse manager that she would have delivered the baby by caesarean section had she seen the monitor readout. &#8220;I need u to help me understand why I was not notified.&#8221; In another text, Dr. Parnell wrote: &#8220;This was preventable.&#8221;...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Block Storage? A Definition and Overview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=11036</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/what-is-block-storage-a-definition-and-overview/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Block storage is a low-level technology that underpins the majority of modern storage — including whatever device you’re reading this on. It divides data into small units called “blocks,” which provide fast and flexible ways to manage data. It’s ideal for local storage and high-performance workloads. This is the first article in a three-part series […]
The post What is Block Storage? A Definition and Overview appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Endangered]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2523/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2523/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/endangered.png" title="The list includes polio, Guinea worm, and this one particular enterovirus strain that they've been tracking out of spite after it went around the lab a few years ago." alt="The list includes polio, Guinea worm, and this one particular enterovirus strain that they've been tracking out of spite after it went around the lab a few years ago." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hardening Your VPN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/hardening-your-vpn.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/hardening-your-vpn.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T16:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The NSA and CISA have <a href="https://www.nsa.gov/Press-Room/News-Highlights/Article/Article/2791320/nsa-cisa-release-guidance-on-selecting-and-hardening-remote-access-vpns/">released</a> a <a href="https://media.defense.gov/2021/Sep/28/2002863184/-1/-1/0/CSI_SELECTING-HARDENING-REMOTE-ACCESS-VPNS-20210928.PDF">document</a> on how to harden your VPN.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Actual Next Million Cloud Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=11028</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/the-actual-next-million-cloud-customers/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone says that the next million cloud customers are coming from enterprise IT. It’s the narrative that all of the major cloud platforms have been saying for a while — to the point that I started accepting it uncritically. I even recently wrote about those next million enterprise IT customers. Oof. No! That’s not how […]
The post The Actual Next Million Cloud Customers appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two-Factor Security Key]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2522/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2522/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/two_factor_security_key.png" title="The bruises on my fingertips are my proof of work." alt="The bruises on my fingertips are my proof of work." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: How to Handle Data Duplication in Data-Heavy Kubernetes Environments]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/09/29/how-to-handle-data-duplication-in-data-heavy-kubernetes-environments/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/09/29/how-to-handle-data-duplication-in-data-heavy-kubernetes-environments/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors:
Augustinas Stirbis (CAST AI)
Why Duplicate Data?
It’s convenient to create a copy of your application with a copy of its state for each team.
For example, you might want a separate database copy to test some significant schema changes
or develop other disruptive operations like bulk insert/delete/update...
Duplicating data takes a lot of time. That’s because you need first to download
all the data from a source block storage provider to compute and then send
it back to a storage provider again. There’s a lot of network traffic and CPU/RAM used in this process.
Hardware acceleration by offloading certain expensive operations to dedicated hardware is
always a huge performance boost. It reduces the time required to complete an operation by orders
of magnitude.
Volume Snapshots to the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check What Information Your Browser Leaks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/check-what-information-your-browser-leaks.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/check-what-information-your-browser-leaks.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T14:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These <a href="https://ipleak.net/">two</a> <a href="https://dnsleaktest.com/">sites</a> tell you what sorts of information you&#8217;re leaking from your browser.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tracking Stolen Cryptocurrencies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/tracking-stolen-cryptocurrencies.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/tracking-stolen-cryptocurrencies.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T11:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Good <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2021/09/22/stolen-crypto/">article</a> about the current state of cryptocurrency forensics.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Spotlight on SIG Node]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/09/27/sig-node-spotlight-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/09/27/sig-node-spotlight-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Dewan Ahmed, Red Hat
Introduction
In Kubernetes, a Node is a representation of a single machine in your cluster. SIG Node owns that very important Node component and supports various subprojects such as Kubelet, Container Runtime Interface (CRI) and more to support how the pods and host resources interact. In this blog, we have summarized our conversation with Elana Hashman (EH) & Sergey Kanzhelev (SK), who walk us through the various aspects of being a part of the SIG and share some insights about how others can get involved.
A summary of our conversation
Could you tell us a little about what SIG Node does?
SK: SIG Node is a vertical SIG responsible for the components that support the controlled interactions between the pods and host resources. We manage the lifecycle of pods that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: Person in Squid Suit Takes Dog for a Walk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/friday-squid-blogging-person-in-squid-suit-takes-dog-for-a-walk.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/friday-squid-blogging-person-in-squid-suit-takes-dog-for-a-walk.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T21:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>No, I don&#8217;t <a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/trending/ever-seen-a-squid-take-a-dog-for-a-walk-watch-hilarious-video-101631777302548.html">understand it</a>, either.</p>
<p>As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.</p>
<p>Read my blog posting guidelines <a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2017/03/commenting_poli.html">here</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Am Not Satoshi Nakamoto]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/i-am-not-satoshi-nakamoto.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/i-am-not-satoshi-nakamoto.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T19:05:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This isn&#8217;t the first time I&#8217;ve received an e-mail like this:</p>
<blockquote><p>Hey! I&#8217;ve done my research and looked at a lot of facts and old forgotten archives. I know that you are Satoshi, I do not want to tell anyone about this. I just wanted to say that you created weapons of mass destruction where niches remained poor and the rich got richer! When bitcoin first appeared, I was small, and alas, my family lost everything on this, you won&#8217;t find an apple in the winter garden, people only need strength and money. Sorry for the English, I am from Russia, I can write with errors. You are an amazingly intelligent person, very intelligent, but the road to hell is paved with good intentions. Once I dreamed of a better life for myself and my children, but this will never come &#8230;...</p></blockquote>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AWS dumps the mental burden of inconsistent APIs on developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=10990</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/how-aws-dumps-the-mental-burden-of-inconsistent-apis-on-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Years ago, I founded a company that built iPhone apps. And those apps needed web services.  Back in 2009, that meant you ordered rack-mounted servers at Dell, carried them into your local data center for colocation, and managed them by hand or through automation tools like Ansible. I vividly remember spending nights restoring crashed servers […]
The post How AWS dumps the mental burden of inconsistent APIs on developers appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luc van Donkersgoed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[17 More Ways to Run Containers on AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=10980</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/17-more-ways-to-run-containers-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It started as a meme, but it turned into a real post on “The 17 Ways to Run Containers on AWS.” Apparently my list continues to be a source of amusement inside of AWS. Given that I do prefer to give the people what they want, I’d like to talk about 17 more ways to […]
The post 17 More Ways to Run Containers on AWS appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your AWS Bill is Likely a Product of 2-Pizza Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=10952</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/awss-per-service-margins/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How AWS makes its billions — $13 billion in operating income in 2020 alone — to support the bulk of Amazon’s net income is a question that stumps the public. To shine some light on the topic, CNBC’s Jordan Novet published an article on AWS’ estimated margins on a per-service basis. Amazon obviously isn’t publishing […]
The post Why Your AWS Bill is Likely a Product of 2-Pizza Teams appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing Single Pod Access Mode for PersistentVolumes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/09/13/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/09/13/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chris Henzie (Google)
Last month's release of Kubernetes v1.22 introduced a new ReadWriteOncePod access mode for PersistentVolumes and PersistentVolumeClaims.
With this alpha feature, Kubernetes allows you to restrict volume access to a single pod in the cluster.
What are access modes and why are they important?
When using storage, there are different ways to model how that storage is consumed.
For example, a storage system like a network file share can have many users all reading and writing data simultaneously.
In other cases maybe everyone is allowed to read data but not write it.
For highly sensitive data, maybe only one user is allowed to read and write data but nobody else.
In the world of Kubernetes, access modes are the way you can define how durable storage is consumed.
Th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>