<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-09-19T12:27:52.375Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://shinomineko.github.io/feed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Jackbox Party Pack 8 is out next month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168211</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-19-the-jackbox-party-pack-8-is-out-next-month"/>
        <updated>2021-09-19T12:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good news for fans of party games - the eighth instalment of The Jackbox Party Pack is set to release on October 14, 2021.
If you missed the announcement teaser a couple of weeks back, here it is:
The Jackbox Party Pack 8 will feature five new games - Job Job, Weapons Drawn, Drawful Animate, the Wheel of Enormous Proportions, and Poll Mine. Here's how the developer describes each of the new games courtesy of a recent blog post (thanks, TheGamer):
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends servers are seeing three times more disconnects than usual]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168210</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-19-apex-legends-servers-are-seeing-three-times-more-disconnects-than-usual"/>
        <updated>2021-09-19T11:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No, it's not just you - Apex Legends' servers are unstable right now.
The problem first crept in a few days back, but despite fixes and assurances from Respawn that the issues had been rectified, the developer has since acknowledged that despite improvements, players are continuing to experience "roughly three times the normal rate of disconnect errors".
"We're ramping up our server capacity today and have some scheduled fixes for tomorrow. However, we believe some problems will require work through the weekend," the team announced on Friday.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some players are even cheating in Call of Duty: Vanguard's beta test now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168208</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-19-some-players-are-even-cheating-in-call-of-duty-vanguards-beta-test-now"/>
        <updated>2021-09-19T11:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Vanguard isn't even out yet, but players are already reporting that cheaters are out in force during this weekend's cross-platform beta test.
The heavily advertised anti-cheat measures have yet to be introduced, of course - which means the cheat systems players use in Warzone and Modern Warfare 2019 are very likely still functional - but nonetheless, the prevalence of in-game cheating is once again dominating the game's reddit and social media pages.
Right now the beta is only available for those who've pre-ordered the shooter but already players are reporting - and even providing video evidence - of what seem to be wall hacks and other cheats (thanks, VGC).
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fire weather is getting worse in the American West]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796359</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796359"/>
        <updated>2021-09-19T11:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change is driving more days that are hot, dry, and windy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[League of Legends players face new punishments for leaving matches and being AFK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168170</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-18-league-of-legends-players-face-new-punishments-for-leavers-and-being-afk"/>
        <updated>2021-09-18T17:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Riot Games has outlined changes it hopes will improve player behaviour when it comes to idling or leaving early in League of Legends. 
"We know that AFKs and leavers are some of the most disruptive behaviours you face, so we're happy to be coming to you today with an update around AFK and Leaver punishments." wrote BarackProbama and TimTamMonster in s blog on the game's official website.
Bundling both idle "AFK" behaviour and intentional quitters together as one single nuisance, the pair said that the team was introducing a number of new "prongs" to manage the issue, including new penalty "tiers" and a means of "shielding" players from repeat offenders.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sonic 30th Anniversary Symphony is available to stream now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168169</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-18-sonic-30th-anniversary-symphony-is-available-to-stream-now"/>
        <updated>2021-09-18T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sonic 30th Anniversary Symphony album is now available to stream on iTunes and Apple Music.
Not your preferred music streaming platform? Don't panic. According to Sonic's own social media manager, the album will be "rolling out to other services soon", "hopefully by next week" (thanks, NME).
Even if you're not a music streaming subscriber, however, you can sample the wonder of Sonic's music by the Tomoya Ohtani Band, Crush 40, and Sonic Adventure Music Experience by previewing the tracks right now on iTunes. No, you won't get the full-length glory of the FILMharmonic Orchestra Prague renditions, but even the brief snippets of the preview tracks are a wonderful treat.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sega's new mobile RPG is getting four times as many dislikes as likes on YouTube]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168168</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-18-segas-new-mobile-rpg-is-getting-four-times-as-many-dislikes-as-likes-on-youtube"/>
        <updated>2021-09-18T16:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember that surprise new mobile RPG that Sega teased yesterday? Well, people are already downvoting the reveal trailer on YouTube. 
Though we still don't know very much about it at all - right now all we have is a very brief teaser and a website with very little information on it - fans are registering their dismay that it's a mobile-only title in the only way they know how; by downvoting it.
Without knowing anything else about the new IP, the teaser trailer is currently racking up four times as many likes as dislikes on its Japanese-language YouTube account. While I can't attest to the flavour of the comments left in Japanese, the majority of English-language comments seem unhappy that the game is seemingly only coming to mobile devices which leave some fearing it will be "monetise[d] to death". 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new app helps Iranians hide messages in plain sight]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796375</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796375"/>
        <updated>2021-09-18T11:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nahoft uses encryption to turn chats into a random jumble of words.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dying Light 2 brings back degrading weapons - but this time with a twist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168148</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-18-dying-light-2-brings-back-degrading-weapons-but-this-time-with-a-twist"/>
        <updated>2021-09-18T10:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just like its predecessor, Dying Light 2 will feature weapon degradation.
Confirmation about the beleaguered zombie game's combat came in the latest instalment of the game's Dying 2 Know More series in which PR specialist Paulina Dziedziak spoke to producer Szymon Strauss.
However, things will be slightly different this time around. The team insists that because "the world has changed", the weapons we used in the original game "wore out". Although you'll occasionally come across a "high-tier" ready-made weapon, they're rare to find and pretty expensive, so we'll mostly be "building stuff from scraps and materials you find on the fly".
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google is getting caught in the antitrust net]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796339</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796339"/>
        <updated>2021-09-18T10:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One case in Turkey cuts to the heart of the search giant’s power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WIRED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diablo 2: Resurrected dev says players should "do what they feel is right" when it comes to buying the game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168145</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-18-diablo-2-resurrected-dev-says-players-should-do-what-they-feel-is-right-when-it-comes-to-buying-the-game"/>
        <updated>2021-09-18T09:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diablo 2: Resurrected director says players should "do what they feel is right" when deciding whether or not to support publisher Activision Blizzard by buying the remake when it goes on sale next week.
It's the first game the company has released since allegations of a "frat boy" work culture at Activision Blizzard were made by the California Department of Fair Employment and Housing, although it's important to note that the lead developer here is Vicarious Visions, which has not been involved nor implicated in the legal complaint.
"It was definitely very troubling to hear these types of things," design director Rob Gallerani told Axios (thanks, VGC). "And we really wanted to support our colleagues and our co-workers."
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jagged Alliance 3 is coming "soon" to PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168143</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-18-jagged-alliance-3-is-coming-soon-to-pc"/>
        <updated>2021-09-18T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THQ has confirmed Jagged Alliance 3 is in development.
While there's no estimated release window as yet, developer Haemimont Games - the same team behind recent Tropico games - has revealed the "beloved series" is coming "soon" to PC.
Here's the announcement trailer, which debuted yesterday: 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikki Blake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THQ Nordic makes its Destroy All Humans 2 remake official]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168130</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-17-thq-nordic-makes-its-destroy-all-humans-2-remake-official"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following some sneaky teasing earlier this year, and a spot of more recent leakage from Sony, THQ Nordic has officially confirmed that Destroy All Humans 2 is getting the remake treatment.
Destroy All Humans! 2 - Reprobed, as THQ is calling its latest remake, will be "developed from scratch" in Unreal Engine 4 by Black Forest Games, the studio behind the striking 2020 remake of the original Destroy All Humans.
The sequel, if you're unfamiliar, initially released for PlayStation 2 and Xbox back in 2006, serving up a second helping of comedic ET action charting the continuing adventures of Crypto as he rampages across the 1960s following the destruction of his mothership by the KGB - a chaotic journey that sees him soaking up (and blowing up) the sights in the US, UK, Soviet Union, Japan, and even to the moon. Expect all that in the remake, only prettier.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valve moves Dota 2 International to Romania, adds mask-and-vax rules]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796333</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796333"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T22:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valve's championship is the latest gaming event to implement strict pandemic rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Haske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDA advisors green-light Pfizer boosters for people 65+ and at-risk groups]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796430</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796430"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T22:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The committee roundly rejected approving boosters for everyone 16 and up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cult-classic sci-fi adventure Outcast is getting a sequel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168129</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-17-cult-classic-sci-fi-adventure-outcast-is-getting-a-sequel"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T21:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sequel to cult-classic sci-fi adventure Outcast is in the works, with original developer Appeal Studios once again at the helm.
Outcast 2: A New Beginning, as the sequel is known, unfolds 20 years after the original adventure (which released back in 1999) as preposterously named series protagonist, and ex-Navy Seal, Cutter Slade returns for another jaunt across the alien world of Adelpha. 
This time, the planet is under threat of invasion, as a ruthless army of robots begins enslaving and murdering its citizens. Cutter's mission - unfolding as a 3rd-person open-world action-adventure that should be familiar to fans of the original - is to mount a resistance, liberate the people, and rid Adelpha of the robot invaders once and for all.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: Ram’s Horn Squid Shells]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/friday-squid-blogging-rams-horn-squid-shells.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/friday-squid-blogging-rams-horn-squid-shells.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T21:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>You can find <a href="https://www.kentucky.com/news/nation-world/national/article254150943.html">ram&#8217;s horn squid shells</a> on beaches in Texas (and presumably elsewhere).</p>
<p>As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.</p>
<p>Read my blog posting guidelines <a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2017/03/commenting_poli.html">here</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SpaceX’s Starlink will come out of beta next month, Elon Musk says]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796340</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796340"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T20:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With 600,000 orders, SpaceX boosting dish production to (hopefully) meet demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomers solve centuries-old mystery of supernova observed in 1181]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796040</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796040"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T20:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Parker's Star" is surrounded by the Pa30 nebula discovered in 2013.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The iPhone 13, 13 mini, 13 Pro, and 13 Pro Max are available to order today]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796238</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796238"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T19:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ship dates for some configurations are already slipping to late October, though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FAA releases initial report on Boca Chica launches, and it’s not terrible]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796263</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796263"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T19:20:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Support is greatly appreciated!"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volkswagen’s electric ID.4 was already good—does AWD change that?]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796115</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796115"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T19:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We test out the new AWD version of the electric VW and visit its new factory.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Gitlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple and Google cave to Putin’s censors, block Navalny app as election begins]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796254</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796254"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T18:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Navalny app designed to boost opposition candidates deemed "illegal in Russia."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Brodkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIP Sir Clive Sinclair, creator of UK’s famed ZX Spectrum gaming computer]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796244</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796244"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T18:27:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Began his career as a mail-order radio salesman; failed to launch 1980s electric cars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monster Hunter Rise's Mega Man crossover arrives next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168120</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-17-monster-hunter-rises-mega-man-crossover-arrives-next-week"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T18:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monster Hunter Rise's schedule of Capcom-themed crossovers continues next Friday, 24th September, with the arrival of long-serving Mega Man character, Rush.
Capcom's Mega Man crossover - the fourth post-launch collaboration update to release for Monster Hunter Rise since its launch back in March - follows cameos for the likes of Okami's Amaterasu and Street Fighter 5's Akuma.
This time, though, players will be able to unlock a brand-new piece of layered armour turning their trusty Palamute companion into the Mega Man series' robo-canine Rush, even replacing the standard Palamute dash animation with the Rush Jet ability.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android 6 and up will start stripping unused apps’ permissions]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796167</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796167"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T18:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Play Services update will soon strip unused apps of their permissions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Amadeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook forced troll farm content on over 40% of all Americans each month]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796217</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796217"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T17:17:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Report blames Facebook’s prioritization of engagement over all else.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[36,000 gigatons of carbon heralded history’s biggest mass extinction]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1794311</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1794311"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T16:38:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New insights into the end-Permian mass extinction 252 million years ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sonic creator Yuji Naka is teaching himself how to program his own smartphone game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168103</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-17-sonic-creator-yuji-naka-says-hes-teaching-himself-how-to-program-his-own-smartphone-game"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T15:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yuji Naka, famed creator of Sonic the Hedgehog, has revealed he's teaching himself how to program his own smartphone game following his departure from Square Enix earlier this year.
Naka joined Square Enix in 2018, and his first project with the publisher - action-platformer Balan Wonderworld - was announced last summer for release this year. Unfortunately, Balan Wonderland was met with generally unfavourable reviews and disappointing sales when it launched in April, and Naka confirmed his departure from Square Enix in June. At the time, he told Twitter, "I'm 55 years old, so I may retire."
It seems Naka has been busy since then, however, and he's celebrated his birthday today by revealing some of what he's been up to since leaving Square. "Thank you for your birthday message," he wrote on Twitter. "Recently I've started studying programs again, and I'm making a simple game for smartphones with Unity."
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency launchpad hit by $3 million supply chain attack]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796093</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796093"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T14:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SushiSwap's MISO launchpad hacked via a malicious GitHub commit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ax Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Splitgate will have forge mode before Halo Infinite, dev insists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168087</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-17-splitgate-will-have-forge-mode-before-halo-infinite-dev-insists"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T14:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splitgate will get its own version of forge mode before it arrives in Halo Infinite, developer 1047 Games has said.
In a response to a tweet by KFCGaming of all places, the official Splitgate account announced the plans. 
Forge mode, which made its debut in Bungie's Halo 3, lets players edit and create playable maps that can then be shared with the community. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishraq Subhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell XPS 15 9510 review: Come for the screen, stay for everything else]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1793336</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1793336"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T14:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Limited ports and a midrange GPU don't detract much from an excellent laptop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram emerges as new dark web for cyber criminals]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796172</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796172"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T13:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing network of hackers sharing data leaks on encrypted messaging app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Financial Times</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dota 2 will soon remove support for 32-bit systems, Valve warns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168078</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-17-dota-2-will-soon-remove-support-for-32-bit-systems-valve-warns"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dota 2 will soon remove support for 32-bit systems, Valve has warned.
The mega-popular MOBA launched eight years ago, and Valve said it's time to leave older tech behind.
So, in the coming months, Dota 2 players will need to have a 64-bit machine and operating system to run the game.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like Warzone bans are being carried over to Call of Duty Vanguard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168070</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-17-looks-like-warzone-bans-are-being-carried-over-to-call-of-duty-vanguard"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T13:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reports are emerging that cheaters banned from Call of Duty Warzone are also banned from Call of Duty Vanguard servers. 
Screenshots from cheating Discord servers and forums appear to show that players who received a hardware ID ban on Warzone are unable to login to Vanguard's beta. 
CharlieIntel has independently confirmed that players who have received a hardware or account ban on Warzone are unable to play on Vanguard. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishraq Subhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bungie enables matchmaking help for those who get repeatedly thrashed 5-0 in Destiny 2's Trials of Osiris]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168062</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-17-bungie-enables-matchmaking-help-for-those-who-get-repeatedly-thrashed-5-0-in-destiny-2s-trials-of-osiris"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got smashed in Destiny 2's Trials of Osiris last weekend? Developer Bungie is making some changes to the 3v3 high-stakes PvP mode for this weekend that should help.
In a post on Bungie.net, the developer said it's making two key changes to matchmaking based on how things went on the successful reintroduction of Trials last weekend.
The first of these relates to the matchmaking for players after seven wins.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-Click iMessage Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/zero-click-imessage-exploit.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/zero-click-imessage-exploit.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T11:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Citizen Lab released a <a href="https://citizenlab.ca/2021/09/forcedentry-nso-group-imessage-zero-click-exploit-captured-in-the-wild/">report</a> on a zero-click iMessage exploit that is used in NSO Group&#8217;s Pegasus spyware.</p>
<p>Apple <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-ca/HT212807">patched</a> the vulnerability; everyone needs to update their OS immediately.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/09/13/technology/apple-software-update-spyware-nso-group.html">News</a> <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2021/09/13/pegasus-spyware-new-exploit-apple/">articles</a> <a href="https://news.trust.org/item/20210913191431-yc55r/">on</a> <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/3aq9q3/apple-patches-zero-click-imessage-hack-used-by-nso">the</a> <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2021/09/13/apple-zero-day-nso-pegasus/">exploit</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocket Report: Virgin Galactic delays flight, Falcon Heavy nets NASA mission]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1795961</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1795961"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T11:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["There was a large bang and some white smoke went up."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Berger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9-year-old Guild Wars 2 getting DirectX11 support to "help the game continue to look beautiful"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168027</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-17-9-year-old-guild-wars-2-getting-directx11-support-to-help-the-game-continue-to-look-beautiful"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guild Wars 2 is getting DirectX11 support soon, developer ArenaNet has said.
In a post on the Guild Wars 2 website, senior engine programmer James Fulop said a beta for the DirectX11 support goes live on 21st September.
Guild Wars 2, which launched in 2012, currently supports DirectX9.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why God Of War Ragnarok ends the Norse saga]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168014</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-17-why-god-of-war-ragnarok-ends-the-norse-saga"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T10:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we finally got a first look at God Of War Ragnarok during the PlayStation Showcase last week, Sony also confirmed the game is the last of the Norse mythology series. This took everyone by surprise, since the Greek mythology series had three mainline games. 
Now, in an interview with God of War YouTuber Kaptain Kuba, Santa Monica Studio's creative director Cory Barlog explained the decision.
"There are several reasons, I think one of the most important reasons is [time]," Barlog said. "The first game took five years. The second game, I don't know how long it's going to take but I'm just going to throw out that it's going to take close to a similar time, right, to do this. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishraq Subhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Castlevania Advance Collection rated for PS4, Xbox One, Nintendo Switch and PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168017</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-17-castlevania-advance-collection-rated-for-ps4-xbox-one-nintendo-switch-and-pc"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evidence is mounting for the near release of the so far unannounced Castlevania Advance Collection.
Gematsu reports the Taiwan Digital Game Rating Committee rated Castlevania Advance Collection for PlayStation 4, Xbox One, Switch and PC. The listing has since been deleted.
In the video below, Digital Foundry Retro's John Linneman looks at Castlevania Anniversary Collection and offers a series retrospective. It's well worth a watch if you're into Castlevania!
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Titan Quest and Jagged Alliance free to download and keep forever on PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168009</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-17-titan-quest-and-jagged-alliance-free-to-download-and-keep-forever-on-pc"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titan Quest Anniversary Edition and the Jagged Alliance 1: Gold Edition are free to download right now on PC.
Publisher THQ Nordic has made both games available to download and keep forever on Steam as part of its 10th anniversary. The offer ends at 6pm on 23rd September.
Titan Quest Anniversary Edition combines 2006 action role-playing game Titan Quest and its 2007 expansion Titan Quest Immortal Throne in one game. Donlan wrote about Titan Quest for our The Double-A Team series last year.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sega teases new mobile RPG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2168003</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-17-sega-teases-new-mobile-rpg"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T09:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sega has teased a new mobile role-playing game.
We don't know much of anything about the mystery RPG, but Sega did release a teaser video, below, which confirms an anime art style.
The teaser trailer also mentions the RPG is for mobile devices. A reveal is expected during the Tokyo Game Show on 1st October.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rover Replies]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2517/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2517/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/rover_replies.png" title="I'm so glad NASA let you take your phone to Mars!" alt="I'm so glad NASA let you take your phone to Mars!" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study confirms superior sound of a Stradivari is due to the varnish]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1792679</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1792679"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T23:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chemicals used to soak the wood include borax, zinc, copper, alum, and lime water.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Ouellette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Sacklers’ immunity threatened as DOJ moves to block opioid deal]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796036</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1796036"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T22:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DOJ argues the immunity is unconstitutional and expects the deal to be overturned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Mole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZX Spectrum creator Sir Clive Sinclair has died]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2167961</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-16-zx-spectrum-creator-sir-clive-sinclair-has-died"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T22:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sir Clive Sinclair, perhaps best known as the inventor of the enormously popular ZX Spectrum home computer, has died at the age of 81 following a long illness.
Although Sinclair found success creating a range of small calculators in the early 70s, it was the advent of his first, highly affordable mass-market computer in 1980, the ZX80 - which retailed for less than £100 - that helped make him a household name.
In 1982, the ZX80 and its successor the ZX81 were followed by one of Sinclair's most influential products, the ZX Spectrum - a colour-capable home computer that, thanks to its popularity, played a key role in kickstarting the British software industry, leading to the creation of some of the era's most iconic games, from Manic Miner, Chuckie Egg, and Jet Pac to Lords of Midnight, Knight Lore, and Horace Goes Skiing.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple sunsets the 256GB iPhone SE]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1795930</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1795930"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T22:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The change makes the iPhone SE compete less directly with the iPhone 13 mini.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Axon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo’s “thing after the Switch”: How an overheard convo sent me reeling]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/?p=1795870</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1795870"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T22:15:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shocking? Absolutely not. Yet this freak encounter has plenty worth chewing on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Machkovech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sherlock Holmes: Chapter One gets November release date on PS5, Xbox Series X/S, and PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2167951</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-16-sherlock-holmes-chapter-one-gets-november-release-date-on-ps5-xbox-series-x-s-and-pc"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T19:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sherlock Holmes: Chapter One, the latest entry in developer Frogwares' well-regarded deduction-based adventure series, now has a release date and will be coming to Xbox Series X/S, PS5, an PC on 16th November, with a PS4 and Xbox One release to follow.
Sherlock Holmes: Chapter One, as its name suggests, serves as a prequel to Frogwares' previous Sherlock Holmes titles, taking players back to the detective's days as a fresh-faced 21-year-old and the events that would lead to his life of sleuthing. It begins as Sherlock, with best friend Jon in tow, arrives on the sunny, Mediterranean-inspired island of Cordona - a significant aesthetic departure to the fog-shrouded London streets and rural corners of Frogwares' previous adventure - on the tenth anniversary of his mother's death.
Frogwares has already shared some of the new and returning mechanics players can expect in this latest third-person, open-world investigation adventure, but the developer has now offered some additional information in a new 7-minute gameplay "deep dive" trailer.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sea of Thieves teases a "forgotten world of adventure" beneath the waves for Season 4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2167942</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-16-sea-of-thieves-teases-a-forgotten-world-of-adventure-beneath-the-waves-for-season-4"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T18:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following its majestic, Pirates of the Caribbean infused third season, Sea of Thieves will be embarking on a new adventure next Thursday, 23rd September, with the arrival of Season 4.
As to what's in store this time around (beyond the inevitable fresh 100 levels of seasonal progression and rewards), Rare remains in a teasing mood, albeit dropping some major hints in Season 4's newly revealed announcement trailer.
It appears the malevolant sirens - which got a long-awaited and wonderfully orchestrated introduction during Season 3's A Pirate's Life campaign - are poised to play an even bigger role. Last season's spectacular Sunken Pearl Tall Tale took pirates down into the depths to visit the gorgeous coral-hewn home of the Siren Queen, and it seems we'll be visiting more areas of the sirens' long-lost kingdom once Season 4 gets underway.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Wales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EA sticks with loot boxes for FIFA 22 Ultimate Team, but adds preview packs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2167861</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-16-ea-sticks-with-loot-boxes-for-fifa-22-ultimate-team-but-adds-preview-packs"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FIFA 22 Ultimate Team features the mode's long-standing and controversial loot boxes, EA has confirmed.
However, EA will use the preview packs it trialed towards the end of FIFA 21's life.
In June, under increasing pressure from governments, children's welfare groups and gambling charities, EA added the ability to see what's inside FIFA 21 loot boxes before you buy them.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious new Nintendo Switch controller listed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2167911</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-16-mysterious-new-nintendo-switch-controller-listed"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The filing popped up today, and was first spotted by Twitter user SamusHunter2. It specifically notes the product is a "game controller" with the Nintendo Switch "HAC" peripheral prefix.
Details are scarce, as the rest of the listing is being deliberately obscured until Nintendo officially announces the product, or for up to 180 days (which would take us to March next year).
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Konami selling a £33 eFootball premium player pack you can't use until November]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2167905</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-16-konami-selling-a-gbp33-efootball-premium-player-pack-you-cant-use-until-november"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Konami has begun to unveil how it will monetise the free-to-download eFootball game, including a £33 premium player pack that gives you "chance deal items" you can't claim until November.
The premium player pack, for sale now on the PlayStation Store and Steam, offers six "chance deals" (plus two more if you pre-order).
A chance deal item lets you sign one of 16 featured players with an "exclusive design". These players include Lionel Messi, Neymar, Takefusa Kubo, Ansu Fati, Dayot Upamecano, Marcus Rashford and Jonathan dos Santos.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Aeon Must Die developer uses copyright claim to force trailer off publisher's YouTube channel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2167896</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-16-former-aeon-must-die-developer-uses-dmca-to-force-trailer-off-publishers-youtube-channel"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T14:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former Aeon Must Die developer has used a copyright claim to force the game's trailer off its publisher's YouTube channel.
Arsen Shakhbabyan, an animator who helped make the controversial Aeon Must Die trailer that first premiered during last year's PlayStation State of Play broadcast, had his attorney file the copyright claim after the trailer re-emerged on publisher Focus Home Interactive's YouTube channel last month.
The trailer for the game shown during the August 2020 State of Play, below, depicts a visually arresting beat-'em-up that caught the attention of PlayStation fans.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There's a new WipEout game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2167893</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-16-theres-a-new-wipeout-game"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T14:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WipEout Rush is a new game in PlayStation's legendary racing series - coming to iPhone and Android in early 2022. 
Yes, this is an official WipEout game - at least in name, anyway. The debut trailer, below, clearly shows PlayStation's trademark at the end. It will feature "unique card-based racing" and a single-player campaign.
WipEout Rush is developed by Rogue Games, a studio set up by former IGN journalist and co-founder Matt Casamassina. IGN has the exclusive on the game's reveal today:
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Valheim development has an end point, developer says, as Hearth and Home arrives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2167888</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-16-valheim-development-has-an-end-point-developer-says-as-hearth-and-home-arrives"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[today's big Hearth and Home update arrives. 
There's no suggestion we are close to that yet, but Iron Gate said it wanted to eventually polish off the project and move on - rather than keep it continually updated as a live service game or an MMO.
"Spoiler alert: this game will eventually have an ending. There will be a definitive ending where you beat the game, just so people understand," artist Robin Eyre explained in a 30 minute fireside chat developer video.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[343 to ditch Halo: The Master Chief Collection seasons after Halo Infinite comes out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2167878</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-16-343-to-ditch-halo-the-master-chief-collection-seasons-after-halo-infinite-comes-out"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T13:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[343 plans to ditch Halo: The Master Chief Collection's seasons after Halo Infinite comes out, it's signalled.
Season 8, which launches later this autumn, may prove to be MCC's last season, as 343 moves away from the game's season model to focus on smaller updates "that can land when they're ready based on development status and studio roadmap alignment".
343 insisted these updates will continue to be free and will include the unreleased features and content from this year, and it will make a continued effort to improve stability and tackle legacy fixes where possible. "We still have a lot of goodness to deliver in 2022," 343's publishing team lead producer Michael "Farns" Fahrny said in a post on Halo Waypoint.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Yin-Poole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Turismo 7's big new campaign will require an internet connection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2167851</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-16-gran-turismo-7s-big-new-campaign-will-require-an-internet-connection"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following some uncertainty after Gran Turismo 7's release date reveal last week and a subsequent blog post that stated one of the new campaign modes will require an online connection, Polyphony Digital has confirmed that an internet connection is necessary to play the game's main campaign. 
The addition of a fully fleshed out campaign is one of the key new features in Gran Turismo 7, following its absence at the heart of the online-focussed Gran Turismo Sport. Gran Turismo 7's campaign leans heavily on the series' past, allowing full modding and customisation of cars, as well as placing a fresh emphasis on the car collecting side with new and used dealerships and an all-new GT Cafe that lends some structure to the hoarding of cars. 
A blog post published in the immediate aftermath of the release date reveal stated that an online connection is required for GT Cafe, something series creator Kazunori Yamauchi was able to expand upon in a recent interview with Eurogamer. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tales of Arise breaks franchise records as it hits 1m sales milestone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eurogamer.net/article.php?article_id=2167859</id>
        <link href="https://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2021-09-16-tales-of-arise-breaks-franchise-records-as-it-hits-1m-sales-milestone"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T12:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bandai Namco role-player Tales of Arise has shifted 1m copies worldwide in under a week, breaking sales records for the long-running series. 
It means Arise is the fastest-selling Tales game ever, and the first to hit 1m copies in under seven days. 
Bandai Namco announced the milestone on Twitter today, and shared a celebratory image of the game's characters Alphen and Shionne. 
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying Computer-Generated Faces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/identifying-computer-generated-faces.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/identifying-computer-generated-faces.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T15:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s the <a href="https://techxplore.com/news/2021-09-computer-generated.html">eyes</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>The researchers note that in many cases, users can simply zoom in on the eyes of a person they suspect may not be real to spot the pupil irregularities. They also note that it would not be difficult to write software to spot such errors and for social media sites to use it to remove such content. Unfortunately, they also note that now that such irregularities have been identified, the people creating the fake pictures can simply add a feature to ensure the roundness of pupils.</p></blockquote>
<p>And the arms race continues&#8230;.</p>
<p>Research <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2109.00162">paper</a>.</p>
...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your AWS Bill is Likely a Product of 2-Pizza Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=10952</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/awss-per-service-margins/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How AWS makes its billions — $13 billion in operating income in 2020 alone — to support the bulk of Amazon’s net income is a question that stumps the public. To shine some light on the topic, CNBC’s Jordan Novet published an article on AWS’ estimated margins on a per-service basis. Amazon obviously isn’t publishing […]
The post Why Your AWS Bill is Likely a Product of 2-Pizza Teams appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hubble Tension]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2516/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2516/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/hubble_tension.png" title="Oh, wait, I might've had it set to kph instead of mph. But that would make the discrepancy even wider!" alt="Oh, wait, I might've had it set to kph instead of mph. But that would make the discrepancy even wider!" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Speaking Engagements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/upcoming-speaking-engagements-12.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/upcoming-speaking-engagements-12.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T17:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is a current list of where and when I am scheduled to speak:</p>
<ul>
<li>I’m keynoting <a href="https://www.ciisec.org/live">CIISec Live</a>—an all-online event—September 15-16, 2021.</li>
<li>I’m speaking at the <a href="https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com/online-summits/autumn-online-summit-emea-2021/"><cite>Infosecurity</cite> Magazine EMEA Autumn Online Summit</a> on September 21, 2021.</li>
<li>I’m speaking at the <a href="https://www.cailaw.org/Institute-for-Law-and-Technology/Events/2021/cybersecurity.html">Cybersecurity and Data Privacy Law Conference</a> in Plano, Texas, USA, September 22-23, 2021.</li>
<li>I’m speaking at the fourth annual <a href="https://web.cvent.com/event/58000922-1e88-4123-8935-c7462cc9e96e/summary">Managing Cyber Risk from the C-Suite</a> conference—a virtual event conducted through Webex—on October 5, 2021.</li>
<li>I’ll be speaking at an <a href="https://www.informa.com/">Informa</a> event on November 29, 2021. Details to come...</li></ul>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Contact-Tracing Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/designing-contact-tracing-apps.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/designing-contact-tracing-apps.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T11:41:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Susan Landau wrote an <a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.abi9852">essay</a> on the privacy, efficacy, and equity of contract-tracing smartphone apps.</p>
<p>Also see her <a href="https://mitpress.mit.edu/books/people-count">excellent book</a> on the topic.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vaccine Research]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2515/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2515/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/vaccine_research.png" title="Honestly feel a little sheepish about the amount of time and effort I spent confirming &quot;yes, the vaccine helps protect people from getting sick and dying&quot; but I guess everyone needs a hobby." alt="Honestly feel a little sheepish about the amount of time and effort I spent confirming &quot;yes, the vaccine helps protect people from getting sick and dying&quot; but I guess everyone needs a hobby." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Introducing Single Pod Access Mode for PersistentVolumes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/09/13/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-alpha/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/09/13/read-write-once-pod-access-mode-alpha/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chris Henzie (Google)
Last month's release of Kubernetes v1.22 introduced a new ReadWriteOncePod access mode for PersistentVolumes and PersistentVolumeClaims.
With this alpha feature, Kubernetes allows you to restrict volume access to a single pod in the cluster.
What are access modes and why are they important?
When using storage, there are different ways to model how that storage is consumed.
For example, a storage system like a network file share can have many users all reading and writing data simultaneously.
In other cases maybe everyone is allowed to read data but not write it.
For highly sensitive data, maybe only one user is allowed to read and write data but nobody else.
In the world of Kubernetes, access modes are the way you can define how durable storage is consumed.
Th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Squid Blogging: Possible Evidence of Squid Paternal Care]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/friday-squid-blogging-possible-evidence-of-squid-paternal-care.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/friday-squid-blogging-possible-evidence-of-squid-paternal-care.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T21:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Researchers <a href="https://phys.org/news/2021-09-evidence-paternal-bigfin-reef-squid.html">have found</a> possible evidence of paternal care among bigfin reef squid.</p>
<p>As usual, you can also use this squid post to talk about the security stories in the news that I haven’t covered.</p>
<p>Read my blog posting guidelines <a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2017/03/commenting_poli.html">here</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ProtonMail Now Keeps IP Logs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/protonmail-now-keeps-ip-logs.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/protonmail-now-keeps-ip-logs.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T11:10:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After being compelled by a Swiss court to monitor IP logs for a particular user, ProtonMail <a href="https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2021/09/privacy-focused-protonmail-provided-a-users-ip-address-to-authorities/">no</a> <a href="https://www.theregister.com/2021/09/07/protonmail_hands_user_ip_address_police/">longer</a> claims that &#8220;we do not keep any IP logs.&#8221;</p>
<p>EDITED TO ADD (9/14): This seems to be more complicated. ProtonMail is <a href="https://protonvpn.com/support/no-logs-vpn/">not yet saying</a> that they keep logs. Their <a href="https://protonmail.com/privacy-policy">privacy policy</a> still states that they do not keep logs except in certain circumstances, and outlines those circumstances. And ProtonMail&#8217;s warrant canary has an <a href="https://protonmail.com/blog/transparency-report/">interesting list</a> of data orders they have received from various authorities, whether they complied, and why or why not.</p>
...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lab Equipment]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2514/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2514/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/lab_equipment.png" title="I've been working on chocolate bar annealing techniques to try to produce the perfect laser s'more. Maybe don't mention that on the grant application though." alt="I've been working on chocolate bar annealing techniques to try to produce the perfect laser s'more. Maybe don't mention that on the grant application though." />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Detail on the Juniper Hack and the NSA PRNG Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/more-detail-on-the-juniper-hack-and-the-nsa-prng-backdoor.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/more-detail-on-the-juniper-hack-and-the-nsa-prng-backdoor.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T11:13:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We knew the basics of <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-09-02/juniper-mystery-attacks-traced-to-pentagon-role-and-chinese-hackers">this story</a>, but it&#8217;s good to have more detail.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2015/12/back_door_in_ju.html">Here&#8217;s me</a> in 2015 about this Juniper hack. <a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2007/11/the_strange_sto.html">Here&#8217;s me</a> in 2007 on the NSA backdoor.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(Most) SaaS Cost Tools Suck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=10898</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/saas-cost-tools-suck/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Periodically I get someone excited to talk to me about their new AWS bill optimization tool. This is the shorthand “cheat sheet” that addresses how I think about these things. It looks like you’re building a SaaS tool to manage AWS cost optimization. I don’t think it will work. Here’s why I don’t think it […]
The post (Most) SaaS Cost Tools Suck appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Risks of Relying on a Single Smartphone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/security-risks-of-relying-on-a-single-smartphone.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/security-risks-of-relying-on-a-single-smartphone.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T11:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Isracard used a single cell phone to communicate with credit card clients, and receive documents via WhatsApp. An employee <a href="https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/tech-news/.premium-how-not-to-use-whatsapp-israeli-credit-card-firm-learns-tough-lesson-1.10165329">stole the phone</a>. He reformatted the phone and replaced the SIM card, which was oddly the best possible outcome, given the circumstances. Using the data to steal money would have been much worse.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a link to an <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20210831031201/https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/tech-news/.premium-how-not-to-use-whatsapp-israeli-credit-card-firm-learns-tough-lesson-1.10165329">archived version</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saturn Hexagon]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2513/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2513/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/saturn_hexagon.png" title="Sorry, in SI units that's &quot;there's a big football in there.&quot;" alt="Sorry, in SI units that's &quot;there's a big football in there.&quot;" />]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning Cable with Embedded Eavesdropping]]></title>
        <id>https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/lightning-cable-with-embedded-eavesdropping.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2021/09/lightning-cable-with-embedded-eavesdropping.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T11:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Normal-looking cables (USB-C, Lightning, and so on) that <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/k789me/omg-cables-keylogger-usbc-lightning">exfiltrate data</a> over a wireless network.</p>
<p>I blogged about a previous prototype <a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2019/02/usb_cable_with_.html">here</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schneier on Security</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reusable Components]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/reusable-components/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/reusable-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development satire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Alpha in Kubernetes v1.22: API Server Tracing]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/09/03/api-server-tracing/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/09/03/api-server-tracing/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: David Ashpole (Google)
In distributed systems, it can be hard to figure out where problems are. You grep through one component's logs just to discover that the source of your problem is in another component.  You search there only to discover that you need to enable debug logs to figure out what really went wrong... And it goes on. The more complex the path your request takes, the harder it is to answer questions about where it went.  I've personally spent many hours doing this dance with a variety of Kubernetes components. Distributed tracing is a tool which is designed to help in these situations, and the Kubernetes API Server is, perhaps, the most important Kubernetes component to be able to debug. At Kubernetes' Sig Instrumentation, our mission is to make it easier to understa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hey AWS, You’re Missing Forrest for the Trees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=10862</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/hey-aws-youre-missing-forrest-for-the-trees/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cloud wars are getting a lot more interesting this week. A Cloud Guru’s senior director of content and community, AWS Serverless Hero, and friend of this newsletter (“Aaaah! DON’T CALL ME THAT! DON’T EVER CALL ME THAT!”) Forrest Brazeal has announced that he’s accepted a role as Google Cloud’s head of content. This has […]
The post Hey AWS, You’re Missing Forrest for the Trees appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine 3.11.12, 3.12.8 and 3.13.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.11.12-3.12.8.-3.13.6-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.11.12-3.12.8.-3.13.6-released.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine 3.11.12, 3.12.8 and 3.13.6 released]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alpine Linux News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Kubernetes 1.22: A New Design for Volume Populators]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/08/30/volume-populators-redesigned/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/08/30/volume-populators-redesigned/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors:
Ben Swartzlander (NetApp)
Kubernetes v1.22, released earlier this month, introduced a redesigned approach for volume
populators. Originally implemented
in v1.18, the API suffered from backwards compatibility issues. Kubernetes v1.22 includes a new API
field called dataSourceRef that fixes these problems.
Data sources
Earlier Kubernetes releases already added a dataSource field into the
PersistentVolumeClaim API,
used for cloning volumes and creating volumes from snapshots. You could use the dataSource field when
creating a new PVC, referencing either an existing PVC or a VolumeSnapshot in the same namespace.
That also modified the normal provisioning process so that instead of yielding an empty volume, the
new PVC contained the same data as either the cloned PVC or the cloned Volu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Minimum Ready Seconds for StatefulSets]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/08/27/minreadyseconds-statefulsets/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/08/27/minreadyseconds-statefulsets/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Ravi Gudimetla (Red Hat), Maciej Szulik (Red Hat)
This blog describes the notion of Availability for StatefulSet workloads, and a new alpha feature in Kubernetes 1.22 which adds minReadySeconds configuration for StatefulSets.
What problems does this solve?
Prior to Kubernetes 1.22 release, once a StatefulSet Pod is in the Ready state it is considered Available to receive traffic. For some of the StatefulSet workloads, it may not be the case. For example, a workload like Prometheus with multiple instances of Alertmanager, it should be considered Available only when Alertmanager's state transfer is complete, not when the Pod is in Ready state. Since minReadySeconds adds buffer, the state transfer may be complete before the Pod becomes Available. While this is not a fool proof way of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine 3.14.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.14.2-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://alpinelinux.org/posts/Alpine-3.14.2-released.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine 3.14.2 released]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alpine Linux News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Effectively Interview for Work with a Portfolio Site]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lastweekinaws.com/?p=10841</id>
        <link href="https://www.lastweekinaws.com/blog/how-to-effectively-interview-for-work-with-a-portfolio-site/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve taken the Cloud Resume Challenge, it’s reasonable to assume that you’re looking to start a career in the world of cloud computing. Congratulations or condolences, to your preference. There’s a good chance that in hopes of snaring your next great job, you’ve built a portfolio website on top of AWS to show off […]
The post How to Effectively Interview for Work with a Portfolio Site appeared first on Last Week in AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Quinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/meaning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.monkeyuser.com/2021/meaning/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development satire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MonkeyUser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog: Enable seccomp for all workloads with a new v1.22 alpha feature]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/08/25/seccomp-default/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2021/08/25/seccomp-default/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Grunert, Red Hat
This blog post is about a new Kubernetes feature introduced in v1.22, which adds
an additional security layer on top of the existing seccomp support. Seccomp is
a security mechanism for Linux processes to filter system calls (syscalls) based
on a set of defined rules. Applying seccomp profiles to containerized workloads
is one of the key tasks when it comes to enhancing the security of the
application deployment. Developers, site reliability engineers and
infrastructure administrators have to work hand in hand to create, distribute
and maintain the profiles over the applications life-cycle.
You can use the securityContext field of Pods and their
containers can be used to adjust security related configurations of the
workload. Kubernetes introduced dedicated …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes – Production-Grade Container Orchestration</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>